Resync @ http://capturewp.xyz“http://capturewp.xyz同步
The war ended, bahubali and bhlal dev战争结束了，bahubali和bhlal dev
showed politeness and mercy.表示礼貌和怜悯。
But like bahubali defended his people.但像bahubali辩护人。
By his impression, the queen以他的印象，女王
declared him the king..宣布他为国王
The people were happy,人们很高兴，
and queen was awaifi'ng for him.他和王后awaifi'ng。
Then the beast comes up,然后野兽来了，
who comes once In 26 years..26年来一次。
lt's the royal rules that the bride这是新娘的皇室规矩
of royal family goes to her test.王室去她的测试。
She's to go to temple bear foot她要去寺庙熊脚
toward the beast holding _re向控股_re野兽
fi'll the trouble goes away,麻烦会消失，
the feet shouldn't be stopped.脚不应该停止。
The queen..女王..
Did you ever feel that you你有没有感觉到你
should kill your mother.应该杀了你妈妈。
l felt, the lap you should get It.我觉得，圈你应该得到它。
After his birth, your mother他出生后，你母亲
gave him a half..给了他一半
Then l feltto kill him然后我feltto杀他
the seprafi'on In gold, kingdom,黄金seprafi'on，王国，
and all the rights.和所有的权利。
When she was giving him half当她给他一半
of evemhing, so l felt to kill her.对evemhing，所以我觉得杀了她。
When he's giving the kingdom,当他给了王国，
so l'm feeling to wreck his neck.所以我觉得要破坏他的脖子。
Do we kill him我们杀了他
lt's not your madhirapur.那不是你的madhirapur。
Whats up you dog..你的狗怎么了
What to bark?叫什么？
The bahuballi Is going的bahuballi会
to get the kingdom..得到王国。
Queen wanted you to know that..皇后想让你知道
lt happened that day,那天发生的，
my kingdom nominated to my brother.我的王国被我的兄弟提名。
And today my son's kingdom今天我儿子的王国
Is going to nominated to his son.将要提名他的儿子。
Will my generafi'on stay我将generafi'on停留
like a slave?像奴隶？
Why he's not nominated king.?为什么他没有被提名为国王？
l'm disable so?我禁用了吗？
l've iron hand..我有铁腕
The reason Is not your disabality原因是不是你的disabality
your disable brain.你的大脑失效。
You dog, one who insult royals你狗，侮辱王室的人
will be executed.将被执行。
Pardon me, think about killing原谅我，想想杀人
your wife..你的妻子..
You heared It..你听到了..
No l'm dog, l smelled It.不，我是狗，我闻到它。
She's the princess varohi.她是公主varohi。
lt Is said, there's no beaufi'ful这是说，没有beaufi'ful
woman like her In enfi're india.像她这样的女人在我在印度。
She hasn't shine In her eyes.她没有在她的眼中闪耀。
She don't deserve bahubali.她不值得bahubali。
Find someone else.找到别人。
Remember one thing, the girl will not记住一件事，女孩不会
be only bahubali's wife but queen too只有bahubali的妻子但女王
there shouldn't be any reason不应该有任何理由
to point her out指出来
you called me..你叫我..
Yes, you should go now for mission是的，你现在应该去执行任务
this fi'me Is not good for that..这是不好的fi'me ..
Why demi god's idol Is roaming In temple?为什么半神的偶像漫游在圣殿里？
So the demi god can see所以半神可以看到
the problem of people.人的问题。
When the future king goes out,当未来的国王出去，
so he _nds out the problem of poeple.所以他_nds出人的问题。
That old man ate my brain那个老人吃了我的脑
telling me stories.告诉我故事。
Till you'll come back, l'll _nd the直到你回来，我会_nd的
princess for you ..公主为你..
You're so amazing In this age.在这个时代你是如此的神奇。
You've not seen yet.你还没见过。
ln those days the girls never blinks在那些日子里女孩从不眨眼
when l play with the sword.当我玩弄剑。
This castle Is being build for you这座城堡正在为你建造
this bow and arrow for you,这是你的弓和箭，
which can target 50 feet可以瞄准50英尺
l'm gem'ng this In exchange我gem'ng这个交换
ofgiving kingdom to younger brother.?给天国的弟弟。？
l'm not so low that l grief for我不是那么低，我为
not gem'ng kingdom..不gem'ng王国..
Your orders are on my eyelashes.你的命令在我的睫毛上。
Don't insult me to give me gift.别侮辱我给我礼物。
What a power of veer bahadur.什么是转向Bahadur功率。
There're some robbers,有一些强盗，
and soldiers for catching them.和士兵抓他们。
She's using sword like flash.她用剑似的闪光。
Who can she be?她会是谁？
l can't see veer bahadur.我看不到改变他。
Two go there, _o tere.两个去，_o泰雷。
And 10 people stay here.还有10个人留在这里。
You're like a horse, and hiding你就像一匹马，藏起来
behind the women, don't you feel shame?在女人背后，你不觉得羞耻吗？
Please forgive me, my nephew请原谅我，我的侄子
Is the moron.是白痴。
He can't do anything right,他不能做任何正确的事，
so his family thorow him out.所以他的家人thorow他。
His own family?自己的家庭？
Yes.对.
You're kind..lfyou teach him something,你的那种..如果教他一些东西，
so l'll be obliged for life.所以我将终生感激。
He's tall, he can be soldier他很高，他可以当兵
If he learn to use sword.如果他学会了使用剑。
l'll teach him我会教他
princess, no bodody Is more公主，没有bodody更
religions than you In this kingdom.宗教比你在这个王国。
No.不.
Can't hit the _o bird by one arrow.不能用一支箭射中_o鸟。
Evemhing Is possibleevemhing是可能的
for my sister.给我妹妹。
You're teaching your你在教你
sister all this..姐姐这一切..
Will you choose one In purposals,你会选择一个purposals，
or l get you mary with my brother.或者我把你和我哥哥玛丽。
lt's a gada... you can't pick It up这是一个检测…你不能把它捡起来
lt's a spike, you can't hit It.这是个扣球，你打不到。
lt's a sword..这是一把剑..
Ty It性吧
tell me what do you know?告诉我你知道什么？
l know hide and seek, marbles我知道捉迷藏，大理石
and girls don't let me女孩不让我
play with them和他们一起玩
l'll teach you how to use sword.我会教你如何使用剑。
Pick It up and hit.捡起来打。
l can't do It..我不能这样做..
l'll show you again.我再给你看。
You hat It..你帽子..
What happpned to you.你什么happpned。
Princess Is coming.公主来了。
Brave soldiers like you像你这样勇敢的士兵
shouldn't do It..不应该这样做..
You may know It.你也许知道。
Yes, l forgot.是的，我忘记了。
We've to go to hunfi'ng In morning,我们去hunfi'ng早上，
the wildhog are ruining _elds..的wildhog毁了_elds ..
Farmers are complaining.农民抱怨。
He scares with the mouse,他用老鼠吓，
and taking him on hunfi'ng?和他在hunfi'ng？
lf he'll come with me,如果他跟我来，
so he'll know what he can do.所以他会知道他能做什么。
Bring him把他
good hit.好打。
Kumar verma amazing.库马尔Verma惊人。
He killed wildhog alone.他杀死了wildhog孤单。
Keep those corpse In cattle,把尸体放在牲口身上，
It will replic for new generafi'on它将为新的generafi'on拷贝
l was In doubt to see your acfi'ng我在怀疑，看到你的acfi'ng
what did you tell your name.你叫什么名字。
Shivo.Shivo。
This hands are wounded by war..这双手被战争伤了。
She's saying something..她在说些什么
He's just moron boy.他只是个低能儿。
Call the bahadur.打电话给他。
You give him the spike..你给他秒杀。
He killed my nephew,他杀了我侄子，
he hasn't loose his milk teeth他没有松开他的乳牙
who's gonna mary him...谁要去玛丽…
what do l do now?我现在该怎么办？
Didn't you hear the physician?你没听医生的话吗？
Give him this medicine.给他这种药。
How can someone sleep人怎么能睡
with a broken hand.手断了。
Who'll sing him lullaby谁会为他唱摇篮曲
l don't know.我不知道。
Will you sing a lullaby for him你会为他唱摇篮曲吗
lt's fi'me for worship demi god.这是fi'me敬拜神。
Bahubali reached to kundal village.巴虎巴丽达到kundal村。
Bahubali Is acfi'ng likebahubali是acfi'ng像
being moron是白痴
why do he need It.他为什么需要它。
He's already moron.他已经是白痴。
But why? l think he fell In love但是为什么呢？我想他恋爱了
with the princess.与公主。
lt's her painfi'ng.这是她painfi'ng。
Kingdom and princess Is his..王国和公主是他的..
l only should get It..我只应该得到它..
How come It possible.怎么可能呢。
Yu get the lover ofyour玉有情人你
younger brother,弟弟，
because she don't know that因为她不知道
brother loves her, l'll move _rst.哥哥很爱她，我会把_rst。
You didn't come In morning.你早上没来。
What happened..它怎么发生了。
Nothing..没有什么..
l know..我知道..
The new planet raised In west side.新行星在西边升起。
What're you saying.你在说什么。
l'm saying It..我是这么说的
Show me.向我展示.
The beauty by whcih通过这样的美
beaufi'ness feels shy.beaufi'ness感到害羞。
Who's she..她是谁
She's princess她是公主
since he saw this picture..自从他看到这张照片
The planet changed the direcfi'ons.地球改变了direcfi'ons。
Do you like the princess,你喜欢公主吗，
yes, l want that.是的，我想要。
You're asking like she's a doll你问她像个洋娃娃
why It's not possible..为什么这是不可能的..
She rejected the kingdom她拒绝了王国
lf l can't ful_ll his small desire,如果我不能ful_ll他的小愿望，
so what kinda mother l am.所以我有什么样的母亲。
Send the gold to dev battalion把黄金送到开发营
and also send the gold threat cloths并发送黄金威胁布
to royal family..皇室。
The royal sword of bhalladev.对bhalladev皇家剑。
Arrange the marriage with this sword.用这把剑安排婚姻。
Start preparafi'on for welcoming欢迎开始preparafi'on
the bride of our family.我们家的新娘。
The great queen writes to jaysena..伟大的王后写jaysena ..
Handsome like kamdev..英俊的像kamdev ..
Talented like great dev..天才像巨大的发展。
ln _ght..the great warrior..在_ght ..伟大的战士..
For my son..为了我的儿子
l've selected your sister我选了你妹妹
as life partner for my son.作为我儿子的终身伴侣。
Send your sister to my kingdom把你的妹妹送到我的王国
as my daughter-ln-law.作为我女儿的法律。
Till you'll come back. there'll be直到你回来。会有
a princess for you telling stories.给你讲故事的公主。
You selected her his life partner.你选中了她的终身伴侣。
Vey big kings and prince sends非常大的国王和王子发
us purposal to bond relafi'on with us.我们的目的relafi'on美国债券。
But our queen Is kind on you small kingdom.但是我们的女王对你很仁慈。
Princess Is vey lucky公主很幸运
to sending your sister to us,送你妹妹给我们，
all the gifts are yours..所有的礼物都是你的
You've never seen these kind你从未见过这种
ofgift ever In your life..ofgift曾经在你的生活中。
ls your queen like this or你的女王是这样还是
eveybody Is like this..每个人都是这样的..
People like you can move tail像你这样的人可以移动尾巴
for these kind ofgifts..这类礼物..
But these are like dust for me.但这些对我来说就像尘埃。
Uncapable person like him...他不喜欢的人…
our kingdom dogs won't mary.我们王国的狗不会玛丽。
lt's her decision... write your answer..这是她的决定…写下你的答案..
To shivgami devi..对shivgami德维..
The queen of kundaldev...对kundaldev女王…
ls wrifi'ng that...LS wrifi'ng…
what Is your son and what talented什么是你的儿子和什么才华
ls he, you want me to consider him他，你想让我考虑他
great by sending gifts..伟大的发送礼物..
But l think he's the guy who但我认为他是那个家伙
hides behind the woman... coward.躲在女人后面…胆小鬼.
l'm sending my sword with your gifts.我送你的礼物剑。
Put on those jewelley to your son把那些jewelley你儿子
tell him to mary my sword and告诉他我的剑和玛丽
come to my house..到我家来..
l'll take care of him like flowers.我会像花一样照顾他。
Vey politely...很有礼貌地…
devsena..devsena ..
Tell our commander that prepare告诉指挥官准备
for battle with them.与他们战斗。
Why to use sword for killing bird,为什么用剑杀人，
bahubali Is near that county.bahubali是附近县。
Send the message with eagle,用鹰发送信息，
he'll destroy them and bring princess.他会摧毁他们，带来公主。
Take devsena as prisoner.以devsena囚犯。
Send this message to bahubali.发送此消息给bahubali。
l heared that queen Is singing我听说女王在唱歌
the love song..爱之歌..
That moron.那个白痴。
There's good and bad news..有好消息和坏消息。
What do l give?我给了什么？
Both..what Is good, l'll tell you好的，我会告诉你
great queen has sent the大皇后派了
tambor for your marriage with devsena.对于你的婚姻devsena坦博尔。
Mother knows what l want.妈妈知道我想要什么。
But princess sent the answer但公主送来了答案
with anger and rejected purposal愤怒和拒绝的目的
lt Is the good news too..这也是个好消息
How, because she loves me怎么，因为她爱我
WeapOn.武器。
You used to walk like moron,你过去走路像白痴，
but today like brave.但今天像勇敢。
Where're you going.?你要去哪里？
To princess.公主。
How dare you go to meet你怎么敢去见
devsena In midnight.devsena在午夜。
Our kingdom Is In trouble,我们的王国陷入困境，
do what l say.照我说的去做。
lt's not fi'me to explain you.这是不是说明你fi'me。
you're touching me.?你在碰我？
Time gives chance once to时间给机会一次
become the great warrior.成为伟大的战士。
The god gives life, physician saves上帝赐予生命，医生拯救生命
the life, and warrior protects life生命，战士保护生命
princess...公主…
who are you?你是谁？
It's not fi'me to tell you告诉你，这不是fi'me
we're peacefull people we can't battle,我们是和平的人，我们不能战斗，
Ifthe thinking Is strong you can如果思维强你可以
your battalion are few..你的营很少。
Success Is low, are you ready成功率低，你准备好了吗
l couldn't know who are you.我不知道你是谁。
l said to you rubbish.我对你说垃圾。
l kicked you....我踢你…
when you kicked me, l felt your power.当你踢我，我感觉到你的力量。
lt's not blood, but the vermillion那不是血，但朱砂
who says you're worrior.谁说你的武士。
You saved us like demi god.你像半神一样拯救了我们。
Who're you?你是谁？
Where you from?你从哪来？
Let It go who am l ..让它去谁是我..
l come here because you can help us.我来这里是因为你能帮助我们。
What can we help to so great worrior.我们有什么可以帮到这么伟大的战士。
He's In love with a girl ofyour kingdom他爱上了一个女孩你的王国
who Is the lucky girl..谁是幸运的女孩..
Your princess.你的公主。
What else can be so happiness.还有什么可以如此幸福。
The relafi'ves hugs each other,的relafi'ves拥抱彼此，
never bow to each other.永不低头。
The queen sent the purposal女王派的目的
for this great worrior..这个伟大的战士..
Bahubali loves princess..bahubali爱的公主。
Queen never know that.女王永远不知道。
When you refused so she told当你拒绝，所以她告诉
to take you as prisoner把你当作囚犯
my mother can't make mistake,我妈妈不会犯错，
there's always reason what she says.她说的总是有道理的。
Come with me as a prisoner..跟我来当囚犯
You're my lover.. Ifyou take me as你是我的爱人如果你把我当作
a slave, l'll live with you all life.一个奴隶，我会和你一起生活。
ls evemhing _ne princess?LS evemhing _ne公主？
Your intenfi'on Is somewhere else你的intenfi'on是别的地方
you don't wory, queen will lookafter你不用担心，皇后会照顾
you like a daughter..你喜欢一个女儿..
l insulted you sending orders我侮辱你发送命令
sent you answer with anger愤怒地回答你
and hurt your feeling伤害你的感觉
can you forgive my anger?你能原谅我的愤怒吗？
The anger on daughter-ln-law女儿的愤怒
of shivgami looks good.对shivgami看起来不错。
Stand by your future husband..站在你未来的丈夫..
My decision Is right or wrong,我的决定是对的还是错的，
maheswafi' will see It.maheswafi '会看到它。
l've promised bhallal to mary devsena.我答应bhallal玛丽devsena。
Who're you to arrange my marriage你是谁安排我的婚姻
with someone with my permission有人与我的许可
an adult girl has right to choose成年女孩有权选择
his husband..他的丈夫。
Don't you have brain?你没有脑子吗？
How dare you talk to me like this你怎么敢这样跟我说话
make this angy girl like slave on knees.让本该女孩像奴隶在膝盖上。
lf anyone touch devsena..如果有人联系devsena。
So think you touch bahubali's sword.所以想你触摸bahubali的剑。
l've promised to protect devsena.我承诺要保护devsena。
You're going against the queen.你要对抗女王。
For the promise, and for truth and jusfi'ce.的承诺，并为真理和jusfi'ce。
lfyou've to go against anybody如果你去反对任何人
even the demi god..甚至半神。
lt's a true religion.这是真正的宗教。
lt's wrong to promise your son答应你儿子是不对的
without knowing girl's decision.不知道女孩的决定。
You made mistake.你犯了错误。
Shivgami made mistake?Shivgami错了吗？
You swallowed your mother when born.你生了你的母亲。
She grew up like her own son.她长大像她自己的儿子。
To annouce you prince?宣布你的王子吗？
Is that her mistake?那是她的错吗？
You want the kingdom..你想要的王国..
Or that devsena?或者说，devsena？
For the kingdom, l break my promise,对于王国，我打破我的承诺，
It's insult ofyour educafi'on.这是侮辱你的educafi'on。
The child of devgami..devgami的孩子..
Who's known as bhallaldev谁被称为bhallaldev
l'll protect this kingdom..我会保护这个王国
By taking oath ofgod以上帝的誓言
bhalaldev...bhalaldev…
Ionglive..ionglive ..
Bahubali means me..bahubali意味着我..
The protector of kingdom and princess.王国与公主的保护者。
And the member of battalion和营的成员
of bhalaldev对bhalaldev
lf l may lose my life while如果我失去了我的生命
protecfi'ng...protecfi'ng…
so l'll not think所以我不会想
l'm taking oath ofgreat queen.我宣誓的伟大女王。
Maheshmafi', since l'm adult,Maheshmafi，自从我成人，
my heart throbes for you我的心为你throbes
ln evey dream l saw you在梦中我看见你的每
on my head like crown.我的头像王冠。
After so many years and wars.经过这么多年和战争。
You've come to me,你来到我身边，
why're you running away from me.为什么你要离开我。
l loved you, and you refused me我爱你，你拒绝了我
and embraced bahubali拥抱bahubali
the sun raise on or not,太阳升起与否，
l'll set It down on west.我会把它放在西边。
You feeded an snake.你喂蛇。
One day he will sfi'ng you..有一天他会sfi'ng你..
You've never gone against me ever你从未背叛过我
because of me, you've crush In your family因为我，你迷恋你的家人
l'm vey sad about It..mother Is sad我对此很伤心..妈妈伤心
fi'll we give her grandson.我们会给她的孙子。
You have not bring gift for me?你没有给我带礼物吗？
l'm the slave who has no right我是没有权利的奴隶
to bless you..祝福你..
What can l give you..我能给你什么
l ask you what you can give me.我问你你能给我什么。
We've tradifi'on that grandpa hold我们tradifi'on爷爷住
the son when It born..儿子出生的时候..
Will you take my son on your lap?你能把我儿子抱在腿上吗？
The female fi'ger born the cub..女性fi'ger出生的幼崽..
Kumar hunted the fi'ger..库马尔把fi'ger ..
Is It true?这是真的吗？
When l've sword of bahubali In hand.当我bahubali手剑。
So an kid can kill the fi'ger.所以，一个孩子可以杀死fi'ger。
This Is happening In front ofyou这是发生在你的面前
and you're seeing It like idol?你看到它像偶像？
lt seems that you don't know似乎你不知道
our tradifi'on..我们的tradifi'on ..
lt's the right of king that to whome这是正确的，国王的人
he has to give designafi'on他给designafi'on
lt's all excuses..这都是借口
lt's the harmfull thing for kingdom这是王国的有害的东西
don't you know that..你不知道..
Removing the designafi'on of bahubali除bahubali的designafi'on
and giving to a an dog..给一只狗
Whoever comes here with gift for me.谁带着礼物来这里。
You have not give anything,你没有给任何东西，
will you give me what l ask for?你会给我我所要求的吗？
You've to sit on the maheswafi''s seat.你坐在maheswafi的座位。
lt's the wish of mine and people..这是我和人们的愿望
And It Is said, to ful_ll这是说，要ful_ll
the desire of people Is religion人的欲望是宗教
the wife of bahubali devsena Is accused对bahubali devsena妻子指责
that she cutted ofthe _ngers她剪的_ngers
ofthe commander..的指挥官..
On the order ofgreat queen shivgami对订单有shivgami女王
this hearing Is decided.这次听证会决定。
Do you want to say something你想说些什么吗
about your felony?关于你的重罪？
Without any hearing l've hand coughs,没有任何听力，我手上咳嗽，
and declared me a culprit.宣布我是罪犯。
What kind ofiusfi'ce Is It?这是什么样ofiusfi'ce？
You're culprit fi'll prove innocent.你是罪魁祸首将证明无罪。
Put yourjusfi'ce In river,把yourjusfi'ce河，
and excute yourjuy执行yourjuy
lfyou say a word against so...如果说反对这样…
with the pride and tall building,与骄傲和高楼大厦，
the kingdom never builds up.王国从未建立。
lt's fi'me to come..这是fi'me来..
So l said..所以我说..
J
Come from the other door.来自另一扇门。
not front door.不前门。
What Is the behavior, you're threfi'ng的行为是什么，你threfi'ng
the vicfi'm.是的vicfi
You're corssing limits,你穿越界限，
this iuy crossed the limits to cought这iuy交叉引起的限制
a pregnant woman一个怀孕的女人
whatever... the iusfi'ce无论什么...的iusfi'ce
Is equal for eveyone.每个人都是平等的。
Do you know what'd happened?你知道发生了什么事吗？
What'd happened devsena?发生了什么事devsena？
Shiva called all the woman a side..湿婆把所有女人都叫到一边。
He was tying to rape me..他想强奸我
So l cutted ofF his _ngers..所以我砍下了他的_ngers ..
You did wrong..你做错了..
You should know cut of his _nger你应该知道把他的_nger
but you should behead him但你要斩他
one side Is your educafi'on一边是你的educafi'on
and one side your religious preching.一边放进你的宗教。
The war be_een both,战争be_een两，
and In middle my sword.在我的剑中。
l'll always be ready to protect我会随时准备保护
the maheshwafi'maheshwafi
lf he stayed alive..如果他还活着..
Will live like king.活得像国王。
How can you sleep, he's provoking the你怎么能睡觉，他激怒了
people to come Ifyou've problem如果有问题，人们会来
we don't need king.我们不需要国王。
Someone Is playing game there,有人在那里玩游戏，
l'm afraid..恐怕..
What're you doing here alone?你一个人在这儿干什么？
Why he has come here/他为什么来这里/
forgive me lord, today he manage to escape.原谅我主，今天他设法逃脱。
Till tomorrow, l want his head In my hand.直到明天，我想要他的头在我手中。
Or your head will be on your hand.或你的头将在你的手。
Who's head?谁的头？
Bahubali's headbahubali的头
are you gone mad?你疯了吗？
You want to kill him?你想杀了他？
l'll kill his wife and kid too我也会杀了他的妻子和孩子
lfyou come be_een me,如果我来be_een，
so l'll forget that you're my father.所以我会忘记你是我的父亲。
l know my son vey well.我知道我的儿子很好。
lf he thinks about something,如果他想什么，
he'll do It done他会做的
we should tell this to bahubali我们应该把这一点告诉bahubali
he won't believe that his他不会相信他的
brother Is so mean.兄弟是如此吝啬。
There's only a way..只有一种方式..
What?什么？
lt's In your hand.在你手中。
You've to kill bhallal dev.你杀了bhallal发展
For bahubali and devsena.对于bahubali和devsena。
l don't understand whats happening.我不明白发生了什么。
The great order for kill bahubali杀bahubali大订单
by the shivgami's hand.由shivgami的手。
You're a small challenge.你是个小挑战。
Kumar and his people killed our库马尔和他的人民杀了我们
body guards保镖
and injured the king too也伤害了国王
after all this, now what're you thinking?毕竟，现在你在想什么？
What're you thinking shivgami,你怎么想的shivgami，
do your duty as a queen.履行你作为女王的职责。
Bhallaldev Is not your son only,是不是你的儿子只有bhallaldev，
but the king ofthis county但是这个国王
whoever tries to kill king..无论谁试图杀死国王..
He should be punished to death.他应该被处以死刑。
Your ancesstors took oath that你的ancesstors宣誓
they'll be always servant of kingdom他们将永远是王国的仆人
and they'll follow the orders of king.他们会听从国王的命令。
Are you sfi'll on that oath.你会在这一誓言，SFI。
Yes..对..
Order me.为了我。
Kill bahubali杀bahubali
what're you saying?你在说什么？
But why?但是为什么呢？
Do what you're said..照你说的做
l beg ofyou, take your words back.我求你了，把你的话。
Bahubali can't make this mistake.bahubali不能犯这样的错误。
You feeded her ..你喂她。
Now you've to kil him现在你要杀了他
l can't do this..我不能这样做..
Will you kill him..你会杀了他吗？
Or want me to kill him还是要我杀了他
this sin shouldn't be done这罪不该做
by your hands..由你的手..
l'll kill him..我会杀了他
Kattapa Is being punished for betraying.kattapa被惩罚背叛。
Haye you seen?Haye，你见过吗？
He promised me to take our他答应我带我们
kid In his lap.孩子在他的大腿。
Bring him safely..带他安全..
Leave me here..把我留在这里..
Ty to understand me.请理解我。
Let me die..让我死吧..
You promised my wife that你答应过我妻子
you'll take my son In your lap.你会把我的儿子抱在你的膝上。
And l promised my wife to我答应我的妻子
bring you safely把你安全
let me do my work..让我做我的工作..
l beg ofyou..我求你了。
Go from here.从这里走。
lt was order to kill you是为了杀你
take care of mother.照顾母亲。
l doubt on you for nothing katappa.没有你我不katappa。
You're my dog..你是我的狗
Now l'm bahubali..现在我bahubali ..
l'm the king of maheshwafi''s people我maheshwafi的人王
l'm taking oath of shivgami.我宣誓shivgami。
Moron queen.傻子皇后。
You're going to kill me,你要杀了我，
l made their trust..我得到了他们的信任
And l made write your death by her.我写了你的死亡。
And you were taking her oath你在宣誓
mOfOn aUeen..mofon aueen ..
When he was dieing, he was thinking当他死去，他想
about his wife and kid关于他的妻子和孩子
do you know what he said?你知道他说了什么吗？
Take care of mother.照顾母亲。
He asked for give bless他请求给予祝福
these hands snatch your husband.这些手抢走你丈夫。
Nafi'on Is cying because you've是因为你nafi'on伏
not annouced the death of bahubali不依照bahubali死亡
now come and announce..现在来宣布..
l'll take care ofthis kid.我会照顾这个孩子。
Call the iusfi'ce iuy, the culprits打电话给iusfi'ce iuy，罪犯
will be executed将被执行
the bahubali you loved alot,很多爱你的bahubali，
you _nd him guilty and killed him你_nd他有罪，杀了他
and l'm so mean, why will you forgive me.我如此吝啬，为什么你会原谅我。
Kill that kid..杀了那个孩子
lfyou will save my son, so l'll think如果要救我的儿子，所以我会想
that my husband Is alive.我丈夫还活着。
You've to come back..你必须回来..
l'll wait for you我会等你
will you come?你会来吗？
There was no stop on the cruelty残酷的事没有停止
of bhallal on kingdom.在王国的bhallal。
Because of his anger on devsena,因为他的怒气devsena，
he destroyed her county他毁了她的县
lf any left for you In this world如果你在这个世界上留下了什么
so It's me..所以是我..
We thought that you're dead,我们以为你死了，
but your grandma kept you alive.但你奶奶让你活着。
Make your hands like weapons..使你的手像武器..
The kingdom of maheswafi'..maheswafi王国的“..
And the previlages和特权
unfi'll l was thinking that..企业会认为..
l get safi's_ed by It..我safi's_ed通过它。
The iron made this chain..铁做了这条链子。
Will punish devsena..将惩罚devsena ..
l want devsena..我想devsena ..
Whoever supported her should无论谁支持她
be beheaded..被砍头的。
Or l'll behead you或者我会砍你的头
10 thousand family will scream1万家人会尖叫
and you'll be reach to death你会到达死亡
he lived with you for 9 months他和你一起住了9个月
In your womb..在你的子宫里
And you lived with me你和我一起生活
for 25 years..25年了。
So after his coming how那么他的到来之后
can you leave me alone.你能留下我独自。
Stop, how can l endure停下来，我怎么能忍受
that my mother Is In his prison我母亲在他的监狱里
let me die ...let me go.让我死吧，让我走。
Did your mother waited for your death?你母亲等你死了吗？
For his death.为了他的死亡。
You're the son of bahubali你的儿子bahubali
think like your father.像你父亲一样思考。
Like bahubali像bahubali
_nd those soldiers.._nd那些士兵。
What're you doing kattappa.你在做什么kattappa。
For so long your ancesstors这么长时间，你的ancesstors
were loyal to kingdom..忠于王国..
By destroying kingdom do you摧毁王国你
want to break your promise想打破你的承诺
_x up your mistake._x你的错误。
Kill his son like you像你杀他的儿子
killed bahubali..杀了bahubali ..
Go kattappa, kill him去kattappa，杀了他
25 years ago, queen declared25年前，女王宣布
bahubali our king.bahubali我们的国王。
Believing him dead,相信他死了，
l hided the truth.我隐藏的真相。
Today our truth has come back.今天我们的真相回来了。
Kattappa never breaks promise.kattappa从未打破的承诺。
Before you _nish the third round, l'll在你_nish第三回合，我会
keep ready creamafi'on to burn him alive.保持好creamafi'on烧他活着。
Till you will come back,直到你回来，
l'll keep your son's head on your hand.我会把你儿子的头放在你手上。
Whoever completed It.谁完成了它。
Can't be succesful不能成功
stop It... devsena's它停下来…devsena的
foot should be stopped.脚应停止。
Before complefi'ng temple stairs,在complefi'ng寺楼梯，
burn It down.烧毁它。
l thought you're dead,我以为你死了，
but you came back但你回来了
l can't tell you how happy l am..我不能告诉你我有多幸福
Why are you running away..你为什么逃跑..
l couldn't kill you我不能杀了你
you've come back having你回来了
that face..那张脸..
You gived me chance to你给了我机会
tear apart your chest.撕裂你的胸膛。
How do l thank you我该如何感谢你
when he'll scream by the pain当他将尖叫的痛苦
ofthe death的死亡
so maheshwafi' castle's wall所以maheshwafi城堡的墙
will be shrived..将赦免了..
lt's my _rst order after taking这是我的_rst订单后
the oath with queen shivgami.女王shivgami誓言。
Evey person who works with每个人的作品
jusfi'ce, honestly, good intenfi'onjusfi'ce，老实说，好的intenfi'on
will live with proudly..将自豪地生活..
lf someone did iniusfi'ce,如果真的有人iniusfi'ce，
so he'll be beheaded fi'll hell所以他将被斩首地狱
lt's my promise...这是我的承诺…
my promise Is my proud.我的承诺是我的骄傲。
Resync @ http://capturewp.xyz“http://capturewp.xyz同步