NINJA WARS忍者大战
Why do people fight each other?为什么人们互相打架？
Why do they kill each other?他们为什么互相残杀？
Although everyone says they advocate peace...虽然大家都说他们提倡和平…
Why does it happen?为什么会那样？
In Eiroku period [1558-1570], Japan was...在永禄时期[ 1558-1570 ]，日本…
in the middle of the Era of Civil Wars.内战中期。
Some books from those days contain...那些日子里的一些书…
...the name of the wizard, Kashin-koji.…精灵的名字，Kashin koji。
He was said to have changed into a据说他已经变成了一个
bird and to have revived the dead.鸟与复活死者。
Who on earth was the man?地球上的男人是谁？
That remains...剩下的…
...a mystery even today.即使今天还是个谜。
How beautiful it is.它是多么美丽。
Do you like it, Lady Ukyodayu.你喜欢吗，Lady Ukyodayu。
I am so glad. I appreciate it.我很高兴。我欣赏它。
With your remark, l, Danjo Hisahide...用你的话，我，Danjo Hisahide…
...feel my effort of building感受我努力的建筑
this castle tower is rewarded.这个城堡塔得到奖励。
Oh, you're joking again.哦，你又在开玩笑了。
No, I'm not joking, Milady.不，我不是开玩笑的，夫人。
Danjo.Danjo。
My wife is a naive person, so我妻子是个天真的人，所以
she cannot respond adequately.她不能作出充分的反应。
Do not concern yourself about her so much.不要那么担心她自己。
Oh, excuse me.哦，对不起。
My heart was captivated by her我的心被她迷住了
beauty, and without my knowing...美，没有我的了解…
...I behaved rudely. I apologize.我举止粗鲁。我向你道歉。
Sir Danjo.Danjo爵士。
So, shouldn't the tea be ready by now?那么，现在茶不该准备好了吗？
Yes.对.
I know.我知道.
Milady...夫人…
The tea-ceremony master of茶道大师
the country, Sen-no-Soeki...这个国家，没有soeki森…
...has made this tea with the用这种茶做的
best utensils of the country.全国最好的器皿。
This is very good artistry.这是非常好的艺术。
This teakettle with the spider relief is这茶壶与蜘蛛的救济
too good for Matsunaga Danjo to possess.Matsunaga Danjo拥有的太好了。
It could not be helped.它不能帮助。
He insisted it should be given to him for他坚持要把它交给他
the opening of the tea-ceremony room.开幕式茶艺室。
That man is like an animal.那人像动物。
He looked at you as if he他看着你，仿佛他
was watching a prostitute.看着妓女。
A prostitute?一个妓女吗？
What's the matter, Shinzaemon?怎么了，Shinzaemon？
Please do not move.请不要移动。
What's wrong?发生了什么？
Who are you?你是谁？
That's what one would expect of the这就是人们所期望的
head of the Yagyu manor, Shinzaemon.的柳生庄园的头，Shinzaemon。
You certainly detected你一定会发现
my coming, Shinzaemon.我来了，Shinzaemon。
Tell your name!告诉你的名字！
I am Kashin-koji.我叫Kashin koji。
Kashin?Kashin？
Kashin-koji.Kashin koji。
Danjo.Danjo。
I have come to realize your dream.我已经实现了你的梦想。
What?什么？
The one who captures the heart of Ukyodayu,谁抓住了ukyodayu心，
the wife of your lord, Miyoshi Yoshioki...你的主的妻子，Miyoshi Yoshioki…
...will have the country in his hands.将有国家在他的手中。
My divination sign tells me so.我的预言告诉我。
Is that true?是真的吗？
- You should not listen to him, Sir Danjo.你不应该听他的，Danjo爵士。
This man is of an evil spirit.这个人是邪恶的灵魂。
Wait!等待!
Are you going to disobey me, Shinza?你要服从我，Shinza？
Do you want to turn Yagyu你想把生
manor into a sea of blood?庄园变成血海？
Sir Danjo!Danjo爵士！
- No, don't say it!-不，不要说！
Otherwise, the kin of Yagyu will否则，对柳的亲属将
be extinguish from this earth.从这个世界被扑灭。
The tea ceremony is already over, Shinzaemon.茶仪式已经结束，Shinzaemon。
Danjo.Danjo。
He is gone.他走了。
Tell me, Kashin. How will I be able to get...告诉我，Kashin。我怎样才能得到…
...Ukyodayu... no, the country?…ukyodayu…不，国家？
You only need to trust...你只需要信任…
...my power.我的力量。
What?什么？
Rasetsuho.Rasetsuho。
Who is that man?那人是谁？
Just a little ninja.只是个小忍者。
Ninja?Ninja ?
So, who sent him?那么，是谁派他来的？
But, this is splendid.但是，这是辉煌的。
What this man did doesn't这个男人做了什么
look humanly possible.看起来可能。
But this is a human being.但这是一个人。
By the way, Danjo...顺便说一下，Danjo…
From today, I will...从今天起，我将…
...entrust my five disciples,委托我的五个门徒，
including Rasetsuho...包括Rasetsuho…
...to you, Danjo.你，Danjo。
Capture the heart of Ukyodayu...捕捉ukyodayu心…
And you will have this country under your rule.在你的统治下，你将拥有这个国家。
Love potion. It is a love potion.爱情药水。这是爱的药水。
Love potion?爱情药水吗？
The mystery will begin soon...神秘即将开始…
Kashin!Kashin！
I've done it.我已经做到了。
Kagaribi, you've finally masteredkagaribi，你终于掌握了
Ninja Art Mikagetsu-ken.忍者艺术mikagetsu肯。
Jotaro, I owe it all to your flute playing.Jotaro，这是我欠你的长笛演奏。
You have become a full-fledged female ninja.你已经成为一个成熟的女忍者。
From now on, you can fight enemies alone.从现在开始，你可以独自对抗敌人。
No. I don't want to if I am not with you, Jotaro.我不想如果我没有你，Jotaro。
Kagaribi, you're not a child any more.kagaribi，你不再是个孩子了。
If I'm with Jotaro, I will fight enemies.如果我是Jotaro，我会战斗的敌人。
Wait!等待!
Kagaribi!kagaribi！
Kagaribi. You will marrykagaribi。你要结婚了
whomever is decided by the chief.谁是由行政决定。
That is the rule.这就是规则。
I know.我知道.
But I have decided.但我已经决定。
I will tell the chief that...我会告诉长官…
No one but Kagaribi...但没有一kagaribi…
...can be my wife.……可以做我的妻子。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Why are you after us?你为什么跟着我们？
Take off your hat!取下你的帽子。
What do you want from us?你想从我们这里得到什么？
Fubuki Jotaro, we do notFubuki Jotaro，我们不
have any business with you.和你有任何生意。
What we want is that woman.我们想要的是那个女人。
What?什么？
Go tell the chief.去告诉酋长。
They aren't ordinary people.他们不是普通人。
But...但…
Hurry, Kagaribi.快点，Kagaribi。
Go!去！
Hurry.快点。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Go!去！
This is Suijubo's secret skill.这是Suijubo的秘密技巧。
Is this...?这是……吗？
He's dead, sir.他死了，先生。
Kashin-koji...Kashin曲…
He's a ninja.他是个忍者。
It seems that he deceived the他似乎欺骗了
enemy by pretending to be dead.假装死的敌人。
Is this...?这是……吗？
She looks exactly like Ukyodayu.她看起来很像Ukyodayu。
I will have this woman. Understand?我会有这个女人。明白了吗？
I will have her.我将拥有她。
We will give her to you, of course.我们当然会把她交给你。
But, it will be after we take the source但是，这将是后，我们采取的来源
of the love portion from this woman.从这个女人的爱的部分。
Is that right, Kokuuho?是吗，Kokuuho？
What?什么？
That's right.这是正确的.
She is a virgin with complete purity.她是纯洁纯洁的处女。
And she is related to Ukyodayu.她与ukyodayu。
The tears she'll shed when she'll她会流下的眼泪
be made into a woman by us...被我们变成女人…
...will be the source of the love将是爱的源泉
portion taught by Kashin-koji.Kashin koji教的部分。
Wait.等待.
Then, this girl is a relative of Ukyodayu?然后，这个女孩是ukyodayu相对？
She is her twin sister.她是她的孪生妹妹。
Twin?双胞胎？
Even if their father is an Ashikaga shogun,即使他们的父亲是足利幕府，
their mother is a married Christian woman.他们的母亲是已婚的基督徒妇女。
That's why Ukyodayu was这就是为什么Ukyodayu
adopted by a court noble.宫廷贵族收养。
And this girl was secretly abandoned.而这个女孩被秘密抛弃。
Is that right?你觉得那样对吗？
Good.好的。
If it's in order to make Ukyodayu fall in如果是为了让ukyodayu下降
love with me, nothing will stand in my way.爱我，什么也阻挡不了我。
Hurry and make this love potion. Hurry.匆忙做这爱药水。快点。
No, no. Please wait.不，请等。
We need to mix more than 10 kinds of我们需要混合超过10种
drugs imported from European countries...欧洲国家进口药品…
...with the tears of this woman...用这个女人的眼泪…
...and boil it down for about two hours.然后煮大约两个小时。
And the kettle needed to boil it down...和水壶需要煮下来…
Yes...对...
It should be the teakettle with the spider它应该与蜘蛛茶壶
figure, the most famous one in the country.图，全国最有名的一个。
Jotaro! Where is Jotaro?Jotaro！Jotaro在哪儿？
He's dead.他死了。
It's a lie!这是一个谎言！
If you're sad, cry.如果你悲伤，哭泣。
Cry! Hold a grudge against god!哭泣！对上帝怀恨在心！
The first big mistake is...第一大错误是…
...that people love each……人们彼此相爱
other and trust each other.相互信任。
Curse!诅咒！
Be crazed!是疯狂的！
And...和…
Let us make you into a woman.让我们把你变成一个女人。
This is wonderful!这是美妙的！
What the...什么的…
You!你！
What are you going to do?你打算怎么办？
Isaribi... Isaribi!isaribi…isaribi！
Why you! Have you gone crazy?为啥是你!你疯了吗？
You're disturbing us.你打扰我们了。
Kill them!杀了他们！
Don't let any of those monsters leave alive!别让那些怪物离开！
Milord.老爷。
Are you going to kill me?你要杀了我吗？
Stop. Stop!停止。停止！
You're...你是...
I can't believe it.简直无法相信。
And... why?和…为什么？
Why are you wearing Isaribi's clothes?你为什么穿着Isaribi的衣服？
Isaribi...isaribi…
Isaribi, have you been revived, too?isaribi，你已复活，太？
This... This head...!这…这头…！
Doesn't happen often but不经常发生，但
I've made a little mistake.我犯了一个小错误。
Did you exchange their heads?你交换他们的头了吗？
It was a little failure that...那是一个小小的失败…
...their blood didn't mix他们的血没有混合
well and she went insane.她疯了。
Their blood didn't mix well?他们的血混合得不好？
Yes, but...是的，但是…
Even if the face is Isaribi's, the body即使面对的是isaribi，身体
is that of a virgin with total purity.是纯洁纯洁的处女。
So, Kagaribi's heart remains in this woman.所以，kagaribi的心仍在这个女人。
Then... then... This woman is...然后…然后…这个女人…
And that woman is...那个女人是…
Please, Milord...请，Milord…
Please treat me with affection...请善待我…
Me, with the same face as Ukyodayu...我用同样的脸，Ukyodayu…
Please, now.请，现在。
What shall we name this woman?我们该给这个女人取什么名字？
Shall we call her "Onibi" [fire demon]我们叫她“onibi”[火妖]
from now on?从现在开始？
Kagaribi!kagaribi！
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Cry! Cry until you run out of tears!哭泣！哭直到你用完眼泪！
I want your tears.我想要你的眼泪。
By mixing the tears and more通过混合的眼泪和更多
than 10 kinds of drugs...超过10种药物…
...and boiling them down, this love potion然后把它们煮沸，这爱药水
is created. And we take a little of this.创建。我们采取了这一点。
Please look.请看。
After she drinks it, she will她喝完后，她会
love the first man she sees.爱她看到的第一个男人。
Will she be like this?她会像这样吗？
Will Ukyodayu be like this?Will Ukyodayu是这样的吗？
Yes, she will be more than this.是的，她会比这更多。
With the two of us alone...只有我们两个人…
Kagaribi!kagaribi！
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Jotaro. You're alive.Jotaro。你还活着。
I'm glad.我很高兴。
Who are you?你是谁？
Jotaro, Kagaribi has died.Jotaro，kagaribi已经死了。
What?什么？
Is that true?是真的吗？
She died.她死了。
Don't touch me!别碰我！
Kagaribi was raped.Kagaribi被强奸。
Raped?强奸？
That cross...交叉…
Jotaro!Jotaro！
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Kagaribi is no longer near you.kagaribi不再靠近你。
She cannot be near you.她不能靠近你。
If I am with you, Jotaro,如果我是你，Jotaro，
I will fight the enemies.我要与敌人作战。
Kagaribi...kagaribi…
What on earth...究竟是什么…
What on earth happened to Kagaribi?kagaribi到底怎么了？
Hagunbo, trace that smell.Hagunbo，微量的气味。
We underestimated her我们低估了她的
because she's a crazy woman.因为她是个疯女人。
Matsunaga Danjo and the five magic monks...Matsunaga Danjo和五魔僧…
Are you saying that they made you...你是说他们让你…
...go through such a thing?……经历这样的事情？
Just because Danjo wanted to...只是因为Danjo想…
...make your sister, Ukyodayu, love him!…让你的妹妹，Ukyodayu，爱他！
Just for that purpose.只是为了这个目的。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
I cannot die...我不能死…
I cannot die as it is.我不能死，因为它是。
Kagaribi...kagaribi…
I will definitely avenge you.我一定会为你报仇。
I'll drop Danjo and his five monsters into hell...我会把Danjo和他的五个怪物变成地狱…
And I'll make sure to protect your sister.我会保护你的妹妹。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Please think of this as Kagaribi.请把这作为kagaribi。
Jotaro... Jotaro...Jotaro…Jotaro…
Do not trust the woman who不要相信女人
has Kagaribi's face now...有kagaribi的脸现在…
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
What's wrong with your nose?你的鼻子怎么了？
He sprinkled some powder of prickly ash.他撒了一些花椒粉。
He must be carrying that injured woman.他一定带着那个受伤的女人。
Destroy the demons with our love.用我们的爱摧毁恶魔。
Kagaribi, I killed one of them.Kagaribi，我杀了他们中的一个。
Why?为什么？
I'm sure I...我肯定I. ..
We are immortal.我们是不朽的。
We'll take that teakettle.我们会把茶壶。
Kokubo!小久保！
Chief!首席！
Premises of Hattori Hanzo房屋Hattori Hanzo
Chief.首席。
Chief, Kagaribi was...长官，Kagaribi…
Say no more.不再说。
Jotaro, who decided KagaribiJotaro，谁决定kagaribi
was to be your wife?做你的妻子？
You have violated the rules...你违反了规则…
If you insist on fighting those men...如果你坚持和那些人战斗…
...leave the Iga clan.离开IgA家族。
Chief...首席…
Thank you for taking care of me for so long.谢谢你照顾我这么久。
Throw that away.扔掉那。
It is a source of misfortune.它是不幸的来源。
I won't throw it away.我不会把它扔掉。
Kagaribi was killed for this.kagaribi是杀了这。
It's also the proof of Danjo's evil.这也是Danjo的邪恶的证明。
Do not follow him!不要跟着他！
Goodbye, Jotaro.再见，Jotaro。
Hattori Hanzo drove theHattori Hanzo开车
youngster away from Iga manor?年轻人远离IgA庄园？
Hanzo...Hanzo…
Sensing that his manor will be destroyed,感觉他的庄园将被摧毁，
he tries to survive by cutting off his tail.他试图通过切断尾巴来生存。
It seems so.似乎如此。
My four comrades are searching我的四个同志正在搜寻
for that youngster now.为了那个年轻人。
He will be found soon.他很快就会找到的。
In three days in Todaiji temple...三天在Todaiji寺…
The "prayer for peace" ceremony和平祈祷仪式
by the Miyoshi family will be held.由Miyoshi家族将举行。
By having Ukyodayu drink通过ukyodayu喝
the love potion by then...那时的爱情药水…
I want to show Yoshioki her love for me.我想告诉Yoshioki，她对我的爱。
Teakettle. The teakettle.茶壶。茶壶。
Jotaro will come to Todaiji temple, Milord.Jotaro将到东大寺，Milord。
What?什么？
Jotaro must have heard about Ukyodayu...Jotaro一定听说过Ukyodayu…
...from Isaribi, who had the heart of Kagaribi.…从isaribi，谁有kagaribi心。
Jotaro will surely come toJotaro肯定会来
Todaiji temple for Ukyodayu.东大寺Ukyodayu。
Jotaro is that kind of man.Jotaro是那种人。
It may be as Onibi says.这可能是Onibi说的。
Isaribi's body and Kagaribi's head...isaribi的身体和kagaribi的头…
She must sense something.她必须感觉到什么。
Because something inside her tells her.因为她内心的东西告诉她。
Milord...Milord…
What?什么？
By the technique of dazzling...以眼花缭乱的手法…
...monk soldiers...和尚士兵…
I will...我会的...
...take the country.带着这个国家。
Three days later...三天后…
Todaiji Temple东大寺
Who are you?你是谁？
Where are you monk soldiers from?你从哪里来的僧兵？
The technique of dazzling!眼花缭乱的技巧！
What? Monks from some什么？僧侣从一些
unknown temple have attacked?无名寺遭袭？
Yes.对.
We don't know what this is about.我们不知道这是关于什么。
Damn! They set fire to Daibutsu-den!该死!他们放火烧了Daibutsu den！
[building that holds the great image of Buddha][拥有如来佛祖伟大形象的建筑]
Kill them! Kill them!杀了他们！杀了他们！
Milady!夫人！
Milady, please go first!夫人，请先去！
Who are you?你是谁？
What are you doing?你在做什么？
Damn you! Have you gone crazy?该死的你！你疯了吗？
Milord!老爷！
Milord! Milady... Milady was...老爷！夫人…夫人…
What happened to my wife?我老婆怎么了？
She was... taken by an她是…由一个
unidentified man... and...身份不明的人…和…
They went toward the Daibutsu-den.他们走向大佛的巢穴。
What?什么？
Lord!主！
Milord!老爷！
Milady!夫人！
- Watch out!-小心！
Milady.夫人。
I'm all right.我没事。
Milady, please stay here.夫人，请留在这里。
I'll look for medicine to cool your temperature.我会找药来冷却你的体温。
Wait. What is your name?等待.你的名字叫什么？
My name is Jotaro.我叫Jotaro。
Jotaro...Jotaro…
Lord! Lord! Please wait!主！主！请等待！
Shut up!闭嘴!
Lord, it's dangerous to ride主，骑是危险的
a horse in wilderness alone.独自在荒野中的马。
Lord!主！
Don't come near me!不要靠近我！
Is Kashin-koji a fool?Kashin koji是个傻瓜吗？
Say something.说点什么.
Milord.老爷。
I heard that Jotaro entered我听说Jotaro进入
the fire by his own choice.火由他自己选择。
His own choice?自己选择？
Jotaro is a ninja.Jotaro是忍者。
He must be somewhere with Ukyodayu...他一定在某个地方与Ukyodayu…
I'm sorry I'm back so late.很抱歉我回来得这么晚。
I went far for this today.今天我走了这么远。
It is a new wonder drug that'll这是一种新的神奇药物
cool down your temperature.冷却你的体温。
Why are you so nice to me?你为什么对我这么好？
Why did you help me?你为什么帮助我？
You can tell me now.你现在可以告诉我。
Milady.夫人。
Please only think getting请只考虑得到
well as soon as possible.以及尽快。
If you get well, you can return如果你康复了，你可以回来
to your mansion in Kyoto.到你在京都的豪宅。
I am not upset being here.我不是不高兴在这里。
I want to stay here.我想留在这里。
Jotaro, I don't know why, but...Jotaro，我不知道为什么，但…
I want to stay with you.我想和你在一起。
I want to stay with you forever.我想永远和你在一起。
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Kagaribi?Kagaribi？
Milady.夫人。
Kagaribi was a woman who was to be my wife.Kagaribi是一个女人做我的妻子。
Is that so?真的如此吗？
This is... her keepsake.这是...她的信物。
Milady...夫人…
I will tell you everything.我会告诉你一切。
Do you believe me?你相信我吗？
I trusted you from the beginning.我从一开始就信任你。
I entered the fire with you.我和你一起进了火。
Milady.夫人。
Jotaro, I'll return to the mansion...Jotaro，我会回到大厦…
But, in your physical condition...但是，在你的身体状况…
I'm all right.我没事。
I will disclose everything to Yoshioki and我要揭露一切Yoshioki
pay off my sister Kagaribi's old debts.还清我的妹妹Kagaribi的旧债。
Milady!夫人！
It's my duty as her sister.这是我的职责，她的妹妹。
I'll be all right.我会没事的。
"A monster has located you. "“一个怪物找到你了。”
"He will come back with“他会回来的
his comards. Get away. "他comards。走开。”
"Hurry!"“快点！”
Who wrote that?谁写的？
I do not know. But...我不知道。但…
We have no choice but to believe this now.我们别无选择，只能相信现在。
They're not here. They got away!他们不在这里。他们逃走了！
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Milady.夫人。
Jotaro, I'm sorry.Jotaro，我很抱歉。
Where are they?他们在哪里？
Where did they go?他们去哪里了？
Jotaro.Jotaro。
To fight those demons' evil power...去对抗那些恶魔的邪恶力量…
You need an equivalently你需要一个等价
strong heart to trust people.坚强的心去信任别人。
You have that heart.你有那颗心。
Please tell me your name at least.请至少告诉我你的名字。
I don't need a name.我不需要名字。
Milady...夫人…
Jotaro.Jotaro。
I shall surely tell about the我一定会讲
teakettle to my husband.茶壶我丈夫。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
I will certainly bring Milady to her mansion.我会把夫人她的豪宅。
Farewell! Do not die, Jotaro!再会!不要死，Jotaro！
Those five monsters...那五个怪物…
Who is that man named Jotaro?那个叫Jotaro的男人是谁？
He's a young man dressed like a他是个穿得像
mountain ascetic who helped me.山修道的帮助过我的人。
Milord, that man...Milord，那个男人…
- Silence!沉默！
If he had the teakettle with the spider figure...如果他用蜘蛛图有茶壶…
...that Sen-no-Soeki presented森没有soeki提出…
to Matsunaga Danjo...Matsunaga Danjo…
He must be a thief.他一定是个贼。
Wife, your mind is disturbed now.老婆，你的心现在不安了。
Milord.老爷。
Matsunaga is a horrible man.Matsunaga是一个可怕的人。
How many times do I have to我要做多少次
tell you before you understand?在你明白之前告诉你？
Matsunaga Danjo is the chiefMatsunaga Danjo是首席
vassal of the Miyoshi Family.三好家的附庸。
Are you telling me to believe a thief...你是要我相信一个小偷…
And the men dressed in穿着衣服的男人
black who brought you here?谁把你带到这里来的？
Milord.老爷。
Don't you believe anything I said?你不相信我说的话吗？
You don't believe a single thing.你不相信一件事。
The teakettle and Matsunaga...茶壶和Matsunaga…
Wife.妻子。
I will give the teakettle back to Danjo.我将茶壶回到Danjo。
So do not touch it! Understood?所以不要碰它！明白了吗？
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
You do not have to be so surprised.你不必如此惊讶。
Kashin knows everything thoroughly.Kashin知道一切彻底。
Is the love potion made from the是爱情药水制成的
teakettle at Miyoshi's mansion?在三好的豪宅呀？
And Ukyodayu too?和Ukyodayu吗？
Kashin, we have to hurry and settle this.Kashin，我们要赶快解决这。
Release me from your spell!释放我从你的法术！
Kashin! Kashin!Kashin！Kashin！
Kashin! Hurry!Kashin！快点！
You don't have to hurry. You have...你不必匆忙。你有…
...those five magic monks.那五个魔法和尚。
And...和…
...this woman. Too.这个女人。太。
Sooner or later...迟早会的。
What? Will Onibi be...?什么？Will Onibi是…？
Damned Jotaro...该死的Jotaro…
Who were those people on那些人是谁
horses who took them away?把他们带走的马？
The chief will find out who首领会找出谁
they are sooner or later.他们迟早。
My hunch tells me...我的直觉告诉我…
That they are definitely他们肯定
not people of the Iga clan.不是IgA族。
I can rely on the chief's hunch,我可以依靠的主要是直觉，
but I cannot rely on your hunch.但我不能依靠你的直觉。
Bastard.混蛋.
You've been resurrected你已经复活
many times thanks to me.很多次感谢我。
You cannot underestimate a doctor.你不能低估医生。
That's true. Thank you, doctor.那是真的。谢谢你，医生。
Now, you are no longer immortal.现在，你不再是不朽的。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Let's forget everything...让我们忘记一切…
And let's live happily together.让我们一起快乐地生活。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Please tell me one thing.请告诉我一件事。
Who were those men dressed那些穿着的男人是谁
in black and riding horses?在黑色和骑马？
Jotaro.Jotaro。
You will tell me, won't you?你会告诉我的，不是吗？
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
Who were those men dressed那些穿着的男人是谁
in black on horseback?骑在马背上？
Kagaribi.kagaribi。
I know now.我现在知道。
You're the monster who didn't show its face.你是那个没有露出脸的怪物。
I could have stolen your heart我可以偷走你的心
if you had held me longer.如果你再拥抱我。
It was unexpected to be这是意想不到的
disturbed by a dead woman!被一个死去的女人打扰！
What are you telling me?你告诉我什么？
Jotaro set the fire?Jotaro放的火？
No, it's not true.不，这不是真的。
I heard Jotaro confessed that he我听说Jotaro承认他
had set fire to Todaiji temple.火烧东大寺。
Anyway, it was judged无论如何，这是判断
that he will be beheaded.他将被斩首。
Beheaded?砍头？
And also...和也…
Danjo will come to our house soon...Danjo很快就会来我们家…
...to apologize for the inconvenience为不便道歉
caused by the thief at his castle.他城堡里的小偷造成的。
Everything will be settled if一切都将得到解决，如果
we return the teakettle then.然后我们返回茶壶。
That will be good.那将是好的。
That will truly be good.这将是真正的好。
Jotaro will be beheaded?Jotaro会被砍头？
What? Ukyodayu disappeared?什么？Ukyodayu消失了吗？
Without saying where she's going and by没有说她要去哪里
herself, she left dressed in travelling clothes...她自己穿着旅行服离开了…
Do not joke!不要开玩笑！
I will certainly find her.我一定会找到她。
Milord.老爷。
I will be Ukyodayu.我将ukyodayu。
While the true Ukyodayu is away from home...而真正的ukyodayu离开家…
I will claim to be Ukyodayu我会说是ukyodayu
and enter Miyoshi mansion.进入该大厦。
What?什么？
And I will play the role of the one我将扮演one的角色
who captured Lord Danjo's heart.谁抓住了主Danjo的心。
There's no need for her不需要她
to drink the love potion.喝爱的药水。
If Miyoshi Yoshioki, who is如果Miyoshi Yoshioki是谁
in love with Ukyodayu...在与Ukyodayu的爱情…
...happens to die of something...碰巧死于某事…
Ukyodayu is a daughter of the shogun.ukyodayu是一个将军的女儿。
You will have an enough ground to你将有足够的理由
take the country under your rule.把国家置于你的统治之下。
The country...国家…
But, if...但是，如果…
Milord.老爷。
In case the true Ukyodayu...如果真的ukyodayu…
...comes back one day...有一天回来…
I will behead her as an unpardonable imposter.我将她作为一个不可原谅的骗子斩首。
That is what is expected of Kashin-koji.这是Kashin曲会。
What's the matter?怎么了
Could you do what I asked?你能照我的要求去做吗？
Yes, I'll do it if it's for you, Miss Onibi.是的，我如果是你，Onibi小姐。
Jotaro, hurry.Jotaro，快点。
You...你…
I've come to help you.我是来帮你的。
I'm Ukyodayu.我是Ukyodayu。
Milady.夫人。
Why are you doing such a dangerous thing?你为什么做这种危险的事？
I tricked the gatekeeper into fetching the key.我哄骗看门人取钥匙。
Jotaro, we must hurry.Jotaro，我们必须快点。
Let's go.走吧.
The true Onibi went to Kyoto,真正的onibi去京都，
disguising herself as you.将自己伪装成你。
You disguised yourself as Onibi to come here.你伪装自己的Onibi来这里。
This is fate.这就是命运。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Milady, let's go.夫人，我们走吧。
You monster!你的怪物！
What's the matter?怎么了
Catch them!抓住他们！
Hold them down!把它们拿下来！
Jotaro!Jotaro！
I am glad that you've come back safely.我很高兴你平安归来。
And you no longer have any你不再拥有任何
sign of the madness you had.你疯狂的迹象。
I feel that I cannot believe it's true.我觉得我不能相信这是真的。
Wife.妻子。
You...你…
You are...你是...
Wife.妻子。
Who are you?你是谁？
I am Milady's new waiting maid.我夫人的侍女。
My name is Chidori.我叫Chidori。
Chidori?Chidori？
Milord, don't you like me?Milord，你不喜欢我吗？
No, I like you.不，我喜欢你。
I like you very much, Chidori!我很喜欢你，Chidori！
Tomorrow...明天...
Lord Danjo will come to主Danjo会来
pay his respects to you.向你致意。
Milord, you will do exactlyMilord，你会做什么
what I whisper into your heart.我耳语到你的心。
All right?一切都好吗？
Yes.对.
Milady!夫人！
The man in black...黑衣人…
The case of Todaiji temple...对东大寺的情况…
And the case of the teakettle和茶壶的情况
with the spider figure...用蜘蛛图…
...are attributable to my lack of virtue.是由于我缺乏美德。
I am very sorry.我很抱歉。
Yes.对.
It's all right.一切都好。
Everything is all right now.现在一切都好了。
This is the teakettle that was stolen.这是茶壶，被偷了。
Take it.把它。
This is truly...这是真正…
...the one stolen from the castle.那个从城堡里偷来的。
I accept this with appreciation.我接受这个赞赏。
Please wait!请等待！
Milady has already come back...夫人已经回来了…
What on earth is happening?地球发生了什么？
There are... There are two of you.有…有两个你。
Milord...Milord…
This woman is a fake.这个女人是假的。
No. The fake is that woman.不，假是那个女人。
Milord.老爷。
Please do not be deceived!请不要上当受骗！
Milord, that woman is the fake.Milord，那个女人是假的。
The voice is somewhat...声音有点…
But... But...但…但…
It is as if looking in a mirror...这就像在镜子里…
But there cannot be two.但不能有两个。
But...但…
The imposter...冒名顶替者…
...must be killed!必须被杀死！
Milord!老爷！
Milord...Milord…
Please hurry...请快点…
Kill the imposter.杀骗子。
Milord.老爷。
I cannot tell.我不能告诉。
I cannot anymore...我不能再…
I cannot tell anything anymore.我不能告诉任何东西了。
Milord!老爷！
Lord!主！
Lord! Lord!主！主！
Quiet down!安静下来！
Quiet down! Quiet down!安静下来！安静下来！
Lord Miyoshi Yoshiaki...Miyoshi Yoshiaki勋爵…
...went crazy and killed himself.发疯了，自杀了。
From now on...从现在起…
Guard of the Miyoshi Family's在三好家的警卫
territories is taken over...领土被接管…
...by Matsunaga Danjo,通过Matsunaga Danjo，
chief retainer of the family.家庭的主要家臣。
Nothing is better than the real thing.没有什么比真实的东西更好。
Isn't that right, Lady Ukyodayu?不是吗，Lady Ukyodayu？
Drink!喝！
You drink this!你喝这个！
Drink this...喝这个…
...and then look into my face.然后看着我的脸。
Burglar! Burglar!窃贼！窃贼！
Kill him!杀了他！
Danjo!男女！
Look at this, kid!看这个，孩子！
Jotaro!Jotaro！
You're a fool, kid!你是个傻瓜，孩子！
Who are you?你是谁？
Shinzaemon!shinzaemon！
Lord Yagyu!Lord Yagyu！
Danjo!男女！
Take this!把这！
Damn you, Kashin-koji.该死的，Kashin koji。
Jotaro!Jotaro！
Come out!出来！
Milady.夫人。
Jotaro! Jotaro!Jotaro！Jotaro！
Jotaro, I'm glad you are here.Jotaro，我很高兴你在这里。
The five monks were not unskilled.五个和尚不熟练。
Kashin!Kashin！
You are...你是...
Kashin-koji!Kashin koji！
Jotaro!Jotaro！
Milady!夫人！
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Milady.夫人。
Damn you, Kashin.该死的，Kashin。
Jotaro, do not come any closer.Jotaro，不要再靠近。
Don't come any closer.不要再靠近了。
Don't come any closer, Jotaro!别再靠近了，Jotaro！
Don't come any closer!不要再靠近了！
Please destroy the demon with our love.请用我们的爱摧毁恶魔。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
I love you, Jotaro.我爱你，Jotaro。
Please destroy the demon with our love.请用我们的爱摧毁恶魔。
Jotaro.Jotaro。
Love potion...爱情药水…
Fools...傻瓜…