- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[glass cracks][玻璃裂缝]
[birds chirping]【鸟叫声]
__
[panting][喘气]
[phone beeps][电话声]
[beeps][哔哔]
- [man] Hey, Lacie!- [人]嘿，LaCie！
- Hey! [giggles]-嘿！[笑声]
[phone beeps][电话声]
[camera clicks][相机点击]
["send" alert plays]“发送”警报
[phone beeps][电话声]
[giggles][笑声]
[laughing hysterically][大笑]
[Lacie] Ryan?【LaCie ]瑞恩？
[combat sounds on headset][战斗声音在耳机]
Ryan!瑞安！
- [yells]- [大叫]
- [explosion on headset]- [耳机上的爆炸]
- I was holding a bomb!-我拿着一个炸弹！
- [man] Come on![男人] 来吧！
Sorry, guys.对不起，伙计们。
Landlord is sending buyers over房东送买家过来
today so... put your pants on.今天如此…穿上你的裤子。
Maybe if I don't, it'll scare 'em也许如果我不，它会吓到他们
off and we can stay here.关闭，我们可以留在这里。
[singsong] Not an option, Ryan.[唱]不是一种选择，赖安。
Lease is up in four weeks.租约在四周内。
Hey, I'm thinking of you.嘿，我在想你。
I've got somewhere to go.我有地方要去。
Nate's roommate took a job in伊北的室友出去工作
Phoenix so I get his place.凤凰，所以我得到他的地方。
- Okay.-好的。
- Now who's the slow poke?-现在谁是慢拨？
I'm... seeing some places我是...看到一些地方
over lunch. Catch you later.在吃午饭的时候。稍后赶上你。
[gunfire on headset][耳机上的枪声]
Sorry, that was my sister.对不起，那是我妹妹。
Yeah. Yeah, I bet you'd love to.是啊.是的，我打赌你会喜欢的。
[man] Jasmine tea?[男人]贾斯敏茶？
[child giggles][笑]的孩子
[phone beeps][电话声]
[man] And that's one Brushed Suede.[人]，这是一个刷绒。
You want a cookie with that?你想要一块饼干吗？
- It's on the house.-它在房子里。
- Sounds awesome. [giggles]-听起来真棒。[笑声]
- [Lacie giggles]- [笑] LaCie
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- See you tomorrow, JJ.明天见你，JJ。
- See you, Lacie.你看，LaCie。
[laughs][笑]
[gasps] Oh, I saw your boy in[喘气]哦，我看到了你的男孩
the fire hat just now! So cute!刚才的火帽！太可爱了!
- Yeah, he's really something.-是的，他真的是。
- [laughs][笑]
[phone beeps][电话声]
[chuckles softly][笑]地
[laughs][笑]
[camera shutter clicks][相机快门点击]
Hmm.隐马尔可夫模型.
[phone beeps][电话声]
[phone beeps repeatedly][重复]电话哔哔声
[elevator bell dings][电梯铃声一响]
Hey, Lacie!嘿，LaCie！
- Bets, it's great to see you!-投注，很高兴见到你！
- You too.-你太。
[Lacie giggles][笑] LaCie
[cat meows][猫]
[Lacie] How's Pancakes?【LaCie ]如何的煎饼？
He's hilarious. Such a他很滑稽。这样的一个
funny cat. Just the best.有趣的猫。只是最好的。
[both laugh][都笑]
- Are you still at Hoddicker?-你还在hoddicker？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
- Yeah. It's going pretty great.-是的。这是非常伟大的。
- Good to hear.-很好听到。
- So what brings you back here?-那么是什么让你回到这里？
- New job, first day.-新工作，第一天。
- First day?-第一天？
- At Blankman-Harper.在Blankman Harper。
Whoa! Top floor! That's...哇！顶层！那是...
- Well, good luck.-好，祝你好运。
- I know, right? [laughs]-我知道，对吗？[笑]
It's great you're still这是伟大的你仍然
happy at Hoddicker.快乐的hoddicker。
- Well, maybe not forever.-嗯，也许不是永远。
- No, not forever.-不，不是永远。
- But for now...-但现在…
- It's OK for now.-现在是确定的。
It's great for now, yes. Yes, it is.这是伟大的，现在，是的。是的，它是。
[chattering][格格]
[phone ringing][电话铃声]
[phone beeps][电话声]
[beeping][哔]
[waves crashing, seagulls squawk]【海浪，海鸥的叫声]
Lacie, I got you a smoothie.莱斯，我给你买了个冰沙。
Got one for everyone, actually.给每个人都有一个，实际上。
Still a bunch of them for grabs.仍然是一群他们争夺。
They're from the organic他们是从有机
stall at the farmers' market.农贸市场的摊位。
Sure. Okay.当然.可以.
[gasps][喘气]
Mmm!嗯！
[phone beeps][电话声]
Thank you. Thank you.谢谢您.谢谢您.
[whispers] We're kind[低语]我们是善良的
of not talking to Ches.不谈Ches。
- 3.1? What happened?3.1？怎么搞的？
- Him and Gordon split up.-他和戈登分手了。
Oh...哦...
- Poor Ches.- Poor Ches。
- No, no, no, we're all on Gordon's side.-不，不，不，我们都在戈登的身边。
Sure! Obviously.当然!很明显。
Ches is kissing ass.Ches是拍马屁。
Trying to scrape himself back.试图把自己刮回来。
Of course, if it drops below two-five,当然，如果它下降到二五以下，
then it's... bye-bye.然后它的..再见.
[phone beeps][电话声]
[both gasp][两个喘息]
__
[phone beeping]【电话响】
[ringtone chiming][和谐]铃声
[Lacie] Hello?【LaCie ]你好吗？
- [Ryan] Yo, they're taking it.- [瑞安] 哟，他们正在服用它。
- Who?-谁？
The couple the landlord sent over.这对房东送过来的夫妻。
I heard them talking.我听见他们在说话。
Okay.可以.
So, now we move into所以，现在我们进入
the light space area.光空间面积。
Ideal for special times with loved ones.与所爱的人的特殊时代的理想。
- Great food, great company.-伟大的食物，伟大的公司。
- Mm-hmm!嗯，嗯！
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- Whoa! [laughs]哇哦！[笑]
[woman] Sampled your[女人]你的
photo stream to make her.照片流使她。
Great hair!伟大的毛！
[woman] Styled free of charge[女人]风格的免费
at the members' salon.在会员沙龙。
Oh, my God. [giggles]我的天！[笑声]
[Lacie] It's hilarious!【LaCie ]很有意思！
[woman] You like him?[女人]你喜欢他吗？
- He's okay.-他很好。
- He doesn't come with the apartment.-他不来的公寓。
[both laugh][都笑]
But there is a bar and restaurant但是有一个酒吧和餐馆
on site, tenants only.现场，租户只。
We have unparalleled我们拥有无与伦比的
metrics on romantic geneses.在浪漫的成因指标。
Uh-huh.嗯。
[woman] I gotta say,[女人]我必须说，
these places are going like "that."这些地方都是这样的“。”
- So don't delay if you're interested.-所以不要拖延，如果你有兴趣。
- Oh, I'm more than interested.-哦，我很感兴趣。
Standard occupancy on a标准占用
minimum six-month contract,六个六个月的合同，
we're talking... this much.我们在说话…这多。
- How often are the payments?-付款多久？
- That's weekly.-这是每周。
- Okay.-好的。
- [woman laughs][女人笑]
- A little more than expected?-比预期的多一点？
- Yeah.-是的。
There's options.有选项。
You know our Prime Influencers Programme?你知道我们的主要影响者的计划吗？
- Do I qualify for that?-我有资格做这个吗？
- No. No, you don't.不，不，你不知道
We'd need you around a 4.5.我们需要你在一个4.5。
4.5?4.5？
Hit 4.5 and there's a 20% discount.打4.5，有20%的折扣。
- 4.5.- 4.5。
- That's right.-这是正确的。
[sighs]【叹息】
[laughs][笑]
[laughter][笑]
[beeps][哔哔]
[laughs softly][温柔地笑]
Pelican Cove? What is this?鹈鹕湾？这是什么？
A eugenics programme?一个优生优育的计划吗？
- A lifestyle community.-一个生活方式社区。
- No one is this happy.-没有人是快乐的。
A two-year-old with a fucking一个两岁的孩子和一个他妈的
balloon isn't this happy.气球不是这个快乐。
It's actually a pretty cool place.它实际上是一个很酷的地方。
Like you'd even qualify.就像你甚至有资格。
There's nothing I can do, sir.我没有什么可以做的，先生。
[man] Well, it's not hopeless,[人]嗯，这不是没有希望，
you're clearly a tryer.你显然一个试验器。
That's the sense you get just from... me?这就是你从中得到的感觉…我？
From your rep report analytics.从你的报告分析。
If we drill down into the numbers,如果我们钻入数字，
you've got a solid popularity arc here.你有一个坚实的欢迎弧在这里。
Strong overall trajectory.强整体轨迹。
Let's just look at the last 24 hours.让我们看看过去的24个小时。
You see, even...你看，甚至…
What's that? 8:40 a.m. You're那是什么？早上8:40你
working hard on your socials.努力工作，你的社交活动。
- Great little uptake there.-几乎没有吸收。
- Okay.-好的。
Couple of minor dings there.有几个轻微的钟声。
You cut someone off in traffic?你切断交通了吗？
Oh, just a workplace thing. [laughs]哦，只是一个工作场所的事情。[笑]
Okay. Let's check on可以.让我们检查
your sphere of influence.你的影响范围。
Let me zoom out here.让我放大这里。
Great peripherals.伟大的外设。
Strangers like you, that's a plus.像你这样的陌生人，这是一个加分。
- Healthy inner circle. It's good.健康内圆。很好。
- Thank you. [giggles]-谢谢。[笑声]
There's a ways to go,有一种方法去，
but 4.5 is certainly achievable.但4.5肯定是可以实现的。
How long do you think?你认为多长时间？
- To hit 4.5?-要打4.5？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
Well, barring a major setback,好吧，除非有重大挫折，
a public disgrace kind of deal,公开羞辱的交易，
I'd say 18 months or so.我会说18个月左右。
Oh, I need more short term.哦，我需要更多的短期。
Like... much more. [laughs]像…更多。[笑]
Then you'll need a boost.然后你需要一个升压。
- What kind of a boost?-什么样的升压？
- Well...-好的…
Most of your interactions are你的大多数互动是
confined to your inner circle局限于你的内心
and they're largely, pardon the term,他们在很大程度上，赦免这个词，
mid-to low-range folks.中至低范围乡亲。
Same with your outer circle.和你的外圆一样。
You've got a ton of reciprocal five你有一吨的倒数五
stars from service industry workers,服务业工人的明星，
but there's not much else.但没有太多其他。
At least as far as I can see.至少就我所能看到的。
So in terms of quality,因此，在质量方面，
you could use a punch up right there.你可以用一拳在那里。
Ideally, that's up votes理想的情况下，这是上投票
from quality people.从质量人。
- Quality people?高质量的人？
- High fours.高四。
Impress those up-scale folks,给那些上规模的人留下深刻印象，
you'll gain velocity on your arc你会在你的弧线上获得速度
and there's your boost.还有你的提升。
[phone beeps][电话声]
[panting][喘气]
- Oh, hi, JJ!哦，嗨，JJ！
- Hey, Lacie!嘿，LaCie！
- Keith! Hello.-基思！你好.
- Lacie!-莱斯！
- [Keith] You look great today.- [基思]你今天看起来很不错。
- Thank you!-谢谢！
- Door won't open. I'm on 2.4.门开不开。我在2.4。
- Sorry, Ches. I'm late.对不起，Ches。我晚了。
I just need some stars, please!我只需要一些星星！
Fuck!性交!
[elevator bell dings][电梯铃声一响]
- Oh, hi!哦，嗨！
- Hi!-嗨！
- How's it going at Blankman?它怎么会在失神侠？
- Just great.-只是伟大。
- Well, I bet you work... good there.-嗯，我打赌你的工作…好的有。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
Would you like a croissant?你想牛角包？
They gave me an extra他们给了我一个额外的
at the coffee place.在咖啡的地方。
- Oh, no, I already ate.-哦，不，我已经吃过了。
- Okay, sure. All good. Yes.-好的，当然。所有的好。对.
Yeah.是啊.
- [elevator bell dings]- [电梯铃声一响]
- Well, here's me, so...-嗯，这是我，所以…
- [giggles]- [笑声]
- [phones beep][电话声]
Don't try too hard.不要太努力。
It's impossible to respect.这是不可能的尊重。
High fours can smell it高四能闻到它
a mile off. Just be you.一英里。只是你，
Authentic gestures, that's the key.<我的真实姿态，那是关键。
- That's time up, I'll catch you later.- 这是时间了，我会赶上你的。
- Oh, could I just ask...-哦，我可以问…
[phone chirps][电话声]
[beeping][哔]
[camera clicks][相机点击]
[chirps][声]
[mutters]... "Mr. Rags."[说]…”Rags先生。”
__
[exhales][气]
[sighs]【叹息】
[beeps][哔哔]
[laughs][笑]
[gasps][喘气]
Shit!倒霉!
- What the fuck is that?-那他妈的是什么？
- Tapenade. Want some?-酱。想要一些吗？
Who even are you?你是谁？
It's just something I wanna eat, Ryan.这只是我想吃的东西，赖安。
[phone beeps][电话声]
[gasps][喘气]
Oh, my God.我的天！
- What is it?-它是什么？
- Naomi!-内奥米！
Shit!倒霉!
Old school, el perfecto Naomi?老学校， EL PERFECTO 内奥米吗？
You guys keep in contact?你们保持联系吗？
Ryan, just go! Go!瑞安，只是去！去！
[Lacie] Oh, my God!【LaCie ]哦，我的上帝！
Nay-Nay, how are you? [giggles]Nay Nay，你好吗？[笑声]
I was just fixing myself a snack.我只是在给自己定一个点心。
Oh, Lace, could I just say I哦，蕾丝，我可以说我
am so happy to see your face?看到你的脸我很高兴吗？
- Me too. It's been...我也。它是…
- Too long.太长了。<
- Way too long.-太长。
- And that's my fault.- 这是我的错。
- No, it's mine. Everything is just so...-不，是我的。一切都是如此…
- Everything's just so...- 一切都是这样……
Crazy! Oh, it's so good to see you.疯子!哦，见到你真是太好了。
When you posted that当你发布的时候
Mr. Rags photo...Rags先生的照片……
I know, Mr. Rags!我知道，Rags先生！
I just had to call我只是打电话给
and talk to you because...和你说话是因为……
Whoo-hoo!喽！
[screams, laughs][尖叫，笑]
Wow! That's a... big ring! [laughs]真的!这是一个..大环！[笑]
Congratulations! Who's the, um... Paul?祝贺你!谁是，嗯…保罗？
He is great. So smart. Just sweet.他是伟大的。所以，聪明的。只是甜的，
I know you're gonna love him.<我知道你会爱他。
Uh-huh.嗯。
So, anyways, the big day...所以，不管怎么说，大日子……
Yes, when is it?是的，什么时候？
So, we're getting married in a month所以，我们要在一个月内结婚
on his family's estate /我>
up here on the island.。
This place outside Port Mary,这个地方在玛丽港外，
Honeysuckle. You heard of it?金银花。你听说过吗？
No, but...不，但…
Well, it's a private island.很好，这是一个私人岛屿。
[singsong] Take a looooook![唱] 采取looooook！
Oh, wow! That is... [giggles]哦，哇！这是…[笑声]
I know, right? So... can you make it?我知道，对吗？所以…你能做吗？
Are you kidding? Of course.你在开玩笑吧！当然.
Great, cool,伟大的，酷的，
cos I was wondering if...因为我在想……
Lace, do you think...蕾丝，你认为……
Would you be my maid of honour?你会是我的荣幸吗？
Seriously?真的吗？
Oh, my God.我的天！
I mean, you've got such cool我的意思是，你有这样的酷
friends now. Are you sure?现在的朋友。你确定吗？
Remember when we used to plan our记得当我们用来计划我们的
dream weddings when we were, like, 11?梦幻婚礼时，我们是，像，11？
- I know but we haven't s...-我知道，但我们没有..
- I don't know, just seeing Mr. Rags...-“我不知道，只是看到Rags先生……”
All the memories.所有的记忆。
It just brought things home.它只是把东西带回家。
Oh, Nay-Nay.哦，Nay Nay。
I know we haven't kept in touch我知道我们没有保持联系
as much as I'd have liked尽可能多的我喜欢的
and that is totally my fault,，这是我的错，
but this is a big day.但这是一个大日子。
A big life day and I want my oldest“我是一个大生命日，我想我的最古老的”
friend with me, my oldest friend.我的朋友，我最老的朋友。
I want you by my side.<我要你在我身边。<
Oh, my God. Thank you.我的天！谢谢您.
What do I have to...我必须要做什么…
Not much to it. A speech, mainly.<我不太多。一个演讲，主要是。
Speech? Of course!演讲？当然!
Mm-hmm. How big's the crowd?嗯，多大的人群？
Oh, my gosh, like...哦，我的天啊，像…
[sings] hundreds![唱] 上百！
It's a crazy guest list. I'll send it now.这是一个疯狂的客人名单。我现在就把它寄了。
Paul's invited so many,保罗邀请了这么多，
I don't want to call them big deals,我不想称他们为大交易，
but they're all, like, 4.7 or above.但他们都是，像，4.7或以上。
Uh-huh.嗯。
Nay-Nay, I will notNay Nay，我不会
let you down. [giggles]让你失望。[笑声]
Don't sweat too much!<我不流汗太多！
Just talk about old memories.只要谈论旧的记忆。
- Sure.-当然。
- How we were, any old things.- 我们是什么，有什么旧的东西。
- Gotcha.-明白了。
- I'll ping you some anecdotes.- <我会给你一些轶事。<
- That would be great.-这将是伟大的。
- And what's your dress size?- 和你的衣服大小是多少？
Oh, um...哦，嗯…
I'll tell you what,我会告诉你什么，
I'll just send you a four.我只给你一四个。
- Perfect.完美的。
- We got matching bridesmaids dresses.- 得到匹配的伴娘礼服。
Well, anyway...“我很好，反正……”
[both scream][两个尖叫]
[both laugh][都笑]
Love you, Lay.爱你，打下。
You too, Nay-Nay! [giggles]你也是，Nay Nay！[笑声]
Oh!哦!
Bye.
[laughs nervously][紧张地笑]
[beeping][哔]
[sighs]【叹息】
What was that? The F-word?那是什么？粗话？
You two pussy pals now?你们两个猫朋友了吗？
[sighs] Shut up.[叹息]闭嘴。
- She was always mean to you.-她总是对你意味着。
- No, she wasn't.-不，她不是。
- She had that rhyme about you.她有关于你的诗。
- That was a game.-这是一个游戏。
- What about when she cut your hair?-当她剪你的头发时，怎么办？
- I asked her to.-我问她。
She fucked Greg.她和格雷戈。
She... did not fuck Greg. [laughs]她…没有他妈的格雷戈。[笑]
She looked hot. I'll give her that.她看起来很热。我会给她。
[man] Okay.[男人]好的。
Impressive.令人印象深刻的。
- Uh-huh. Jesus. Yeah, that'd do it.-嗯哼。Jesus。是的，那会这样做。
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
[phone rings][电话铃声]
[woman] Pelican Cove.[女人]  鹈鹕湾。
Carole, it's Lacie. Saw the卡罗尔是LaCie。看到
place yesterday. I wanna take it.昨天。我想带走它。
That's fantastic!这是神奇的！
Uh... Oh, I see you're still…哦，我看到你仍然
on a 4.2. Is that, um...在一个4.2。是，嗯……
Yep, I'm on it, just gonna是的，我在这，只是
transfer the deposit now.转移存款。
- Well, okay.- 好吧，好吧。
- Yes!-是的！
In this world, we're all so在这个世界上，我们都是如此
caught up in our own heads.陷入我们自己的头上。
It's easy to lose sight of看不到它很容易
what's real. What matters.什么是真正的。什么是重要的。
But as I stand here today...但当我今天站在这里…
seeing the joy Paul has看到喜悦保罗有
brought to Naomi's life,给内奥米的生活，
I know she's someone我知道她是一个
who truly matters to me.谁对我真的很重要。
[laughs][笑]
Nay-Nay,Nay Nay，
the little girl who, when we were小女孩，当我们
just five-years-old in art camp,仅五岁在艺术夏令营，
started talking to me开始和我说话
because she saw I was scared.因为她看到我害怕。
The girl who helped me make帮我做的女孩
Mr. Rags. I still have him. [giggles]Rags先生。我仍然有他。[笑声]
He sits on my desk and...他坐在我的桌子上…
every day, he reminds me of Nay-Nay.每一天，他都让我想起了不。
What she meant to me then and now.她对我来说意味着什么，现在。
I am so honored to be here我很荣幸能在这里
and I wish you all the happiness我祝你所有的幸福
this stupid world can muster.这个愚蠢的世界可以鼓起。
I love you, Nay-Nay.我爱你，Nay Nay。
Is the tear too much?是眼泪太多了吗？
- You fucking sociopath.你他妈的变态。
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- Ryan, my car's here. Was it too much?-赖安，我的车在这里。是太多了吗？
- What, the tear, the photo, Mr. Rags?-什么，眼泪，照片，Rags先生？
I do keep him on my desk.我把他放在我的桌子上。
There's sugary and then有糖，然后
there's fucking diabetes.有他妈的糖尿病。
I just wanna make her我只想让她
happy on her wedding day.在她的婚礼上很高兴。
The captive audience of 4-point四俘虏观众
holies five-starring your ass off,五你所主演的屁股，
that's just a bonus.这只是一个额外的。
- Naomi and I were best friends.-内奥米和我是最好的朋友。
- [laughing] Come on...- [笑]来…
I wish her well and wanna我希望她很好，想
express it the best I can.表达它最好的我可以。
And, yeah, if I nail a speech而且，是的，如果我钉一个演讲
and get five-starred并获得五个主角
by hundreds of primes, so what?由数百个素数，所以什么？
It's a win-win.这是一个双赢的局面。
What are you hoping for? Like, 4.3, 4.4?你希望什么？喜欢，4.3，4.4？
Unh-unh. You get points呃-呃。你有点
from your gaming buddies.从你的游戏伙伴。
It's the same thing.还是一样的。
Don't shit on me for aiming higher.别为我的目标瞄准更高的。
Pelican Cove higher?鹈鹕湾高？
What's wrong with Pelican Cove?鹈鹕湾有什么错？
They're great apartments!他们是伟大的公寓！
- They are fake-smile jail cells.-他们是假微笑的监狱细胞。
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
Great. Car cancelled.伟大的.汽车取消了。
And he marked me down so now I have他让我失望，所以我现在
to book another, and I took a ding.另一个，我拿了一个丁。
- Great job.-伟大的工作。
- I am sorry, but I miss the normal you.-我很抱歉，但我错过了正常的你。
Before this obsession, when we在这种痴迷之前，当我们
had conversations, remember?有对话，记得吗？
I need my charger.我需要我的充电器。
This whole ranking thing, just这整个排名的事情，只是
comparing yourself to people who...比较自己的人谁…
- Have you seen my charger?-你看到我的充电器了吗？
- ...only pretend to be happy.-……只是假装快乐。
I said don't borrow this!我说不要借这个！
High fours like Naomi,高的四肢像内奥米，
I bet they're suicidal on the inside.我敢打赌他们在里面是自杀的。
My car is here. Again.我的车在这里。再一次.
Your Pelican Cove deposit,你的鹈鹕湾矿床，
is it refundable?它可以退还吗？
Like, what if this doesn't work?一样，如果这不工作？
- Can't you just stay out of my shit?-你不能呆在我的屎里吗？
- You're my sister!-你是我的妹妹！
Yes! And if you cared about that,对!如果你在乎的话，
maybe you would've noticed也许你会注意到
living with you hasn't been one和你一起生活没有一个
big rainbow sandwich for me.大彩虹三明治给我。
Do you know why I never你知道为什么我从来没有
brought any guys back here?有人回来了吗？
Because I didn't want them to know因为我不想让他们知道
I was sharing a skanky-ass cave我是一个淫荡的屁股洞共享
with Mr. Three Point Fuck.与先生三点他妈的。
Good luck with your performance!好运与你的表现！
[door closes][门关闭]
[door opens][门打开]
[grunts][人]
[phone beeps][电话声]
[door slams]【门声]
- [door rattles]- [门嘎嘎]
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- [horn honks]- [鸣笛声]
- Oh, hi, hi! I'm coming. I'm coming.哦，嗨，嗨！我来了我来了
- Jesus Christ!- Jesus Christ！
- Oh, I'm so sorry.-哦，我很抱歉。
That's great. Just great.真是太好了。太棒了。
[phone beeps][电话声]
- [sighs]- [叹息]
- [horn honks]- [鸣笛声]
Oh... Hi.哦...你好.
[ringtone chimes]【铃声响起]
Nay-Nay! [giggles]Nay Nay！[笑声]
Hey, Lace! Just checking in.嘿，蕾丝！只是检查一下。
I'm on my way to the我在去的路上
airport right now. [giggles]机场现在。[笑声]
Okay, cool, and you're all“我好，酷，你都是
good for the rehearsal dinner?晚餐的晚餐好吗？
Oh, yeah. The flight's, what, an hour?哦，是的。飞行的，什么，一个小时？
That restaurant looks so cool.那家餐厅看起来很酷。
- Uh-huh. And you got the dress okay?- 嗯哼。你把衣服穿好了吗？
- Mm-hmm. In my case. [giggles]-嗯，我的情况。[笑声]
- I love the pink.我爱粉红色。
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
So the latest draft of所以最新的草案
the speech is great.这是伟大的演讲。
Going handwritten's so cool.手写的如此酷。
Those scans of the page, my God,这些扫描的网页，我的上帝，
I welled up just at that.我油然而生，就在那。
- Oh, thank you!- 哦，谢谢你！
- Um... just one thought.-嗯…只是一个想法。
That whole bit where I help you我帮你的那一点
with the eating disorder thing...随着饮食紊乱的事情……
- You think that's a little...-你认为这是一个小…
- A little over-sharing, yeah.- <我有点过分分享了，是的。
You're so right. It's gone.你是如此的对。它消失了。
Okay. Cool. Well, I'll好的。酷。嗯，我会的
see you in a few hours!几小时后见！
♪ I'm getting married tomorrow ♪
[screams][尖叫]
[laughs][笑]
And here's your tip.这是你的小费。
[giggles] Thank you.[笑声]谢谢你。
[phone beeps][电话声]
Oh, come on.噢，得了吧！
[woman on loudspeaker] May I[女扬声器] <我可以
have your attention, please...请注意，请……
- Hi there, how are you doing?嗨，你在干什么？
- I am wonderful.我很好。
[laughs][笑]
I am so sorry, that flight is cancelled.我很抱歉，航班取消了。
- No. No, no, no.-不，不，不，不
- Customer incident at the other end.-另一端的客户事件。
But... So when is the next flight?但…那么，下一班航班是什么时候？
Yeah, they're all kind of full.是的，他们都是满的。
Uh... I booked this weeks ago.休斯敦大学...我是在几个星期前预订的。
It's my best friend's wedding.这是我最好的朋友的婚礼。
- I'm sorry.-我很抱歉。
- I have to get there. I have to.-我必须去那里。我必须。
Okay... let's see what we can do.可以...让我们看看我们能做什么。
Thank you. Thank you so much.谢谢您.非常感谢你。
I see there's one standby seat我看到有一个备用座位
on another plane leaving tonight.在另一架飞机今晚离开。
- [sighs]- [叹息]
- Uh...-嗯…
That's reserved for members这是保留给成员
of our Prime Flight Programme.我们的主要飞行计划。
You gotta be a 4.2 or over to qualify.你必须是一个4.2或以上的资格。
- Oh, I'm... I'm a 4.2.哦，我是..我是一个4.2。
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
I'm afraid you're actually a 4.183.恐怕你实际上是一个4.183。
Oh. Well, that's not my fault. Um...哦.嗯，那不是我的错。嗯...
Some woman dinged me有些女人把我
down in the... Can't you just...在下…你不能只是…
I'm sorry, it won't let me book对不起，它不会让我的书
it without the correct ranking.它没有正确的排名。
- But it's so close.-但它是如此接近。
- There's just nothing I can do.-有什么我可以做的。
- Christ, I mean, surely.基督，我的意思是，当然。
- I'm gonna have to ask you-我要问你
to moderate your language there.在那里温和你的语言。
Sorry. It's just...对不起的.这只是…
I'm maid of honour.我是光荣的少女。
I cannot miss this wedding.我不会错过这个婚礼。
And I am so sorry about that.我很抱歉。
- Can you call the supervisor?-你能打电话给主管吗？
- I cannot do that.-我不能这样做。
- Can you just call the supervisor?-你能打电话给主管吗？
- Call the fucking supervisor!-打电话给他妈的主管！
- Okay, that's profanity.好吧，那是亵渎。
- We're zero tolerance on profanity.我们在亵渎零容忍。
- I'm sorry. It's just...-我很抱歉。这只是…
- I have to serve the next customer.-我必须为下一个客户服务。
- No, no, no, no.-不，不，不，不。
- Can you step away, ma'am?你可以走了，夫人？
- God, just fucking help me!上帝，只是他妈的帮助我！
Ooh.哦。
[phones beep][电话声]
I'm so sorry.我很抱歉。
- I've called security.-我所谓的安全。
- Oh, no, no, no. Please don't do that.-哦，不，不，不，请不要那样做。
I'm, uh... five-starring you. Five stars.我是，呃…五由你主演。五颗星星。
- What's the issue here, Hannah?有什么问题吗，汉娜？
- Intimidation and profanity.胁迫和亵渎。
- Oh, no, no. I was not intimidating.-哦，不，不，我不是恐吓。
- Don't speak, ma'am.不要说话，夫人。
- I was just trying to...-我只是想…
- Ma'am.-夫人。
Okay. So, in order to restore calm,可以.所以，为了恢复平静，
I'm invoking my authority我在召唤我的权威
as airport security机场安全
to dock you one full ranking停靠你一个完整的排名
point as a punitive measure.点作为一种惩罚措施。
- This is a temporary measure.-这是一个临时措施。
- [gasps] No!- [喘气]没有！
Your score reverts你的分数恢复
to normal in 24 hours.在24小时内正常。
No, no, no. But I need it now.不，不，但我现在需要它。
During this period, all down votes在此期间，所有的选票
are subject to a times two multiplier.都受一倍两倍的乘数。
Times two?两次？
We recommend you avoid我们建议你避免
negative feedback at this time.此时负反馈。
I'm on double damage?我在双重伤害？
Please, remove yourself请，删除自己
from the airport immediately.从机场立即。
[phone beeps][电话声]
Okay, well, due to your ranking...好吧，好吧，因为你的排名……
[chattering][格格]
[baby crying][婴儿哭]
Hi there. Chuck! Great name.你好.扔出!伟大的名字。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
- Hope you're having a great night.-希望你有一个伟大的夜晚。
- It's pretty good.-这是相当不错的。
- So I need a car.-所以我需要一辆车。
- You got a vehicle in mind?-你有一辆车吗？
- Anything, really.-什么，真的。
Well, due to your current ranking,嗯，由于你目前的排名，
you're restricted to你仅限于
our super saver fleet.我们的超级节省舰队。
- Yep. That's... Yeah.-是的。那是...是啊.
- I-Cruiser 2?- i-cruiser 2？
They still have the 2?他们还有2个吗？
[alarm beeps]【报警声]
[beeping][哔]
- [woman speaking driver alert in Czech]- [女人说司机警惕捷克]
- Oh, God.哦，上帝。
[woman repeating driver alert in Czech][捷克]重复司机警觉的女人
[beep, wipers creaking][哔]，雨刷吱吱作响
- [music on TV][电视上的音乐]
- Oh, come on.哦，来吧。
Uh...休斯敦大学...
[men speaking Czech on TV][男人说捷克电视]
- [beeping]- [哔]
- Damn it!该死的！
[laughs][笑]
[sighs]【叹息】
[Czech dialogue continues]【捷克对话继续]
[engine sputters]【引擎故障]
[engine starts][发动机启动]
The little girl, who when we were小女孩，当我们
both five years old in art camp,两个五岁的艺术营，
[sobs] started talking to me[哭泣]开始和我说话
because she saw I was scared.因为她看到我害怕。
The girl who helped me make Mr. Rags...帮我做Rags先生的那个女孩…
Teardrop. Crowd goes wild. You can do this.泪滴。人群疯狂。你可以这样做。
- [ringtone plays]- [起]铃声
- [woman speaking Czech]- [捷克]女人说话
- Sorry, okay, I swear I'm on my way.-对不起，好吧，我发誓我在我的路上。
- [Naomi] How far away are you?- [内奥米] 离你有多远？
Uh... Quite a ways. I missed my flight.休斯敦大学...相当一种方式。我错过了我的航班。
- What?-什么？
- Well, not missed it but...-嗯，没有错过它，但…
So you're not gonna make所以你不想让
the rehearsal dinner?彩排晚宴？
- No.-不。
- Lacie!-  LaCie！
I am so sorry. It's been... [groans]我很抱歉。它是…[呻吟]
I got a rental car. I'm driving.我有一辆出租汽车。我在开车。
Driving? That's like nine hours.开车吗？这就像九个小时。
I'm making good time,
gonna go through the night,要去度过夜晚，
make a road trip out of it. [laughs]做一个客场之旅。[笑]
Is everything okay?一切都好吗？
I can find a replacement我可以找到一个替代品
if something's wrong.如果有什么不对的话。
No. No. No. I'll be there.不，不，我会在那里。
I swear on Mr. Rags.我对Rags发誓。
Ha ha ha!哈哈哈！
Okay, just drive safe!好的，只是驱动器的安全！
- [girls squealing]- [女孩尖叫]
- You bet. I'll just...-你打赌。我只会…
[phone beeping]【电话响】
[phone beeps][电话声]
Come on.来吧。
Please.拜托.
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- [sighs]- [叹息]
Okay.可以.
[yawns][打哈欠]
[woman speaking Czech][捷克]女人说话
- What do you want?-你想要什么？
- [woman speaking Czech]- [捷克]女人说话
[beeping][哔]
[woman speaking Czech][捷克]女人说话
- Oh, shit.哦，该死的。
- [woman's speaking tempo slows]- [女人的说话的节奏减慢]
Hi. Sorry.你好.对不起的.
[woman moaning][女人呻吟]
Your charger doesn't fit my car.你的充电器不适合我的车。
- Don't see those around much these days.-现在没看到这些天。
- It's a rental.-这是一个租金。
Ours chargers are Q2Z, yours one's a K1.我们的充电器q2z，你的K1。
They didn't give you an adapter?他们没有给你一个适配器？
No. Do you have one?不，你有一个吗？
- Not in here. Ask around.-不在这里。问问周围的。
- Thanks, anyway.-谢谢，反正。
You're super helpful.你是超级有用的。
[phone beeps][电话声]
[gasps][喘气]
Two stars?!两个星星？！
Two stars?两个星星？
Wasn't a meaningful encounter.不是一个有意义的相遇。
[Lacie] Sir, excuse me.【LaCie ]先生，对不起。
Excuse me, sorry.对不起，对不起。
Do you have a K1 adapter, by any chance?你有一个K1的适配器吗？
Ma'am, how about you, a K1 adapter,夫人，你怎么样，K1适配器，
perhaps, in the trunk of your car?也许，在你的汽车的行李箱里？
Sure.当然.
Great.伟大的.
Oh, ma'am, hi. Do you have a K1 adapter?哦，小姐，你好。你有一个K1适配器？
I have a rental car. It's...我有一辆出租汽车。它..
[grunting][喷]
- Slow down. Let's give her a ride.-慢下来。让我们给她一个骑。
- [man] She's, like, 2.8.[男人]她，像，2.8。
[phone beeps][电话声]
Come on!来吧！
I didn't even do anything!我甚至没有做任何事情！
You look like you need a ride.你看起来像你需要一个骑。
Um...嗯...
Actually, I'm okay.事实上，我很好。
Don't look it. Come on. I don't bite.不看它。来吧。我不咬人。
Luther, Mrs. Coffee, reds,卢瑟，夫人咖啡，红，
whiskey. Help yourself.威士忌。请随意.
I'm okay. Thanks.我很好。谢谢.
Where are you headed?你要去哪里？
Uh... Just as close as you can get休斯敦大学...正如你可以得到接近
to Port Mary would be great. [laughs]到玛丽港将是伟大的。[笑]
Checking my feed for danger signs?检查我的饲料的危险迹象？
I get it a lot. 1.4 gotta be我得到了很多。1.4要
an antisocial maniac, right?一个反社会的疯子，对吗？
- You seem...-你似乎…
- Normal?正常吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
It took some effort.它采取了一些努力。
What happened to you?发生什么事了？
I mean, you're a 2.8,我的意思是，你是一个2.8，
but you don't look 2.8.但你不看2.8。
That's not... This is temporary.那不是…这是暂时的。
- I'm gonna turn it around.-我要把它围绕。
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
- I'm going to a wedding. Maid of honour.-我要去参加一个婚礼。荣誉女佣。
- Nice.- Nice。
Wanna hear my speech?想听我的演讲吗？
No.不.
So how come you're a 2.8?那么你是怎么一个2.8？
Well, I got marked down嗯，我被记下来了
at the airport for yelling,在机场的叫喊，
and they put me on double damage.他们把我放在双重伤害。
- How did it feel?-感觉如何？
- Awful.-可怕的。
I meant the yelling.我的意思是叫喊。
I don't know. I was mad.我不知道。我疯了。
Look at where it got me.看看它得到了我的地方。
But as long as I get to the但只要我到了
wedding, do the speech,婚礼，做演讲，
they'll overlook the他们会忽略的
2.8. I'm with the bride.2.8。我和新娘在一起。
And if I do well, well,如果我做得很好，很好，
they're all high fours他们都是高四
so that velocitates my arc.所以，我velocitates弧。
And once they lift the point penalty,一旦他们解除了点罚，
well, my average goes way up,嗯，我的平均水平上升，
and, yeah, it's gonna be okay.而且，是的，这是好的。
God, you remind me of me.上帝，你让我想起了我。
- Hmm.-嗯。
- Not now.-不是现在。
I was, uh... 4.6 once.我是，呃…4.6一次。
- 4.6?4.6？
- Used to live for it.-用于生活。
All the work I put in...所有我投入的工作…
Eight years ago, Tom,八年前，汤姆，
my husband, got cancer.我的丈夫得了癌症。
It was pancreatic. It was a real bitch.这是胰腺。这是一个真正的婊子。
The symptoms showed up late.症状出现较晚。
I'm so sorry.我很抱歉。
You don't know me so你不了解我
you're not really sorry.你真的很抱歉。
You're just mainly awkward cos I你只是主要是尴尬的我
have sprung some cancer talk at you.有一些癌症在你说话。
Anyway, I five-starred every doctor,无论如何，我五个主演的每一个医生，
every nurse, every high-four每一个护士，每一个高四
consultant that we had.我们曾经的顾问。
Ding. Ding. Ding. Thank you so much.丁。丁。丁。非常感谢你。
The cancer didn't give a shit.癌症并没有给你一个屎。
It just kept growing.它只是不断增长。
A couple of months in, we heard几个月的时间，我们听到
about this experimental treatment.关于这个实验治疗。
It was very expensive.这是非常昂贵的。
It was very exclusive.这是非常独特的。
I did everything I could我做了我能做的一切
to get him a spot there.给他一个地点。
Tom was a 4.3.汤姆是一个4.3。
They gave his bed to a 4.4.他们把他的床给了一个4.4。
So when he died I thought, fuck it.所以，当他死了，我想，他妈的。
I started saying what I wanted,我开始说我想要的，
when I wanted.当我想要的时候。
Just drop it out there.就把它扔在那里。
People don't always like that.人们不总是这样的。
It is incredible how fast它是令人难以置信的速度有多快
you slip off the ladder你从梯子上滑下来
when you start doing that.当你开始这样做的时候。
It turned out a lot of my它证明了我的很多
friends didn't care for honesty.朋友不在乎诚实。
Treated me like I had taken a对待我就像我已经采取了
shit at their breakfast table.在他们的早餐桌上的屎。
But, Jesus Christ, it felt good.但是，Jesus Christ，感觉很好。
Shedding those fuckers.脱落的那些混蛋。
It was like taking off tight shoes.这就像脱下紧身的鞋子。
- Maybe you should try it?-也许你应该试试？
- Oh, come on. [laughs]哦，来吧。[笑]
Why not?为什么不呢？
I can't just kick off my shoes我不能只是把我的鞋脱下来
and walk the earth or whatever.走在地球上或是什么。
- You won't know unless you try.-你不会知道，除非你尝试。
- Oh, that's just...-哦，那只是…
Look, you had something with your life,看，你的生活有了什么东西，
real things, good things,真实的东西，美好的东西，
and you lost it all, and I'm sorry.你失去了一切，我很抱歉。
So now you've got nothing left to lose.所以现在你已经没有什么可以失去了。
But I don't even have the但我甚至没有
something worth losing, not yet.一些值得失去的东西，还没有。
You know, I mean,你知道，我的意思是，
I'm still fighting for that.我仍在为那一。
- And what is "that"?-什么是“那”？
- I don't know. Enough to be content?-我不知道。足够的内容？
Like, to look around and think,喜欢，环顾四周，思考，
well, I guess I'm okay.好吧，我想我很好。
Just to be able to breathe out,只是为了能够呼吸，
not feeling like... like...不感觉像…像…
Like just... And that is就像…这是
way off, like, way, way off.关闭的方式，像，方式，关闭。
And until I get there, I have直到我到达那里，我才有
to play the numbers game.玩数字游戏。
We all do, that's what we're in.我们都这样做，这就是我们的。
That's how the fucking world works.这就是他妈的世界的作品。
Look, maybe you don't remember,看，也许你不记得了，
you know, you're just too old to get it.你知道，你太老了，得到它。
I do not mean that how it sounds.我并不意味着它的声音。
Don't worry. I'm not voting you down.你别担心。我没有投票你。
- Sweetheart.- Sweetheart。
- [gasps] What time is it?- [喘气]是什么时候？
I'm heading east from here so I think我从这里向东，所以我想
you need to get yourself another ride.你需要给自己另一个旅程。
- Where are we?-我们在哪里？
- About 30 miles from Port Mary.-从玛丽港约30英里。
A lot of buses stop here许多公共汽车站在这里
so you should be fine.所以你应该很好。
- Well, thank you.-好，谢谢你。
- Good luck with your speech.-祝你的演讲好运。
[laughs][笑]
I put a little something in there for you.我在里面放了一点东西给你。
- You did?-你做了吗？
- Emergency escape hatch!-紧急逃生舱！
Bye.再见.
[Lacie] In this world,【LaCie ]在这个世界上，
we're all so caught up...我们都被抓住了…
- [door opens][门打开]
- ...in our own dramas.在我们自己的戏剧里。
- [girl] So, Dad was like...- [女孩]，爸爸是喜欢…
- It's easy to forget what matters.-很容易忘记什么事情。
[girl] He'd never even heard of the show.[女孩]他甚至从来没有听说过这个节目。
I'm like, "You never heard of我喜欢，“你从来没有听说过
Sea of Tranquillity?"海的宁静吗？”
Like, the number-one sci-fi fantasy,喜欢，头号科幻幻想，
and he's all like,他都喜欢，
"What the fuck?" Whatever!“他妈的什么？”无论什么!
I think I'm allergic to this purple.我想我对这种紫色过敏。
So I'm like, "Well, I'm going所以我喜欢，“嗯，我要去
to Tranquillity Con in Port Mary.寂静和玛丽港。
That's why I'm dressed这就是我穿衣服的原因
like Lieutenant Duster."像Lieutenant Duster。”
He's all like, "Uh...他都喜欢，“嗯…
Port Mary is frickin' miles away."玛丽港是该死的哩。”
Yadda, yadda, yadda.等等，等等，等等。
- [toilet flushes]- [厕所冲]
- He one-stars me. Like, thanks, Dad.-他是我的星星。喜欢，谢谢，爸爸。
- [girl 1] See you back on there.- [女孩1 ]看到你回来了。
- [girl 2] Okay.- [女孩2 ]好吗。
Are you guys headed to Tranquillity Con?你们去宁静的骗局？
- You're into Sea of Tranquillity?你到海的宁静吗？
- Totally.-完全。
I was all set to go.我都准备去。
My friend, who is there already,我的朋友，谁已经在那里，
has my costume, but my car broke down.有我的服装，但我的车坏了。
Well, there's some space in the RV.嗯，在RV有空间。
- Hi.-嗨。
- Hey!-嘿！
- You're a Trank head, huh?你是一个跑道头，嗯？
- Sorry?对不起？
Trank head. Sea of Tranquillity fan?跑道头。大海平静的粉丝吗？
Oh, yeah. We say Tranksters where I'm from.哦，是的。我们说tranksters我来自哪里。
- Who's your favourite character?-你最喜欢的角色是谁？
- Gotta be Lieutenant Duster.-一定是Duster中尉。
- She's awesome.-她真棒。
- She?-她？
He! I misspoke.他！我说错了。
Lieutenant Duster has no fixed gender.Duster中尉没有固定的性别。
I know, and that's why it's我知道，这就是为什么它的
so hard to remember, right?很难记住，对吗？
- [ringtone playing]- [音乐铃声]
- Excuse me. Gotta get this.-对不起。必须得到这个。
My friend, at the convention. [giggles]我的朋友，在大会上。[笑声]
Hi, Nay! [laughs]嗨，Nay！[笑]
So, oh, my God, insane night,所以，哦，我的上帝，疯狂的夜晚，
but I am so close now.但我现在如此接近。
[Naomi] Don't come.[内奥米] 不来了。
What? No. No. I'm, like, an hour away.什么？不，我是，像，一个小时的路程。
Don't come. I don't want you here.不要来。我不想你在这里。
I don't know what is up with you,我不知道你是怎么了，
but I cannot have a 2.6 at my wedding.但我不能有一个2.6在我的婚礼。
Oh, no, that's temporary!哦，不，那是暂时的！
That's temporary.这是暂时的。
Well, the wedding's today so...“我很好，今天的婚礼是这样的……”
- But it doesn't change anything.-但它不会改变任何东西。
- Lacie...-  LaCie…
- I can still do the same speech.-我仍然可以做同样的演讲。
- And there's Mr. Rags!-还有Rags先生！
- No!-没有！
But... But you invited me.但却…但你邀请了我，
You've seen the guest list.你看过客人名单。
They are all, like, 4.5 or above.他们都是，喜欢，4.5或以上。
They are going to freak at a 2.6,他们会在2.6个怪物，
and I am not taking that kind of damage,我不接受那种伤害，
plus I haven't dipped under加上我还没有下降
a 4.7 in, like, six months.一个4.7，像，六个月。
You said you wanted your oldest friend.你说你想要你最老的朋友。
When I asked you to speak,当我让你说话的时候，
you were a 4.2, okay?你是个4.2岁的人，好吗？
And the authenticity of a vintage bond和一个老式债券的真实性
low four at a gathering of this calibre低四，这个口径的聚会
played fantastically on all打得所有
the stimulations we ran.等我们跑。
Forecast was a prestige预测是一种威望
bounce of 2 minimum.最小反弹2。
But now you're a sub three. Sorry.但现在你是一个分三。对不起的.
That just puts the stink on只是把臭味
things a little too much.东西有点太多了。
That just plays badly for us.这对我们来说是很糟糕的。
So it was just about numbers for you?那么这是你的号码吗？
Oh, cut the shit! It was哦，切屎！这是
numbers for both of us.我们两个的数字。
You wanted those“我”你想要的
primo votes, don't deny it.第一票，不要否认。
It's not like you could get them on这是不喜欢你可以让他们
your own. Let's not kid ourselves.你自己。让我们不要骗自己了。
Oh, I'm... I'm getting those votes.哦，我是..我要得到那些选票。
What? You're just gonna roll up什么？你只是要卷起
here and make people like you?在这里，让人们喜欢你吗？
- That's right. I'm doing my speech.-这是正确的。我在做我的演讲。
- No, you're not.-不，你不是。
Yes, I am. And they are gonna vote me是的，我是。他们会投票给我
through the roof when they hear it.穿过屋顶时，他们听到。
- Weep their fucking eyes out!-他们的眼睛哭了出来！
- Go home!-回家！
- [phone beeping]- [手机响]
- Hello?-你好吗？
[sighs] Fuck![叹息]他妈的！
I have never seen我从来没有见过
your stupid fucking show.你愚蠢的表演。
[tyres screech]【轮胎的尖叫]
[shouts] Hope they cancel it![呼喊]希望他们取消它！
- [horn honks]- [鸣笛声]
- I need a ride!-我需要一个旅程！
[shouts][呐喊]
- [phone beeping]- [手机响]
- Fuck!-他妈的！
Jesus!Jesus！
[engine roars]【引擎咆哮]
Hey! Hey!嘿!嘿!
Hey!嘿!
- Can I borrow your bike?-我能借你的自行车吗？
- What?-什么？
Can I borrow your bike?我能借一下你的自行车吗？
Do you, Naomi Jayne Blestow,你，Naomi Jayne Blestow，
take this man to be your husband,把这个男人做你的丈夫，
to live together with him和他一起生活
in the covenant of marriage?在婚姻的契约中？
To love him, comfort him,爱他，安慰他，
honour and keep him,荣誉和留住他，
in sickness and in health...在疾病和健康…
and forsaking all others,放弃所有其他人，
be faithful unto him...对他忠实…
[cheering and applause][欢呼和掌声]
[indistinct radio chatter][模糊的无线电聊天]
[revs engine]【转速发动机]
[screams][尖叫]
[applause][掌声]
To my best mate, Anthony.给我最好的伴侣，安东尼。
Let's hear it for him.让我们为他听吧。
[cheering][欢呼]
You've been there from day one.你从一开始就在那里。
I love you, man. I appreciate you.我爱你，男人。我很感激！
Hilarious speech, by the way.热闹的演讲，通过的方式。
By your standards.按你的标准。
[laughter][笑]
- Pow! Pow! Pow!- Pow！战俘！战俘！
- Oh! Oh! Oh! [laughs]-哦！哦!哦![笑]
[Paul] He's still got a few[保罗]他还有几
bullets left. Oh, man.子弹离开。哦，男人。
Oh, gosh, well, um...哦，天啊，嗯，嗯…
[gasps] Shit![喘气]大便！
[Paul] We have so many people to[保罗]我们有这么多的人
thank. Our beautiful bridesmaids.谢谢。我们美丽的伴娘。
- [cheering]- [欢呼]
- But, of course,但是，当然，
my most heartfelt thanks,我最衷心的感谢，
my warmest thanks,我最温暖的感谢，
are to someone who's my best friend,是给我最好的朋友的人，
my lover and now,我的爱人和现在，
I'm honoured to say, my wife.我很荣幸地说，我的妻子。
- Naomi!-内奥米！
- [cheering and whooping]- [欢呼和呐喊]
- [cheering]- [欢呼]
- [Paul] One, two, three! Naomi!- [保罗]一，二，三！内奥米！
- [man] The A Team![人]一队！
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
I love you so much, darl.我是如此的爱你，亲爱的。
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!喔喔喔喔！
[man] Congratulations, sir.[男人]恭喜你，先生。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
- No, thank you.-不，谢谢。
- [whooping]- [呐喊]
- Get over here!-在这里结束！
Get your ass over here.在这里得到你的屁股。
- Get in here, big boy.-在这里，大男孩。
- [phones beep][电话声]
- You're beautiful!-你是美丽的！
- [cheering]- [欢呼]
Yeah! Gimme five! Good choice!是啊!给我五！不错的选择！
You fucking earned it, man.你他妈的赢得了，男人。
You fucking earned it.你他妈的赢得了。
[giggles nervously][笑声]地
Everybody, hello!大家，你好！
- Oh, my God.-哦，我的上帝。
- I love you.-我爱你。
Can everyone be quiet for a moment?大家能安静一会儿吗？
Thank you. [giggles]谢谢您.[笑声]
- Get rid of her.-摆脱她。
- That would play awful.-这将发挥可怕的。
She's a fucking 1.1.她是个他妈的1.1。
Now for those of you who don't现在为那些不在你的人
know me, which is... all of you...知道我，这是…你们所有人…
my name is Lacie Pound我的名字是LaCie磅
and, believe it or not,而且，信不信，
I am one of Naomi's oldest friends.我是内奥米最老的朋友之一。
Hi, Nay-Nay!嗨，Nay Nay！
It's great to meet you too, Paul.很高兴见到你，保罗。
I've heard a lot about you.我久仰你的大名。
He's a pretty big deal, that Paul.他是一个相当大的交易，保罗。
- Pretty big deal.-相当大的交易。
- [camera shutter clicks][相机快门点击]
He makes his own tapenade! Yeah.他让自己的酱！是啊.
[laughs] Uh...[笑]嗯…
Anyway, um... I...无论如何，嗯…I. ..
have looked up to Naomi已经看了内奥米
pretty much my entire life.几乎我的整个生活。
We met when we were five years old,我们五岁的时候就认识了，
and right up through to our teenage并通过对我们的青少年
years, we made quite the pair.几年，我们取得了相当的对。
We'd talk about all the我们会谈论所有的
things girls talk about,谈论女孩谈论的事情，
you know, boys, hair, products,你知道，男孩，头发，产品，
uh... more boys. [laughs]休斯敦大学...更多的男孩。[笑]
I mean, I tried sometimes我的意思是，我有时尝试
to expand our range a little为了扩大我们的范围有点
and talk about climate change,谈论气候变化，
but she found that kind of boring so...但她发现那种无聊的…
Go on.去。
She was probably right.她可能是对的。
I mean, fuck the planet, right?我的意思是，他妈的地球，对吗？
Whoo!喔！
Yes, thank you! Come on.好的，谢谢。来吧。
Let's have a little fun here.让我们在这里有一点乐趣。
You know, fuck the planet! [laughs]你知道，他妈的地球！[笑]
- [shouts] Fuck the planet!- [喊]他妈的地球！
- [feedback][反馈]
[crockery rattles]【陶器摇铃]
- [phone beeps]- [电话声]
- Anyway...反正…
I... looked up to NaomiI. ..仰望内奥米
pretty much my entire life,几乎我的整个生活，
which meant she was looking down on me.这意味着她在看我。
Always with a smile though. [laughs]虽然总是面带微笑。[笑]
In high school,在高中，
she was my shoulder to cry on.她是我的肩膀哭泣。
She seemed to enjoy that.她似乎很喜欢这个。
Guys and me never worked out.家伙和我从来没有工作。
They'd see Naomi and just... Whoo!他们会看到内奥米和公正…喔！
You know, that was it.你知道，就是这样。
She had this tight ass,她有这紧的屁股，
like two fists.像两个拳头。
Uh-huh.嗯。
[giggles] I was all like...[笑声]我都喜欢…
[giggles][笑声]
I was like...我就像…
through the hallways in high school.穿过走廊在高中。
[cackling][唱]
[phones beep][电话声]
[cries][哭泣]
And she was there for me.她在那里为我。
Holding my hair back...拿着我的头发…
as I knelt, vomiting,当我跪下，呕吐，
in front of the crapper.在厕所前面。
Thank you for that, Naomi.谢谢你，内奥米。
I always wished I was you.我总是希望我是你。
And...和…
I guess that's why you我想这就是为什么你
kept me around so long?让我这么长时间？
Until you got your new job直到你找到了你的新工作
and your fancy new friends.和你的新朋友。
And that...那…
[laughs][笑]
...fucking... jackhole!…他妈的…jackhole！
And you didn't need me.你不需要我。
You probably got another me.你可能有另一个我。
Guess there's some other "yeth Beth"想有一些其他的“是Beth”
you moved on to like a succubus.你开始像一个女妖。
- [phones beeping]- [手机响]
- I'm getting to Mr. Rags, okay? Jesus!-我要去Rags先生，好吗？Jesus！
- [crowd gasps]- [人群喘息声]
- Stay back.-呆。
Stay the fuck back! I'll kill him!呆在他妈的回来！我会杀了他！
I'll cut his head off我会砍下他的头
and stick it up my ass!然后把它贴在我的屁股上！
[gasps][喘气]
[gasps] Time's nearly up![喘气]时间快到了！
- Hey! Calm down.-嘿！冷静.
- I...- I.。
I just wanted to say, in this我只是想说，在这个
world so caught up in our own shit,世界如此陷入我们自己的屎，
- let's not forget what matters.-让我们不要忘记什么重要。
- It's okay. It's okay.-这是好的。这是好的。
Happiness, fucking Paul幸福，他妈的保罗
and Naomi, and she's...和内奥米，她的..
She... She fucked Greg!她…她和格雷戈！
I know she did.我知道她做了。
- I know you did.-我知道你做过。
- No...-不..
Don't even try to deny...甚至不要试图否认…
- [screams]- [尖叫声]
- [feedback screeches]- [反馈的尖叫]
The little girl who, when we小女孩，当我们
were just five-years-old in art camp,在艺术营地只有五岁，
started talking to me开始和我说话
because she saw I was scared因为她看到我害怕
and helped me make Mr. Rags.并帮助我使Rags先生。
He reminds me of you and他让我想起了你和
what you meant to me then!你对我来说意味着什么！
[cries] And I'm so honoured[哭泣]，我是如此的荣幸
to be here to see this shit!到这里来看看这个屎！
[screams] I love you, Nay-Nay![尖叫声]我爱你，Nay Nay！
I've always loved you!我一直都爱着你！
I love you!我爱你！
[camera shutter clicking][相机快门点击]
[whirring][呼呼]
[breathes deeply][深呼吸]
[sobs][哭泣]
[laughs][笑]
What the fuck are you looking at?你他妈的在看什么？
Just what I was wondering.正是我想知道的。
Well...好...
Don't!不要!
Don't? Don't wonder?不？不知道？
Uh-huh.嗯。
It would be a dull这将是一个乏味的
world without wonder.没有奇迹的世界。
I don't give a shit about your world.我不在乎你的世界。
I don't like your brassiere.我不喜欢你的胸罩。
I don't like your moustache.我不喜欢你的胡子。
I don't like your aura.我不喜欢你的光环。
- My aura?-我的光环？
- Yeah.-是的。
I don't like your... head.我不喜欢你的…头。
Your entire head is你的整个脑袋是
just ridiculous to me.只是可笑的我。
Really?真的？
You look like an alcoholic你看起来像个酒鬼
former weatherman.以前的天气预报员。
You sound like a lost little lamb你的声音像一只迷路的小羊羔
that just got told there's no Santa Claus.刚刚被告知没有圣诞老人。
What sort of cartoon character什么样的卡通人物
did your mum have to fuck你妈妈有没有他妈的
to brew you up in the womb?把你在子宫里？
At least I look like I was born,至少我看起来像我出生，
not shit out by some tormented cow没有狗屎了一些痛苦的牛
creature in an underground lab.在地下实验室里的生物
You got tossed out of that lab.你被赶出了实验室。
- Oh, yeah?-哦，是吗？
- Oh, yeah, flushed out.-哦，是的，冲了出来。
- Ooh!-哦！
- In the trash!在垃圾桶里！
- Your face is a fucking...-你的脸是他妈的…
- Fucking.-他妈的。
Fucking biological car crash该死的生物汽车碰撞
that made Picasso screw这使Picasso螺杆
his eyes up and say,他的眼睛起来，说，
"Well, that just don't make sense."“好吧，那就别有意义了。”
[laughs][笑]
- You're a fucking asshole.-你他妈的混蛋。
- Fuck you!-他妈的你！
- Fuck you next Wednesday.下个星期三去他妈的。
- Fuck you for Christmas!-他妈的你的圣诞节！
- Fuck you!-他妈的你！
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --