Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com
__
Belinda Carlisle there with one贝琳达卡莱儿有一
of the biggest hits of 1987 so far.1987到目前为止的最大的点击率。
Gotta love that track!<我要爱那轨迹！
Coming up next in just a moment...在短短的一个时间……
Could you please stop it?你能阻止它吗？
I just wanna have some fun, okay?我只是想有一些乐趣，好吗？
Kelly, come on.凯莉，来吧。
- Kelly.-凯莉。
- I'm still walking, Wes.-我还在走，韦斯。
We've only got a couple of hours我们只有几个小时的时间
so let's, uh... let's use it.所以让我们，呃…让我们使用它。
I am using it.我正在使用它。
Hey.嘿.
You're good at this.你很擅长这个。
It's, uh... got different endings.它是，嗯…有不同的结局。
Depending on if you're in one取决于如果你在一个
or two player.或两个球员。
Uh-huh?嗯？
- It was kinda the first game to do that.-这是有点第一场比赛做。
- Damn it!该死的！
Do you wanna play Top Speed?你想玩最高速度>吗？
Oh, no.哦，不，
Thank you.谢谢您.
I just wanna get my bearings a bit.我只是想让我的轴承有点。
Uh... okay.休斯敦大学...可以.
- See you around?-看到你在身边吗？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
Go along with whatever I say.跟我说的话。
- Sorry?对不起？
- Whatever I say, go along with it.无论我说什么，都要跟着它。
Okay, Wes, you're just pestering now.好吧，韦斯，你只是缠着我们。
- Do I have to red light you?-我要红灯吗？
- Two hours 35.-两小时35。
- There's not much time left.-没有太多的时间。
- Wes.-韦斯。
Look...看…
- Last week, we had the most amazing...-上周，我们有了最惊人的…
- Last week was last week.上周是上周。
I need to talk with my friend here, okay?我需要在这里和我的朋友谈谈，好吗？
Haven't seen her in a while.有一段时间没见过她了。
Wes, she's sick.韦斯，她生病了。
Like "six months to live" sick.像“六个月活”生病。
Five, actually.五，实际上。
I need to catch up with her.我需要赶上她。
Private time.私人时间。
Okay.可以.
- Hey, I'm sorry.-嘿，我很抱歉。
- That's okay.-这是好的。
See you around?看到你在身边了吗？
Sure.当然.
Sorry for killing you.对不起，杀了你。
The whole "six months to live" thing?整个“六个月”的事情？
Sorry. Five.对不起的.五。
Five was a nice touch.五是一个很好的联系。
- Kelly.-凯莉。
- Yorkie.-约克。
- Yurgie?- Yurgie？
Like the dog breed?像狗一样？
Yeah.是啊.
He's not a bad guy. I feel kinda bad.他不是一个坏家伙。我感觉有点坏。
- Met him at the Quagmire so...遇见他在泥潭…
- What's the Quagmire?- Quagmire是什么？
If you don't already know如果你还不知道
what the Quagmire is,泥潭是什么，
you probably don't wanna know.你可能不想知道。
No?没有？
You want another one?你要另一个吗？
- Oh, no, I...-哦，不，I.。
- Yeah, you do. Come on.-是的，你做的。来吧。
Do I have to tug your leash?我要拉你的皮带吗？
- Hey, Blondie.-嗨，Blondie。
- I'm Blondie?我是Blondie？
You are. Jack and Coke times two.你是.杰克和可乐的两倍。
- Oh, no. Mine was just a Coke.-哦，不，我只是一个可口可乐。
- Times two.-次。
- What are you doing?-你在干什么？
- I'm... regarding you.-我..关于你。
I feel like I'm being analysed.我觉得我正在分析。
- Why the glasses?-为什么眼镜？
- Um...-嗯…
I like them. They totally work on you.我喜欢他们。他们完全在你的工作。
But do you need them?但是你需要他们吗？
- Yeah, the lenses don't do anything.-是的，镜头不做任何事情。
- Knew it!-知道它！
I used to wear them in school.我过去在学校里穿的。
So I guess now所以我猜现在
they're just kind of a... comfort thing.他们只是种的一种。安慰的事。
I figured they were我认为他们是
kind of a fashion statement.一种时尚的声明。
- Really?真的吗？
- But then the rest of your outfit is not.-但你的衣服的其余部分不是。
Don't take that wrong.不要采取这种错误。
It's refreshing. I mean, look around.这是令人耳目一新。我的意思是，看看周围。
People try so hard to look人们努力去看
how they think they should look.他们认为他们应该如何看。
They probably saw it in some movie.他们可能在一些电影中看到它。
But I like these.但我喜欢这些。
You're authentically you.你是真实的你。
Thanks.谢谢.
Cheers.干杯.
You never tasted it before?你以前从来没有尝过吗？
No, I...不，I. ..
I just haven't had it in a while.我只是没有它在一段时间。
It's good.很好。
Do you live here?你住在这里吗？
- No. Oh, uh...-不哦，嗯…
- Tourist?旅游吗？
We'll go with tourist.我们将和游客一起去。
So you're new here?那么你是新来的？
- First night.第一夜。
- First night? Wow, okay!-第一个晚上？哇，好吗！
Oh, my God!啊，天哪！
We have to dance to this.我们有跳舞。
- With each other?-相互？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
- Oh, no. Dance floors aren't my thing.哦，不，跳舞地板不是我的东西。
- Oh, let's not limit ourselves.-哦，让我们不要限制自己。
- No, I can't.-不，我不能。
- Yes, you can, come on.-是的，你可以，来吧。
- No, I'll look dumb...-不，我会看起来很傻…
- Just follow my lead!-只要跟随我的领导！
Copy me.模仿我。
You got it.你说对啦。
Hey!嘿!
- Why did you run away?-你为什么逃跑？
- Oh, sorry.哦，对不起。
I... I said I'm not much of a dancer.I. ..我说我不是一个舞者。
No shit.没有大便。
Like a frightened horse像受惊的马
on a frozen lake back there.在一个冰冻的湖上。
I'm kidding. Half kidding.我开玩笑的，半开玩笑。
Sorry I pushed you into it.对不起，我把你推到它。
Saturday nights once a week.每周一次的星期六晚上。
It's like no time. I get impatient.这就像没有时间。我不耐烦了。
No, no, it's not that. It's...不，不，不是这样的。它..
- Everyone was looking.-每个人都在寻找。
- Looking?好看吗？
Yeah. You know, two girls dancing.是啊.你知道吗，两个女孩在跳舞。
Okay, one, folks are way less uptight好吧，一个人不紧张
than they used to be.比他们过去是。
And two, this is a party town.和两个，这是一个党镇。
No one's judging.没有人的判断。
Face it. If they were staring,面对它。如果他们盯着看，
it's because I am bodacious.那是因为我胆大包天。
- You're stupid.-你是愚蠢的。
- Thank you!-谢谢！
- I've never been on a dance floor.-我从来没有在一个舞蹈地板。
- Never?没有吗？
As in the whole time正如在整个时间
you've been alive never?你还活着吗？
Never.从未.
What are you, like, Amish?你是什么样的，阿米什？
That's one sheltered existence这是一个庇护的存在
you got there.你到达那里。
Yeah, well.是的，很好。
As far as my family's concerned,就我的家人而言，
I can't do anything.我什么都做不了。
Well, no one knows嗯，没有人知道
about even half the shit I get up to.甚至有一半的大便，我起床。
With your folks, though,然而，与你的家人，
it's from a place of love, though, right?它是从一个爱的地方，虽然，对吗？
- They worry.-他们担心。
- They don't worry.-他们不担心。
Just the concept of me enjoying myself只是我的概念享受我自己
would blow their minds.会吹他们的头脑。
What would you like to do?你想要做什么？
That you've never done?你从来没有做过？
Oh...哦...
So many things.这么多东西。
San Junipero is a party town.三Junipero是一方镇。
All up for grabs.所有的争夺。
Midnight's two hours away.午夜的两个小时。
Oh, that's not long.哦，那不长。
Why waste time sitting here?为什么要浪费时间坐在这里？
I, um...我，嗯…
- Listen...-听…
- It's okay.-这是好的。
- No, I mean...-不，我的意思是…
- Really, it's okay.-真的，这是好的。
No, I'm, uh...不，我是，呃…
I'm engaged. I have a fiancé.
- He's called Greg.-他被称为格雷戈。
- And is Greg here?-格雷戈在这里吗？
- No, he's...-不，他的..
- Elsewhere?其它地方吗？
Yeah.是啊.
Oh.哦.
Wanna go to bed with me?想和我上床吗？
We could be back at mine in like...我们可以在我的像…
I never did anything like that.我从来没有做过这样的事。
All the more reason.所有更多的理由。
Oh, you're nice.哦，你很好。
- I can't.-我不能。
- Okay.-好的。
- I just... I can't.-我只是…我做不到。
- I get it.-我得到它。
- I have to go.-我必须走了。
- In this?-在这个？
It's been really great to meet you.真的很高兴见到你。
Likewise.同样。
Okay.可以.
Shit.倒霉.
__
- What the hell, Wes?-什么地狱，韦斯？
- Look, I know I'm coming across...-看，我知道我要来…
- I'm red lighting you, for real. Okay?我是红色的灯光，真实的。好吗？
- No, don't do that. Just...-不，不要那样做。只是…
- Then stop this.-然后停止这个。
- Can you hear me out? Please? Please.-你能听到我的声音吗？请？拜托.
How many girls do you think there are你认为有多少女孩
in San Junipero?在三Junipero？
Hundreds? Thousands?数百？千？
I don't care.我不在乎.
I'm saying there's plenty我说有很多
of other girls out there for you, Wes.其他女孩在那里为你，韦斯。
The locals? They're like dead people.当地人呢？他们像死人。
A little lively for dead people.对死的人有点热闹。
Look, I don't want some kind看，我不想要什么样的
of boring romance, okay?无聊的浪漫，好吗？
Like, Jesus,像，Jesus，
put us in a retirement home deal.把我们放在一个退休家庭协议。
Well, if you're looking for someone好吧，如果你在找人
to fuck, there's options.去他妈的，有选项。
- Hang out at the Quagmire again.挂在泥潭了。
- It's not just sex.-不只是性。
- It was just sex.-只是性。
- No, we made a connection.-不，我们做了一个连接。
Wes, it was just sex.韦斯，这只是性。
- No...-不..
- No roots.-没有根。
We had fun.我们玩得很开心。
I'm sorry.我很抱歉.
Enjoy the town, for God's sake.享受城市，为上帝的缘故。
- Hey.-嘿。
Waiting for someone?等待某人？
Not really.不是真的。
I'll get you a drink?我给你拿杯饮料好吗？
Uh, yeah, sure.嗯，是的，当然。
So, uh... yeah,所以，呃…是啊,
it was microsurgery, I guess.这是显微外科手术，我猜。
You know, both my kneecaps你知道，我的膝盖骨
had kind of just worn down.刚刚磨损了。
You know, I never got this song.你知道，我从来没有得到这首歌。
Kind of weird.奇怪的种类。
- Shall we dance?-我们跳舞吗？
- Sure.-当然。
I mean, I guess by the time我的意思是，我猜的时间
I'd put my mind to, like, computing.我会把我的头脑，像，计算。
You know, caught that first wave,你知道，抓住那第一个波浪，
would have had a different story.会有一个不同的故事。
Gotta use the bathroom.必须使用浴室。
Okay.可以.
- I don't know how to do this.-我不知道该怎么做。
- Do what?-做什么？
Just help me.只是帮助我。
Can you just...你能吗…
Just make this easy for me?这对我来说很容易吗？
You wanna get in my car?你想上我的车吗？
- How long have you been here?-你在这里多久了？
- Sorry?对不起？
- In San Junipero?在三Junipero？
Uh... Couple of months.休斯敦大学...几个月。
Plan is long enough to enjoy myself.计划是足够长的时间来享受自己。
Guess I'm a tourist, like you.我想我是一个旅游者，像你一样。
Yeah.是啊.
Hey. You okay?嘿.你还好吗？
Stop!停止！
Sorry, but...对不起，但…
Man, your face!男人，你的脸！
Wow.真的.
- You like it?-你喜欢吗？
- It's just so big.-这是如此大。
Reminds me of where I grew up.让我想起我长大的地方。
__
Miss your mom?想念你的妈妈？
You have to show me.你必须给我看。
- Okay.-好的。
You never slept with a woman before?你以前从来没有和一个女人睡过吗？
That's not a critique.这不是一个批判。
I mean, it was fucking awesome.我的意思是，这是他妈的真棒。
No, never with a woman.不，从来没有一个女人。
Never with anyone.从来没有与任何人。
Not anyone?没有任何人吗？
- What, in town or...?-什么，在镇上还是…？
- No. No one, nowhere.-没有人，无处。
- I guess you deflowered me.我猜你强奸了我。
- I deflowered you?我强奸了你？
What is this? Merry England?这是什么？快乐的英国？
Shut up.闭嘴.
You've had relationships though.你有过关系，虽然。
Mnh-mnh.再妄想。
Hello! You got a fiancé.
- It's complicated.-这是复杂的。
- Yeah, I'll say.-是的，我会说。
When did you know...你什么时候知道的…
- that you liked women?-你喜欢女人吗？
- I like men too.-我也喜欢男人。
Equal rights.平等的权利。
Okay.可以.
But when did you know?但你什么时候知道的？
Do you always know?你总是知道吗？
I was married to a guy.我和一个男人结婚了。
A long time, I was married.很长一段时间，我结婚了。
I always knew.我总是知道。
I mean, I'd be attracted to other girls,我的意思是，我会被其他女孩吸引，
co-workers, friends,同事，朋友，
some waitress that served me.一些服务我的女服务员。
They were crushes.他们被压碎。
God, they were crushes.上帝，他们将。
Never acted on any of it.从来没有采取任何行动。
Never did anything.从来没有做过。
I was in love with him.我爱上了他。
I really was in love with him.我真的爱上了他。
But he chose not to stick around.但他选择不坚持。
So now it's me.所以现在是我。
And I'm passing through.而我通过。
And before I leave,在我离开之前，
I'll have a good time.我会有一个美好的时光。
I'm just gonna have a good time.我会有一个美好的时光。
Time's nearly up.时间快到了。
Then let's lie here.然后让我们躺在这里。
__
Excuse me?原谅我吗？
Have you seen Kelly?你看见凯莉了吗？
- What's that?-那是什么？
- Kelly.-凯莉。
I haven't seen her all night.我一晚上都没见过她。
You tried the Quagmire?你试过泥潭？
What is the Quagmire?的困境是什么？
- Whoa! Hey!哇哦！嘿!
- I'm sorry!-我很抱歉！
Yeah, I know you from somewhere.是的，我知道你来自某处。
Tucker's.希尔斯的。
- Kelly's friend, huh?-凯莉的朋友，嗯？
- Do you know where to find her?-你知道在哪里找到她吗？
- How would I know that?-我怎么会知道？
- You're her friend.-你是她的朋友。
- Was a friend.是< /我是一个朋友。
- Has she been here?她来过这里了吗？
No.不.
You too, huh?你也是，嗯？
Well...好...
Hey. Try a different time.嘿.尝试不同的时间。
Here in '80, the '90s, 2002 one time.在这里，“80，90年代，2002个一次。
She's worth the shot, right?她是值得的，对吗？
__
Introducing the totally redesigned引入完全重新设计
Chrysler Cordoba.克莱斯勒科尔多瓦，
All the luxury you expect is here.所有你期待的奢侈品都在这里。
But so is gas mileage...“我”，但汽油的里程……
No, no, no.不，不，不。
- Hey.-嘿。
Golden age, right?黄金时代，对吗？
- Right.-对。
- You playing or...-你在玩或…
I'm sorry, I'm looking for someone.对不起，我在找人。
Maybe... next time.也许吧...下一次.
__
♪ Don't you think? ♪
♪ It's like rain... ♪
Kelly?凯莉？
__
Yeah!是啊!
You're beautiful!你是美丽的！
- Select a song!选择一首歌！
- Hi.-嗨。
Ladies' room.女士们的房间。
Hey.嘿.
Hey. No, you...嘿.不，你…
Wait a minute.等一下.
Why are you here?你为什么在这里？
I was looking for you.我在找你。
Where did you go?你去哪里了？
I like a change of music.我喜欢音乐的变化。
How the hell is this your era?这到底是怎么一个你的时代？
- You hid from me.-你向我隐瞒。
- One, I did not.-一，我没有。
Two, I owe you zero.两个，我欠你一个。
And three... see point two.和三…见第二点。
It's not about who owes who.这不是谁欠谁。
It's about manners.这是关于礼貌。
You don't know who I am.你不知道我是谁。
You don't know what this means.你不知道这意味着什么。
This means fun.这意味着乐趣。
Or it should. And this...或者它应该。这…
This is not fun, okay?这不好玩，好吗？
This is not fun.这不是乐趣。
So you don't feel bad?所以你不觉得不好吗？
Maybe you should feel bad.也许你应该感觉不好。
Or at least feel something.或至少感觉某事。
Have you seen a girl?你看见过一个女孩吗？
Mid-20s, brown hair, glasses?二十五六岁，棕色的头发，眼镜？
Uh...休斯敦大学...
Oh, jeez.哦，天啊。
Hey.嘿.
Please tell me请告诉我
you got your pain slider set to zero.你把你的痛苦滑块设置为零。
Yeah, I think so.是的，我想是的。
- Okay, listen.-好的，听。
- How many of them are dead?-他们有多少人死了？
Like what percentage?喜欢什么比例？
As in full-timers?和全职的一样吗？
Eighty. Eighty-five.八十。八零五。
I'm sorry.我很抱歉.
- I'm not gonna jump.-我不会跳。
- I know, and I'm sorry, whatever it's...-我知道，我很抱歉，不管它的。
In the time I've been here,在我一直在这里的时候，
I said I wouldn't...我说我不会的。
I don't know, do feelings.我不知道，做感情。
You freaked me out.你吓到我了。
I don't want to like anyone.我不想喜欢任何人。
So you've been just...所以你一直只是…
totally fucking inconvenient.完全他妈的不方便。
It's that...是这样的…
I don't know how long there is.我不知道有多久。
And I can't. I wasn't prepared for you.而我不能，我没有为你准备。
For wanting something...因为想要的东西…
Next week it is.下周是。
I'm getting married.我要结婚了。
Next week?下个星期吗？
To nice Greg?要漂亮的格雷戈？
- Sure you're going through with that?-你肯定会这样吗？
- I have to.-我必须。
- You have to?-你必须？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
He really is a good guy.他真的是一个好人。
I mean, my family don't approve, but...我的意思是，我的家人不赞成，但…
they can't stop us.他们不能阻止我们。
I know he pities me. That pisses me off.我知道他同情我。气死我了。
But that's not fair 'cause he's...但这是不公平的，因为他的..
You said you don't know你说你不知道
how much time there is.有多少时间。
What does that mean?那是什么意思？
They tell me three months.他们告诉我三个月。
It's spread basically everywhere.它的传播基本上无处不在。
They said three months before他们说，三个月前
six months ago.六个月前。
So, you know, what do they know?所以，你知道，他们知道什么？
Doesn't even taste of anything.甚至没有任何东西的味道。
- But so you'll stay here after?-但你会呆在这里吗？
- No.-不。
When I'm done, I am done.当我完成的时候，我已经做了。
But that's cra... I mean...但是，CRA…我的意思是…
- Why?-为什么？
- Richard.-李察。
That's...那是...
My husband's name was Richard.我丈夫的名字叫李察。
He died just two years ago.他是两年前去世的。
So we had the opportunity所以我们有机会
to stay in San Junipero.在三Junipero。
Pass over.过去。
Didn't take it.没有采取它。
- Didn't want to take it.-不想拿它。
- Why wouldn't anyone take it?-为什么没有人拿它？
He had his viewpoint.他有自己的观点。
There were things he believed他相信的东西
and things he didn't believe in,和他不相信的东西，
and this place was one of them.这个地方是他们中的一个。
Wouldn't even visit. Take the trial run.甚至不会访问。试运行。
Shit.倒霉.
I didn't know if I wanted to try it我不知道我是不是想试试
but... I mean...但…我的意思是…
Jesus, without this place,Jesus，没有这个地方，
I never would've met someone like you.我从来没有见过像你这样的人。
- Yeah, you could have.-是的，你可以。
- No, I wouldn't.-不，我不会的。
- We could have met outside all this.-我们可以在这一切之外。
- No.-不。
You... would not have got me at all.你…根本不会有我在所有。
At all.完全.
If we really met, I mean...如果我们真的见面了，我的意思是…
If we really met, you wouldn't like me.如果我们真的>相遇，你就不会喜欢我了。
Try me.我尝试。
Or you'd...或者你会..
You wouldn't want to spend time with me.你不想和我在一起。
- You'd come and then...-你来了，然后…
- Try me.-尝试我。
Why?为什么？
Why? What's the point?为什么？这有什么意义？
What? Where are you? Houston?什么？你在哪儿啊？休斯敦？
Carson City, Nevada.卡森城，内华达州。
So come on.所以来吧。
I showed you mine.我展示给你我的。
Where are you?你在哪？
- I can just look it up.-我可以看看它。
- Santa Rosa, California.-圣罗莎，加利福尼亚。
- That's no distance.-这是没有距离。
- I don't want you to...-我不想你…
- I don't want you to see me. I'm scared...-我不想让你看到我。我怕极了。
- And I'm dying.-我要死了。
Whatever you are can't scare me.无论你是什么都不能吓到我。
Let me come visit.让我来参观。
I want to say hi.我想说声嗨。
__
Here you go.干得好.
You okay?你还好吗？
Please check in at our self-service pods请在我们的自助荚体上检查一下/我>
using swipe cards provided.使用提供的滑动卡。
- You must be Kelly.-你一定是凯莉。
- I guess I must.-我想我必须。
- She's waiting for you.-她在等你。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
Please.拜托.
She won't be able她将不能
to physically respond in any way.以任何方式作出身体回应。
But she can hear you.但她能听到你。
I'll give you some privacy.我会给你一些隐私。
Hello, stupid.你好，愚蠢。
It's good to see you.很好见到你。
Uh... Hello. Excuse me. Is it... Kelly?休斯敦大学...你好.请原谅我.它是...凯莉？
It is.它是.
- I'm Greg.-我是格雷戈。
- You're Greg?-你是格雷戈？
Holy shit.天啊.
Yeah, I think it's great是的，我认为这是伟大的
that you came down here in person你亲自来这里
before she passes over.在她去世之前。
Even her folks甚至她的家人
don't come visit no more so...不要来访问，没有更多的…
She's passing over?她在过吗？
- When?-什么时候？
- Uh...-嗯…
- Let's go grab a coffee.-我们去喝一杯咖啡吧。
- Okay.-好的。
- She didn't tell you?-她没有告诉你？
- No, she did not.-不，她没有。
- Said she was just visiting.-说她只是访问。
- More like sampling the trial version.-更像是试用版的采样。
I mean, I've only known her我的意思是，我只认识她
the past three years.过去三年。
We talk on the comm box.我们的通讯盒说话。
She told you how she ended up她告诉你她是怎么结束的
quadriplegic?四肢瘫痪？
And how long she's been that way?她有多久了？
One night, she's 21,一天晚上，她21，
comes out to her folks.出来给她的家人。
They're a little uptight about it,他们对它有点紧张，
you might say.你可能会说。
They told her they don't他们告诉她他们不
want a gay daughter.想要一个同性恋的女儿。
It's not natural and so forth.这是不自然的，等等。
They fight. She gets in her car.他们的斗争。她在她的车里。
Runs it off the road. Boom!从马路上跑。繁荣!
- When she was 21?-当她21岁的时候？
- More than 40 years back.-超过40年。
It's been her whole lifetime, basically.这是她的一生，基本上。
So the whole San Junipero system所以整个三Junipero系统
has been a big deal for her.对她是一个大问题。
The biggest deal.最大的交易。
Of course now, until she passes over,当然，直到她过去，
it goes permanent,它是永恒的，
she's on a five-hour weekly limit.她每周一五小时的极限。
I guess you're the same.我想你是一样的。
They ration it out.他们定量的。
They don't trust us with more.他们不相信我们更多。
They say you go crazy他们说你疯了
if you have too much, you know?如果你有太多，你知道吗？
You don't leave your seat.你不离开你的座位。
You disassociate body from mind.你把身体从心。
Like that doesn't happen像这样不会发生
in every senior home already.在每一个年长的家里。
The system's there系统的那里
for therapeutic reasons,治疗原因，
immersive nostalgia therapy.沉浸式怀旧疗法。
Plunge you into a world of memories.把你投入到一个回忆的世界。
Helps with Alzheimer's,有助于阿尔茨海默氏症，
that's what they say.这就是他们说的。
Small mercies.小小的恩惠。
So...所以…
About this marriage...关于这婚姻…
The state's got a triple lockdown国家有三锁定
on euthanasia cases.安乐死案件。
You gotta have a sign-off from the doc,你必须有一个签名的文件，
the patient, a family member.病人，一个家庭成员。
It's to stop folks from passing over just是为了阻止人们刚刚过去
because they prefer San Junipero flat out.因为他们喜欢三Junipero平了。
Anyhow, Yorkie's family,总之，Yorkie的家庭，
they're big-time religious,他们是大时代的宗教，
and they will not sign.他们不会签署。
But a spouse can override them.但配偶可以推翻他们。
- Hence the wedding bells.因此婚礼的钟声。
- You got it.-你得到它。
We got a pastor coming tomorrow a.m.,我们有一个牧师明天上午来，
and then she's scheduled to pass然后她就要过去了
tomorrow afternoon.明天下午。
"Scheduled to pass."“预定通过。”
Let's just call it dying.让我们把它称之为死亡。
If you can call it dying.如果你可以称之为死亡。
Uploaded to the cloud, sounds like heaven.上传到云，听起来像天堂。
I guess.我猜。
You gonna wear a suit?你要穿西装吗？
The ceremony's on my coffee break.婚礼在我的咖啡馆休息。
I never married so I just figured,我从来没有结婚，所以我只是想，
you know, what's the harm?你知道，有什么危害吗？
You're a good man.你是一个好人。
It's the least I could do, right?这是我能做的最起码的事，对吗？
Think you could hook us up认为你可以吸引我们
to the system now?到系统了吗？
Just for a little while,只是一小会儿，
before she passes?在她过去之前？
You can still see her afterwards.你仍然可以看到她。
I mean, then she's no limit.我的意思是，她没有极限。
She's full, fat, permanent San Juniperan.她丰满，脂肪，永圣juniperan。
I know, but can you?我知道，但你能吗？
Seriously, it is so tight here说真的，这里太紧了
that they monitor every...他们监视每一个…
I only want a moment.我只想要一个时刻。
Ma'am.太太.
- You got five minutes-你有五分钟的时间
- Thank you.-谢谢。
Hey!嘿!
I've never been here我从来没有在这里
during the daylight.在白天。
It's warm.它是温暖的。
Listen, I gotta be quick.听着，我得快点。
So I spoke to Greg.所以我和格雷戈说话了。
Oh.哦.
- You're passing over tomorrow?-你明天就要过了吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
Couple of hours after the wedding.婚礼后几个小时。
So I guess I am technically所以我猜我在技术上
honeymooning here forever.会永远在这里。
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.对不起，我没有告诉你。
- I'm gonna say something crazy.-我要说些疯狂的话。
- Okay.-好的。
Wanna marry me instead?想嫁给我吗？
It's just... Greg seems great, but...这只是…格雷戈似乎很伟大，但…
Why not someone you've connected with?为什么不是你和你联系的人？
Is that a yes?那是吗？
...to be your lawfully wedded wife,…做你的合法妻子，
to have and to hold,拥有并持有，
in sickness and in health,在疾病和健康，
in good times and in woe,在美好的时光和悲哀中，
for richer, for poorer...为更丰富，为穷人…
__
Hold tight.抓住。
There you go.做你的吧。
Nearly there.近有。
That's it.够了就要这些。
Are you sure you're all right?你肯定你没事吧？
Hey!嘿!
You didn't dress up to see me?你没有穿衣服去看我吗？
Oh...哦...
Come on!来吧！
Better?更好的吗？
Whoop!呐喊！
Oh!哦!
Oh! Whoo!哦!喔！
Looks so real.看起来如此真实。
It feels so real!它感觉如此真实！
- What are you doing?-你在干什么？
- Oh, I love it here!-哦，我喜欢这里！
I just love it.我只是喜欢它。
- You've been here before.-你以前来过这里。
- But now I live here!-但现在我住在这里！
Be with me.和我在一起。
- I'm with you now.-我现在和你在一起。
- That's not what I mean.-这不是我的意思。
Pass over.过去。
- When it's your time.-当你的时间。
- Yorkie.-约克。
- Stay here with me.-呆在这里和我在一起。
- Can we just enjoy tonight?-我们今晚能享受吗？
It's almost midnight.几乎是午夜了。
In ten minutes, you're out of here.在十分钟内，你就离开这里。
Then I gotta wait a week然后我得等一个星期
to see you again.再次见到你。
- You know I'm just a visitor.-你知道我只是一个访客。
- What, a couple of months, then what?-什么，几个月，然后什么？
- We're not discussing this.-我们不是在讨论这个。
- Then you're gone.-然后你走了。
- Just gone. You could have forever.-刚刚走了。你可以拥有永远。
- Forever?永远？
- Who can even make sense of forever?-谁甚至能有永远的感觉？
- However long you want then.-无论你想要多久。
I mean, you can remove yourself我的意思是，你可以把你自己
like that.这样的。
It's not a trap.这不是一个陷阱。
I mean, look at it! Jesus! Touch it!我的意思是，看看它！Jesus！触摸它！
- I'm going.-我要去。
- Hey! Oh. Hey.-嘿！哦.嘿.
It's real.这是真的。
This is real.这是真实的。
And this.这。
- Hmm?-嗯？
- Come on.来吧。
You know that was just a gesture.你知道这只是一个手势。
- You married me.-你嫁给了我。
- To help you pass over.-帮助你过去。
- As a... kindness.-作为一个..善良。
- It's not so kind to leave.离开并不是很好。
Okay, look, look, I'm sorry, I just...好吧，看，看，我很抱歉，我只是…
I got this chance.我得到了这个机会。
We got this chance.获得了这个机会。
I wanna share it with you.我想和你分享。
I said I made my choice.我说我做了我的选择。
What is it? You feel bad这是什么？你感觉不好
because your husband isn't here?因为你丈夫不在这里？
- Because that was his choice.-因为这是他的选择。
- Don't.Don的。
He chose not to stay here.他选择不呆在这里。
It's like he left you.就像他离开了你。
You know, he could have stayed,你知道，他本来可以留下来的，
but he chose to leave you.但他选择离开你。
- You don't know what you're saying.-你不知道你在说什么。
- You should be mad at him.-你应该对他生气。
- Not whipping yourself with guilt.不是鞭打自己的内疚。
- Get off me.-离开我。
You can't see it!你看不到它！
But what he did, it was selfish actually!但他所做的，这是自私的！
Forty-nine years...四零九年…
I was with him for 49 years.我和他在一起49年了。
You can't begin to imagine.你无法想象。
You can't know...你不知道…
the bond, the commitment, the boredom,债券，承诺，无聊，
the yearning, the laughter,渴望，笑声，
the love of it.它的爱。
The fucking love. You just cannot know!他妈的爱。你只是不知道！
Everything we sacrificed.我们牺牲的一切。
The years I gave him.这些年我给了他。
The years he gave me.这些年他给了我。
Did you think to ask?你有没有想到要问？
Did it occur to you to ask?你有没有想到要问？
We had a daughter.我们有一个女儿。
Alison.艾丽森。
Always difficult, always beautiful.总是困难的，总是美丽的。
Died at 39 years old, bless her heart.在39岁去世，祝福她的心。
And Richard and I,和李察和我，
we felt that heartbreak as one.当我们感到心碎。
You think you're the only person你认为你是唯一的人
ever suffered, go fuck yourself.曾经遭受过，去他妈的自己。
- Well, I didn't know...-嗯，我不知道…
- Didn't think to.-没想到。
You know, when he was dying,你知道，当他快要死的时候，
Richard said to me李察对我说
when they offered him this,当他们给他这个，
to pass over, pass through,通过，通过，
spend eternity in this fucking graveyard在这该死的墓地里度过永恒
you're so in love with,你是如此的爱，
he said, "How can I?他说：“我怎么能呢？
When she missed out, how can I?"当她错过了，我怎么能？”
And so he went.所以他去了。
And I wish I could believe he's我希望我能相信他
with her now,现在和她在一起，
that they're together, but I don't.他们在一起，但我不。
I believe they're nowhere.我相信他们是无处的。
Just like you said.就像你说的。
Gone. No, I pitied you,跑了.不，我同情你，
and that's the truth. I pitied you.这是事实。我同情你。
Now you give me some sales pitch现在你给我一些销售摊位
about how fucking peachy forever怎么他妈的桃色的永远
could be.可以是.
I'm sorry.我很抱歉.
You wanna spend forever你想永远的度过
somewhere nothing matters?在什么地方没有什么要紧的事？
End up like Wes?结束像韦斯？
All those lost fucks at the Quagmire那些失去了乱搞在泥潭
trying anything to feel something,尝试任何感觉的东西，
go ahead.前进.
But I'm out. I'm gone.但我出去了。我走了。
Kelly, I'm sorry. Kelly!凯莉，我很抱歉。凯利!
__
Hey, Kelly.嘿，凯莉。
- You all right?-你没事吧？
- Yeah, I am fine.-是的，我很好。
- Well, okay then.-好吧，好吧。
- Huh?-嗯？
Kelly?凯莉？
All things considered...考虑的所有事情…
I guess I'm ready.我想我已经准备好了。
For what?为了什么？
For the rest of it.对于它的其余部分。
__
Ready?准备好了吗？
Whoo!喔！
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com