- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
__
Kenny? Big spillage on table four. Sorry.肯尼？表四大泄漏。对不起的.
Okay. All right.可以.好吧。
Excuse me.请原谅我.
Someone forgot this.有人忘记了这个。
Oh, thank you!哦，谢谢您。
- What do you say?-你说什么？
- Thank you.-谢谢。
- It's all right.-这一切都是正确的。
- She forgets everything. Thanks again.-她忘记了一切。再次感谢。
She was some yoga teacher,她是一些瑜伽老师，
proper bendy. Look. Look.适当的弯曲。看。看。
Jesus! Fuck! What, sheJesus！性交!什么，她
sent that to you, did she?把那寄给你，是吗？
Double naughty.双淘气。
Jog on.慢跑。
Linds!种！
Linds, where's my laptop?很多，我的笔记本在哪里？
- Don't be a bell end!-不要成为一个钟结束！
- Use your own.-使用你自己的。
- Mine's bust. Yours has gone all frozen.-我的胸部。你的一切都被冻结了。
- What did you do?-你做了什么？
- I was trying to put on this film thing.-我试图穿上这部电影的事。
- What film thing?-什么电影的事？
Don't know. Some programme不知道.一些计划
lets you watch free films.让你看免费电影。
While I was trying to put it on,当我试图把它，
then it locked up.然后它被锁起来。
- Look, it's not my fault.-看，这不是我的错。
- Don't take it again. It's not yours.-不要再拿它。这不是你的。
- Oh, fix mine when you've done that.-哦，修复我的当你这样做。
- "Fix mine when you've done that."-“修复我的当你这样做。”
__
- Stop nicking my Cokes!停止我的可乐刻痕！
- Whatever.无论。
Did you draw that yourself, Kenny?你画的是你自己吗，肯尼？
Thanks, Kenny. See you tomorrow.谢谢，肯尼。明天见.
Bye.再见.
- Bye, Kenny.再见，肯尼。
- Bye, Kenny, I'll see you tomorrow.再见，肯尼，我明天会见到你。
You're mental.你是精神上的。
- You're mental.-你是精神上的。
- You're a thief.-你是个小偷。
Love? Kenny? What do you think?爱吗？肯尼？您是怎么想的？
- I'm still not used to the colour.-我还不习惯颜色。
- It's nice.-很好。
Yeah?是吗？
Do me a favour and prison-guard帮我一个忙，帮我个忙
your sister, will you?你妹妹，好吗？
I won't be late. Probably.我不会迟到。可能.
Oh, my God! He's outside.啊，天哪！他在外面。
There's a lasagna thing in the freezer.冰箱里有一个千层面的东西。
I love you.我爱你！
__
Have you seen my keys?你看见我的钥匙了吗？
You okay, Ken? Love?你还好吗，肯？爱吗？
Yeah, fine.是的，好。
Ha!哈!
- Morning, Kenny.-早上，肯尼。
- Hi.-嗨。
__
- Kenny?-肯尼？
- Feeling really sick.-感觉真的很恶心。
- You've only just got here.-你才刚刚到这里。
- I know but think I might throw up.-我知道，但我想我可能会呕吐。
Okay, just next time can you...?好吧，下一次你能……吗？
Whoa! Easy, knobber.哇！容易，二岁鹿。
__
Come on.来吧。
- It's fragile.-它是脆弱的。
- What is it?-它是什么？
They told me to do that.他们告诉我这样做。
Is that it? What do I do now?那个是吗？我现在做什么？
I can't really help you.我真的不能帮助你。
What do I have to do?我必须做什么？
Just whatever they say and once不管他们说什么，一次
you've done that, you're out.你这样做了，你出去了。
They let you off.他们让你离开。
__
Hello?你好吗？
Del... Delivery.德尔…交货。
Wrong room.走错了房间。
They said 121.他们说121。
No, there's no delivery here.不，这里没有送货。
- But they said...-但他们说…
- I haven't ordered anything.-我什么都没有订购。
It's a cake.这是一块蛋糕。
- What cake?-什么蛋糕？
- I don't know. I think it's a sponge.-我不知道。我想这是一块海绵。
I didn't order a cake so我没有订一个蛋糕
just take it back to the bakery只要把它带回面包店
- and tell them they got it wrong.-告诉他们，他们错了。
- Look, if I...-看，如果我..
I don't want the cake.我不想要蛋糕。
So go away or I call the front desk.所以走开或我打电话给前台。
__
I will kick that我会踢那个
cake up your fucking arse.蛋糕上你的屁股。
M-Mindy sent me.m-mindy寄给我。
- What is this? Where's Mindy?-这是什么？Mindy在哪里？
- I was just told to give this to you.-我只是告诉你把这个给你。
- Mindy told you?Mindy告诉你的？
- No.-不。
- You said "Mindy."你说“Mindy”。
- That's what they told me to say.这就是他们告诉我说的。
Get inside.进去。
So what are you saying?那你在说什么？
Are you saying Mindy ordered the cake?你是说Mindy订的蛋糕吗？
No, uh, I don't know.不，呃，我不知道。
It... they... it was them.它…他们…是他们。
Them? They? Who the他们呢？他们？谁的
fuck are you on about?你他妈的是什么？
- The people.-人民。
- What fucking people?-什么他妈的人？
The phone people.电话人。
The people on the phone.电话里的人。
They told me to bring the cake,他们告诉我要带蛋糕，
and they're leaving texts on my phone,他们要在我的手机上留下短信，
- and then I do what they say.-然后我做他们说的。
- Whoa, whoa. Slow down.哇哦，哇哦。慢下来。
Just breathe through your nose.通过你的鼻子呼吸。
Through your nose. Okay?通过你的鼻子。好吗？
Good. Now, just show me what好的。现在，只给我看什么
they said. On your phone.他们说。在你的手机上。
- Show me the text.-给我看文本。
- Okay, well, um... This.-好的，嗯，嗯…这。
- I should...-我应该…
- Shut up. Just let me.-闭嘴。只是让我。
What the fuck is this?这他妈的是什么？
- Who are these people?-这些人是谁？
- I don't know.-我不知道。
- Who are you?-你是谁？
- I'm not them.-我不是他们。
They send me messages,他们给我发短信，
and I do what they say.我做他们说的。
Why? Why would you do that?为什么？你为什么要这样做？
Is it them?是他们吗？
__
- They said I had to do that.-他们说我必须这样做。
- Jesus Christ!- Jesus Christ！
Okay, okay.好吧，好的。
They're saying they just need他们说他们只是需要
us to follow their instructions,我们遵循他们的指示，
and everything will be okay. Okay?一切都会好起来的。好吗？
Shit!倒霉!
They're saying we have to do it together.他们说我们必须一起做。
- What do we have to do?-我们必须做什么？
- Just take the cake somewhere.-把蛋糕拿在什么地方。
They sent me an address.他们给我寄了一个地址。
A map coordinate thing.地图坐标的东西。
- And there's a car we need to get.-有一辆车，我们需要得到。
- A car? What sort of car?-一辆车？什么类型的车？
I don't know what sort of car.我不知道什么样的车。
They said it's in the car park outside.他们说是在外面的停车场。
They sent me a licence plate.他们给我寄了一个车牌。
That's all I know.这是我所知道的一切。
Why both of us?为什么我们俩？
I don't know!我不知道。
Just let me deal with my让我来处理我的
fucking shoe, please.鞋鞋，请。
__
What have they said?他们说了什么？
They say, "Go with him.他们说：“和他一起去吧。
Take the package."拿包。”
Okay.可以.
"V760 DHM."“v760 DHM。”
V760 DHM.v760 DHM。
I'm getting fucking我他妈的
number blindness here.这里的数字盲。
That's it.够了就要这些。
All right. They said the好吧。他们说
keys are on the back. Okay.钥匙在后面。可以.
Look, maybe you better看，也许你更好
drive. Do you drive?驱动。你开车吗？
- I mean, I had a drink back there.-我的意思是，我在那里喝了一杯。
- I can't. I can... I can drive.-我不能…我会开车。
I'm still learning.我仍然在学习。
Haven't passed my test yet.还没有通过我的测试。
All right. Uh... You're navigating.好吧。休斯敦大学...你导航。
Okay, you've got a sat nav on your phone?好吧，你有一个卫星导航在您的电话吗？
Yep.是的.
Here it is. Punch that in.钱在这儿在冲床。
It's a street somewhere out of town.这是一个在小镇上的街道。
Sort of High Wycombe-ish.海维康杂交种。
They said we got to be there by two.他们说我们要在那里待两个。
It's gonna be tight.它会紧的。
So I'm guessing they got some shit on所以我猜他们有一些屎
you that they're threatening to put out?你说他们威胁要出去？
With me, it's...和我在一起，它的..
You saw the room, fucking lacy knickers.你看到房间，他妈的蕾丝内裤。
I was waiting for a prostitute.我在等待一个妓女。
Escort, hooker, whatever护航，妓女，不管
they call them now.他们现在打电话给他们。
I got a family, which is great.我有一个家庭，这是伟大的。
You get bored.你厌倦了。
I mean, when I was young, I used to like...我的意思是，当我年轻的时候，我习惯了…
I can't fucking justify it.我不能他妈的证明它。
I just wanted to fuck a 20-something.我只想他妈的一个20的东西。
For old times' sake, I don't know.看在旧时光的份上，我不知道。
I joined this website. I was curious.我加入了这个网站。我很好奇。
Just wanted to see what was on there.只是想看看有什么。
I got talking to Mindy,我和Mindy说话，
who I thought was Mindy.我以为她是Mindy。
I mean, she sent me pictures.我的意思是，她给我发了照片。
I sent some back.我送了一些回来。
Phone photos. Grabbing my cock.手机的照片。抓我的公鸡。
You name it.你说出来。
They got the whole fucking thing.他们得到了整个该死的东西。
But not just pictures, chat messages.但不只是图片，聊天信息。
All the arrangements, where and when.所有的安排，在哪里和什么时候。
Me haggling over the price我讨价还价
and they say they got it all.他们说他们得到了一切。
Sucked up the whole hard吸了整个硬盘
drive like an audit.开车像审计。
Fucking twat. What a fucking idiot!该死的笨蛋。什么他妈的白痴！
If that shit gets out,如果那该死的东西出来，
that's my wife out the door.那是我的妻子在门外。
Then there's the kids, she'll take them.然后是孩子们，她会带他们。
Oh, no, not a doubt in my mind哦，不，在我的脑海里没有疑问
she'd take them and she'd win.她会带他们，她会赢。
Custody, she'd win.保管，她会赢。
And I'm not losing my kids.我不会失去我的孩子。
I tell you that right now.我现在告诉你。
No way! Absolutely fucking no!没有办法！绝对他妈的没有！
They filmed me.他们拍摄了我。
- Filmed you...-拍摄你…
- Through my computer camera.通过我的电脑相机。
- What, like, filmed you?-什么，像，拍摄了你？
- Yeah, like, you know, doing it.-是的，喜欢，你知道，这样做。
- Like sex?-喜欢性？
- No. Like, you... you know.-不喜欢，你…你知道的.
Jerking off. Jerking off手淫。手淫
to porn or something?看色情片还是什么？
Well, everyone does that.嗯，每个人都这样做。
- The fucking pope probably does that.-他妈的教皇可能会这样。
- They're gonna put it everywhere.-他们会把它放在到处。
Like they're gonna send it to everyone.就像他们会把它发送给每个人。
- Oh, shit the fuck!-哦，该死的他妈的！
- What? What?-什么？什么？
- How long's that light been on?那灯亮了多久了？
- What light?-什么光？
Whoever's car this is,这是谁的车，
they left it fucking empty.他们把它他妈的空。
I won't be a minute.我不会是一分钟。
Unleaded. Unleaded.无铅的.无铅的.
Oh, bugger!哦，妈！
Listen, you pay, yeah? It'll save time.听着，你付钱了，是吗？它将节省时间。
Have you got any money?你有钱吗？
Okay, Visa card PIN number 3109.好的，签证卡密码号3109。
Say that back to me.回到我的话。
- Visa card...-签证卡…
- Just the number!-只有数字！
- Uh... 3109.-嗯…3109。
- Okay, go!-好的，去！
Pump four!泵四！
- What's your pump number?-你的泵号是多少？
- Four.-四。
- You want some chocolate?-你要一些巧克力吗？
- No.-不。
- It's two for one this week.这是本周的两个。
- I'm okay.-我好吗。
31.89.31.89。
Pop your PIN in.弹出你的脚。
- If you're sure you don't mind?-如果你确定你不介意的话？
- No, no, of course not.-不，不，当然不。
- I'll get on to that. Make some calls.-我会继续。打一些电话。
- Brilliant! It's next Wednesday.-辉煌！下星期三。
- Okay.-好的。
- Keep it non-dairy just to be safe.-保持它的非乳制品只是为了安全。
Okay.可以.
This is, uh...这是，嗯…
my nephew.我的侄子。
Nice to meet you.很高兴认识你.
- Kenny.-肯尼。
- Kenny. I'm Karen.-肯尼。我是凯伦。
We're both Ks.我们都是KS。
I'm head of the PTA at Theo and我在西奥PTA头
Cassie's school, for my sins.凯西的学校，为我的罪。
Just roped poor Hector into sorting只是把可怜的Hector为排序
out the catering for the quiz night.走出餐饮业的智力竞赛之夜。
Been the usual balls up.一直都是平常的球。
Listen, we better get this听着，我们最好得到这个
guy to the station.家伙到车站。
His train's... So we better go.他的火车的..所以我们最好去。
- Cansroad Station?- cansroad站吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
Oh, couldn't drop me at the哦，不能让我在
end of my road, could you?我的路的尽头，你能吗？
It's on the way. Mayer Street?它在路上。Mayer街吗？
It's the bus otherwise and that这是公共汽车，否则
goes all the way around the common.一路走在共同的周围。
- We're in a bit of a rush, actually.我们有点匆忙，实际上。
- Well, it's no detour. It's en route.-嗯，这是没有绕道。它的途中。
I'll hop out. Hardly need我会跳出来。几乎不需要
to slow down. Yeah?慢下来。是吗？
- Yep. Sure. Let's go.-是的。当然.走吧.
- Brilliant. Thanks!-辉煌。谢谢!
I'll just get in the back.我会在后面。
Oh, don't want to squash your box.哦，不想挤压你的箱子。
- What's that? Present?-那是什么？礼物？
- It's a cake.-这是一个蛋糕。
- It's just a... it's a cake for Penny.-这只是一个..这是一个便士的蛋糕。
- Oh, lucky her.哦，幸运的她。
So how is Penny?那么佩妮怎么样？
Haven't seen her since...从那以后就没见过她…
must have been sports day.一定是运动日。
She's good.她很好。
- She still planning to get back to work?-她还打算回去工作吗？
- Yeah. Yep.-是的。是的.
__
- I mean, how old's Theo now?我的意思是，Theo现在多少岁？
- Uh... He's seven.-嗯…他七。
__
He was so funny in the play.他在戏里很有趣。
That big top hat on.那顶大顶上的帽子。
Yeah, he had a good time.是的，他有一个很好的时间。
__
Oh, Anna's哦，安娜的
having a sleepover.在那里过夜。
Cassie's probably凯西的可能
already told you about it.已经告诉你了。
Six nine-year-olds in the house.六九岁的孩子在房子里。
I must be mad!我一定是疯了！
__
So, Kenny, where you heading back to?那么，肯尼，你要去哪里？
- Sorry. What?-对不起。什么？
- Are you going home or...?-你是回家还是……？
- Uh...-嗯…
- Train. Birmingham.火车。伯明翰。
Yeah. Uh...是啊.休斯敦大学...
- Yeah, I-I live in Birmingham.是的，我住在伯明翰。
- Oh, my husband's from Birmingham.-哦，我的丈夫来自伯明翰。
- What part are you?-你是什么角色？
- South.- South。
South.南。
- Mainly.-主要。
- Right.-对。
__
Have you always lived there?你一直住在那里吗？
'Cos you don't sound...因为你不健全…
I don't have the accent, no.我没有口音，没有。
Everyone says that...每个人都说…
That... I don't have the accent.那…我没有口音。
Didn't grow up there though.虽然没有长大那里。
I grew up somewhere else.我在别的地方长大。
Like London. I grew up in London.像伦敦。我在伦敦长大。
Okay.可以.
And is your mum and dad on是你的妈妈和爸爸
Hector's side or Penny's?Hector的球队或一分钱吗？
Someone crossing! Crossing!有人穿越！十字路口!
Sorry about that! Can't miss his train.抱歉，那！不能错过他的火车。
This is me.这是我。
Great to meet you, Kenny.很高兴见到你，肯尼。
Give my best to Penny, won't you?把我最好的钱给你，是吗？
- Yes, of course.是的，当然。
- Bye, then.再见，然后。
- Bye, Karen.再见，凯伦。
- Bye.再见。
We're gonna make it, okay?我们要去做，好吗？
It's this junction.是这个结。
- What? This one?-什么？这一个吗？
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.-是的，是的，是的。
You sure this is it?你确定这是吗？
"Look in the cake."“看蛋糕。”
Let's look in the cake.让我们看蛋糕。
Look in the cake.看蛋糕。
In the cake, I suppose.在蛋糕里，我想。
I got something.我得到了一些东西。
What the fuck?什么他妈的？
Oh, my God.我的天！
"Five minutes to decide."“五分钟决定。”
Decide what?决定什么？
- "Who is driver?"-“司机是谁？”
- "Who is robber?"-“谁是强盗？”
__
Oh, no. No.哦，不。
- W-w-we can't. We...- w-w-we不行我们…
- I'm driver.-我是司机。
You said you can't drive. I'm driver.你说你不能开车。我是司机。
I'll be right here with我会在这里
the engine running.发动机运行。
We... We can't. We...我们…我们不能…
Then how else are we gonna那么我们怎么会去
deal with this, Kenny?处理这个，肯尼？
- I'm not...-我不是…
- Listen to me.-听我说。
- Shut up and listen!-闭嘴，听！
Hat and sunglasses.帽子和太阳眼镜。
No one's going to ID you.没有人会想你。
You could be Kevin fucking Bacon.你可能是凯文他妈的熏猪肉。
That's point one.这是一个点。
Shut up!闭嘴!
Point two, in a robbery, staff are trained.第二点，在抢劫中，工作人员被训练。
I am not...我不是…
They are trained to hand over the cash.他们被训练把钱交给他们。
No argument. I saw it in a documentary.不争论。我在一个纪录片里看到的。
No resistance. It looked easy.没有阻力。它看起来很容易。
It's not easy.炒股可不简单，它有很深的学问的。
I know it isn't easy, but what the我知道这是不容易的，但什么
fuck else are we gonna do? Hey?他妈的我们要怎么办？嘿？
This gets out, I will lose my kids.这就出来了，我会失去我的孩子。
And I swear to God,我向上帝发誓，
I will stand in the kitchen我会站在厨房里
and put a fucking bread knife并放了一个他妈的面包刀
through my throat if that happens.通过我的喉咙，如果发生。
- I only looked at pictures and...-我只看照片和…
- And beat one off on camera?-然后在相机上拍一拍？
That's what they got, yeah?这是他们得到的，是吗？
Your hot little face, blurred fist,你的热的小脸蛋，模糊的拳头，
dick burping fucking spunk everywhere?迪克打嗝他妈的勇气呢？
Your mum's gonna love that on Facebook,你妈妈会喜欢脸谱网的，
Twitter, Insta-fucking-whatever.推特，不他妈的什么。
And her friends. All eyes和她的朋友们。所有的眼睛
on you, giving it that.在你，给它。
Toss in the cunts at work,抛在女人在工作，
calling you Spurty McGoo.打电话给你spurty mcgoo。
Laughing at your come face,嘲笑你的脸，
making it their desktop wallpaper.使它成为他们的桌面壁纸。
It's not just weeks.这不仅仅是几个星期。
We're talking years here.我们在这里谈论几年。
Pictures hang about on Google图片挂在谷歌
like a gypsy fucking curse.像一个诅咒的诅咒。
There's no cure for the Internet.互联网没有治愈的方法。
It would never go away.它永远不会消失。
It'd be glued to your name,它会粘在你的名字，
a fucking stain on you.你他妈的污点。
I'd hang myself if that was me.如果那是我，我会挂我自己。
Crack my fucking neck at裂纹我的他妈的脖子
the first opportunity.第一次机会。
They just want the money,他们只想要钱，
so go in there and do it.所以去那里做它。
- You'll drive away.-你会开车走。
- I am not gonna drive away.-我不会开车走。
I'm gonna be sat here我要坐在这里
with the engine running.随着发动机的运行。
I can't. I can't.我不能，我不能。
- You can. You can.-你可以。你可以.
- I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't.-我不能。我不能。我不能。我不能。
- You can.-你可以。
- I can't.-我不能。
We don't have much time, Kenny.我们没有太多的时间，肯尼。
- It's not real. This is not real.-这不是真的。这不是真的。
- You can do this.-你可以这样做。
Keep it together. Please hold it together.把它放在一起。请把它放在一起。
- Shut up, shut up, shut up! Shut up!-闭嘴，闭嘴，闭嘴！闭嘴!
- Okay.-好的。
Have you got a bag?你有一个包吗？
Glasses. Breathe through your nose.玻璃杯.通过你的鼻子呼吸。
Give me money.给我钱。
Just give me money!只要给我钱！
- Yes. Okay.-是的。可以.
- Lots of it. I need lots of it.-它的很多。我需要很多。
Sh-should I use your bag?我应该用你的包吗？
Take it.把它。
I'm going to pass this我要通过这个
back to you now. Is that okay?现在回到你。那好吗？
There was some bloke standing有一些家伙站
there on his phone freaking me out.在他的电话把我吓坏了。
- Did you get it?-你明白了吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
Go faster.走得更快。
Speed limit's 40. Wanna限速的40。想要
get stopped for speeding now?现在停车超速了吗？
- Oh, shit.哦，该死的。
- Fuck!-他妈的！
That's a siren.那是个警报器。
Shh! Shush.嘘！Shush。
- Let's go!-让我们走吧！
- Shut up.-闭嘴。
Wait, wait.等待，等待。
Come on.来吧。
Okay.可以.
We're okay.我们是好的。
We should text them, no?我们应该给他们发短信，不是吗？
Tell them we got the money.告诉他们我们得到了钱。
- They say we got to take it somewhere.-他们说我们要把它带到某个地方。
- Where?-在哪里？
This is it.终于到了！
Yeah.是啊.
Here we go.让我们开始吧。
"Final instruction."“最后的指令。”
"Take car away and destroy."“把车开走并摧毁。”
Destroy the car.摧毁汽车。
"Just you alone."“只有你一个人。”
Why just you?为什么只是你？
__
I got to take the money我得拿钱
somewhere over there.在那里的某个地方。
Why? Why have I got to do it?为什么？为什么我要这样做呢？
Fuck knows.谁知道。
__
So...所以…
You better go, yeah?你最好去，是吗？
Hey, you got this far, haven't you?嘿，你有这么远，不是吗？
Just drop it off. That's it.刚刚放弃它。够了就要这些。
You'll be all right.你会没事的。
Hey, listen, Kenny. Look.嘿，听着，肯尼。看。
I'm sorry about... just back there.我很抱歉…刚刚回到那里。
Shouting at you. Calling you stuff.对你大喊大叫。打电话给你的东西。
I'm an all right bloke really.我是一个好男人真的。
I swear I am, when it's...我发誓我是，当它的。
When stuff's normal.当东西很正常。
You take care, yeah?你照顾，是吗？
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, hang on.是的，是的。挂上，挂上。
They told me I had to他们告诉我，我必须
set this thing off first.把这东西先关。
Okay.可以.
You got the prize money?你拿到奖金了吗？
- Prize money?奖金？
- You know, for the... fight?-你知道的…战斗？
How is there a fight?怎么打？
- They didn't tell you?-他们没有告诉你？
- No.-不。
We've got to fight...我们必须战斗…
...or else they post……否则他们的职位
everything they've got on us.他们对我们所拥有的一切。
Winner takes the money.赢家拿钱。
We've got to do it.我们必须这样做。
I mean...我的意思是…
They're watching.他们在看。
What sort of fight?什么样的战斗？
How do we know when it's over?我们怎么知道什么时候结束？
How... How do we know who's won?怎样...我们怎么知道谁赢了？
I don't know about you,我不知道你，
but my life's over if this gets out.但我的生命结束了，如果这出来。
Fucking over.你妈的。
What they get you for?他们给你什么？
I just looked at some photos.我只是看了一些照片。
That's all.这就是全部.
I just looked at one or two photos.我只是看了一张或两张照片。
Yeah.是啊.
Yeah, yeah, I just是的，是的，我只是
looked at pictures too.看图片太。
How young were they? In the pictures?他们是多么年轻？在图片里？
How young?多年轻？
Yeah.是啊.
Well, me too.嗯，我也是。
Look, mate. Don't. Please.看，伙计。不请。
Please.拜托.
Mindy?Mindy？
Is that what you've become?那是你变成的吗？
- A dirty, sick, disgusting pervert?一个肮脏，恶心，恶心的变态？
- Hey, relax!嘿，放松！
Look at me! Is that what you are?看我！这是你的吗？
__
What did you do, Kenny?你做了什么，肯尼？
They're saying it's kids!他们说这是孩子！
That you've been looking at kids!你一直在看着孩子们！
And Lindsey saw it.Lindsey看到它。
There's a video of you.有一个你的视频。
All of her friends have got it!她的所有的朋友都得到了它！
Kids, Kenny! Tell me that's not true!孩子，肯尼！告诉我那不是真的！
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --