Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com
They're ready now.他们现在准备好了。
Perhaps we could begin with也许我们可以开始
your earliest recollections你最早的记忆
of the events of last May.去年五月的事件。
Well, I first got involved on the 15th.嗯，我第一次参加了第十五。
Could you move the microphone你能移动麦克风吗
a little closer?稍微靠近一点？
Here?在这里吗？
I first got involved on the 15th.我第一次参与了第十五。
__
Chancellor Tom Pickering has defended总理Tom Pickering辩护
the government's stance“我”政府的立场
on disability benefits残疾福利：/我>
as outrage over the death of so-called“我”为所谓的死亡的愤怒
"Wheelchair Martyr" Gwen Marbury grows.“轮椅烈士”马布里格温长。
More than 20,000 people超过20000人
have signed a petition已经签署了一份请愿书
demanding the sacking要求解雇
of newspaper columnist Jo Powers报纸专栏作家Jo Powers
following her controversial article<我追随她有争议的文章
about Gwen Marbury.关于Gwen Marbury，
Conservationists have announced保育人士宣布
another extinction.另一个灭绝。
The Siberian crane has died out西伯利亚鹤已灭绝了
following an unprecedented reduction以前所未有的减少
in its wetland habitat.在其湿地生境中。
And the honeybee-mimicking drone insects和蜜蜂模仿昆虫机器人
known as ADIs被称为艾滋病
have been activated已被激活
for their second summer.对于他们的第二个夏天。
Hope you're ashamed of yourself.希望你为自己感到羞愧。
- Bitch.-婊子。
- Pleasure's all mine.快乐的全是我的。
__
Yo Powers?Yo Powers？
Jo Powers. Jo > 的权力。
Whatever's in there, will it detonate?无论在那里，它会引爆？
That's from bakery. For you.那是面包店的。为你.
- Thank you.-谢谢。
Hello, darling!你好，亲爱的！
Creative, your well-wishers.有创意，你的好心人。
__
Don't eat it.不要吃它。
It's a cake. That's its job.这是一块蛋糕。这是它的工作。
I'm going to have a bath.我要去洗个澡。
♪ Sail away ♪
♪ Sail away, sail away, sail away ♪
♪ From Bissau to Palau
in the shade of Avalon ♪
__
♪ From Fiji to Tiree
and the Isles of Ebony ♪
♪ From Peru to Cebu,
hear the power of Babylon ♪
__
♪ From Bali to Cali... ♪
Ah!啊啊啊啊啊！
__
Grammy-award-winning格莱美获奖
rapper Tusk is still with us.说唱歌手图斯克还和我们在一起。
Now, Tusk,现在，图斯克，
there are loads of online videos有加载的在线视频
of people trying to emulate you,
but this is our favourite.但这是我们最喜欢的。
Take a look at this.看一看这个。
It's a young chap called Aaron Sheen.这是一个年轻的小伙子叫Aaron Sheen。
He's nine years old.他九岁了。
That is one goofy-looking kid.这是一个看起来很傻的孩子。
Not a good dancer.不是一个好的舞者。
He's nine years old!他九岁了！
Come on, he's a pretty good dancer.来吧，他是一个很好的舞者。
That young motherfucker can't dance年轻混蛋不能跳舞
for shit.因为妈的，
He should probably just give up他可能只是放弃了
now, actually.现在，实际上，
Don't hate on me for keeping it real.<我不恨我，因为它是真的。
That's a goofy little motherfucker,这是一个傻傻的小混蛋，
and he can't dance for shit.他不能为大便跳舞。
He is a big fan, Tusk.他是一个大风扇，图斯克。
Don't hate on your boy.不要恨你的孩子。
Everybody's got to start somewhere.“我”每个人都必须从某处开始。
Start somewhere?从某个地方开始？
I looked better than that...我看起来比……好……
- DCI Parke?- DCI Parke？
- No press.-没有新闻。
No, I'm not press. Um... TDC Blue Colson.不，我不按。嗯...TDC蓝科尔森。
I'm your shadow.我是你的影子。
My shadow? They said...我的影子？他们说…
Sorry. Call me Karin.对不起的.叫我卡琳。
- Did you say your name was...?-你说你的名字是…？
- Blue.蓝色的。
- B-l-u-e, Blue?- b-l-u-e，蓝色的？
- Yeah. It's not a nickname.-是的。它不是一个绰号。
- My dad liked the sound of it.我爸爸喜欢它的声音。
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
- Seen a body before?-见过一个身体吗？
- A couple.-一对夫妇。
- On video, I mean.-在视频上，我的意思是。
- Boss?老板？
This is Blue. She's my shadow.这是蓝色的。她是我的影子。
- DS Nick Shelton.- DS Nick Shelton。
- What've we got?-我们得到了什么？
- Jo Powers.- Jo Powers。
- As in...-如…
As in actual Jo Powers.正如在实际Jo Powers。
Saw something she wrote the other day看到她写的东西的另一天
about the wheelchair woman.关于轮椅的女人。
Clickbait piece. Pissed people off.在Clickbait片。生气的人了。
That article was fucking horrendous.那篇文章是他妈的可怕。
Even I signed the petition.即使我签署了请愿书。
To get her sacked.让她被解雇。
Come on.来吧。
Neighbours heard her screaming邻居们听到了她的尖叫声
and called it in.并称之为。
Hell of a struggle.地狱的斗争。
Anyone else at home?家里还有其他人吗？
Husband. Found slashed across the stomach.丈夫。发现胃大幅削减。
- By her?-她？
- Don't know.-不知道。
He was unconscious.他是无意识的。
They've taken him to St. Columbus.他们把他带到了圣。
Her mentions are still pouring in.她的提到仍在涌入。
Restraining bolt's in place.抑制螺栓的位置。
- No other points of entry?-没有其他的入口？
- No. But the outside's ringed with CCTV.不但是外面的环与央视。
- We got the code for the cams?-我们得到了凸轮的代码了吗？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
Okay, then. Check the recordings.好的，然后。检查录音。
Bag that, send it to Toxicology.袋，把它发送到毒理学。
Full autop for her, and we question她全自动手枪，和我们的问题
the husband as soon as he wakes up.丈夫一醒来就。
Come on.来吧。
- You think it's the husband?-你认为是丈夫吗？
- I'm keeping options open.-我保持选项打开。
Cutting the throat, that's unusual.切割喉咙，这是不寻常的。
Thanks, chaps.谢谢，伙计们。
- But you do think he did it?-但你认为他做了吗？
- Don't know anything yet.-什么都不知道。
These things are almost always这些东西几乎总是
either drink, drugs or domestic.无论是饮料，药物或国内。
It is how it is.它是如何。
- You driving home?-你开车回家？
- No licence. Never passed.-没有牌照。从来没有过。
I'm sort of waiting for driverless我有点等待无人驾驶
to go mainstream.去主流。
- Get in.-进入。
- No, honestly, I'll get the Tube.-不，老实说，我会得到管。
- Oh. Okay.-哦。可以.
- So you were in Tech Crime?-那么你是在科技犯罪？
- Digital Forensics. Computer murk.-数字取证。计算机的黑暗。
What happened,发生了什么事，
you get bored of it?你厌倦了吗？
Not exactly. You've seen不完全。你见过
what people tuck away on these.什么人吃了这些。
Schemes and kill lists, kiddy porn.方案和杀人名单，儿童色情。
It's not boring.这不是无聊。
I'm old enough to remember我已经长大到可以记住
when they walked around with that stuff当他们带着这些东西走的时候
just tucked away in their heads.只是藏在他们的头上。
Right. But now they can't help but正确的.但现在他们不能帮助，但
entrusting it to their little companions.委托给他们的小伙伴。
These things absorb who we are.这些东西吸收我们是谁。
They know everything about us.他们知道我们的一切。
If it's interesting,如果它很有趣，
why leave Forensics?为什么要离开法医学？
The Rannoch case.Rannoch的案子。
- Ian Rannoch?- Ian Rannoch？
- The child killings, yeah.-孩子杀人，是的。
I was the one我是那个人
who cracked his souvenir folder.谁破解了他的纪念品文件夹。
- So you saw those pictures?-所以你看到这些照片了吗？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
And the videos too. Saw them all.和视频太。看到他们所有。
You see something like that,你看到这样的东西，
it changes you.它改变了你。
You either get defeated or you think...你要么被打败，要么你认为…
You think, "Fuck me!你想，“他妈的我！
I've got to help stop that shit."我必须帮助停止那些该死的东西。”
Yeah.是啊.
- I mean, out here in the field...-我的意思是，在这里的领域…
- What fucking field?-什么他妈的领域？
You know what I mean.你明白我说的意思吧。
Out here in the real world,在现实世界里，
you can genuinely prevent stuff,你可以真正预防的东西，
can't you?你不能吗？
You are young.你年轻。
Maybe you're old?也许你老了？
Steady.稳定。
Thanks.谢谢.
- See you tomorrow.明天见。
- Yes, boss.-是的，老板。
Jo Powers has been foundJo Powers已被发现
dead at her home in West London.死在她在伦敦西部的家里。
The veteran columnist had been老专栏作家曾是
at the centre of controversy在争议的中心，
over an article she'd written about在一篇她写的文章
disability rights activist Gwen Marbury.残疾维权活动家Gwen Marbury。
The police have yet to confirm the cause...警方还没有确认原因……
It's just the first floor,这只是一楼，
first door on the...第一门上的…
- Starting early?-从早期开始？
- I asked Nick to show me the CCTV.-我让Nick给我看中央电视台。
- Oh, yeah?-哦，是吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
No one came in or out.没有人进来或出去。
Just Jo and her husband all evening.只是Jo和她的丈夫整个晚上。
- And that one there?-和那一个？
- Rear patio.-后院。
- Bust for months by the looks of it.几个月来的样子，它的样子。
- Someone could've come in through there.-有人可能已经进来了。
They'd have to climb the fence,他们不得不爬上篱笆，
make it in and out,使它进出，
knowing the camera wasn't working,知道相机不工作，
but yeah, could have happened. Technically.但是的，可能会发生。技术上。
Okay, sorry.好吧，对不起。
You're keen to help.你渴望帮助。
- She just asked!-她只是问！
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
__
Um... So...嗯...所以…
I'm collating every threat我校每一个威胁
or insult levelled at Jo Powers或侮辱瞄准Jo Powers
over the previous 48 hours.在过去的48小时。
Say it is the husband.说是丈夫。
That's a coincidence, isn't it?这是一个巧合，不是吗？
Not really.不是真的。
You've got everyone throwing a shit fit.你让每个人都扔了一个屎。
Stress levels in that household家庭中的压力水平
would've been through the roof.将已经通过屋顶。
That Internet stuff互联网的东西
drifts off like weather.像天气一样飘。
It's half hate. They don't mean it.这是半恨。他们并不意味着它。
The hate in a marriage, that's in 3D.在婚姻中的仇恨，这是在3D。
That's had work put into it.这是有工作投入到它。
That's sincere.这是真诚的。
- Yeah. I'm divorced.-是的。我离婚了。
- Um...-嗯…
Husband's up and talking.丈夫的谈话。
You're gonna love his alibi.你会爱他的借口。
__
I heard Jo screaming from upstairs.我听到乔在楼上尖叫。
And when I ran in, she was walking当我跑进来的时候，她在散步
'round the room, stumbling.在房间里，绊倒了。
She was clutching... She was clutching她紧紧地抓着…她紧紧抓着
her head as if she was in pain.她的头，仿佛她在痛苦。
And then for a moment, she stopped.然后有一刻，她停了下来。
And then it was like a seizure, she was...然后它像一个癫痫发作，她是…
thrashing... clawing at her own skin.颠簸…抓自己的皮肤。
And she turned...她转过身来…
She smashed her head...她砸了她的头…
onto the desk, hard.到桌子上，很难。
Then she... she pushed me over.然后她…她把我推了过来。
That must've been when the bottle smashed.那一定是瓶子砸了的时候。
Then she picked it up,然后她把它捡了起来，
and she started cutting herself.然后她开始切割自己。
Here. She was gouging.在这里.她刨。
I tried to stop her.我试图阻止她。
But she did this.但她这样做了。
Then she cut her throat.然后她割断了她的喉咙。
I tried to stop her.我试图阻止她。
She cut her own throat with the glass!她用玻璃割破了自己的喉咙！
Mutilated and then killed herself肢解然后自杀
for no apparent reason?没有明显的原因？
I'd say the odds are against that.我想说的是，赔率是反对。
He said it was like他说这是喜欢
she was having a seizure.她正在抽搐。
Maybe there was something in the cake.也许蛋糕里有东西。
- The cake?-蛋糕？
- It had "fucking bitch" iced on it.-它有“他妈的婊子”冰上。
- Could've been something in it.-可能是在它的东西。
- Like a drug?-像毒品？
- I don't know.-我不知道。
- That makes people kill themselves?-这会让人自杀吗？
He was sort of convincing.他是有说服力的。
- He just doesn't seem the...-他似乎不…
- Don't say "the type."-不要说“类型”。
He's ordinary. That is the type.他很普通。那个是的类型。
What, so he bounced her head off the desk?什么，所以他把她的头从桌子上跳了下来？
- Blue.蓝色的。
- Held her steady enough...-保持足够的稳定…
- What?-什么？
- Toxicology are looking at the cake.-毒理学正在看蛋糕。
- Okay.-好的。
Meantime, let's drop in同时，让我们下降
on the person that sent it.关于发送给它的人。
Got the name this morning.今天早上得到了这个名字。
- You don't need to patronize me.-你不需要光顾我。
- We're doing what you want.-我们正在做你想要的。
- Following another lead.-跟随另一个线索。
- That you think is a waste of time.-你认为是浪费时间。
Picking along dead ends just选择沿死结束只是
to prove they're dead ends,为了证明他们是死的结束，
that's most of the job.这是大部分的工作。
I'm not saying it's a waste of time.我并不是说这是浪费时间。
Just...只是…
you haven't had a chance你没有机会
to get bored of reality yet.厌倦了现实。
Okay, that was patronizing.好吧，那 光顾了。
- Is this who sent the cake?-是谁送的蛋糕吗？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
- Have we checked her social feeds?我们检查过她的社会性饲料了吗？
- I don't know.-我不知道。
__
"Death to Jo Powers."“Jo Powers死了。”
She posted that on Monday morning.她在星期一早上发布。
The bakery said that they're面包店说，他们是
not meant to do obscenities,不想做猥亵，
so I said it was for my sister,所以我说是给我妹妹的，
like just a joke thing,就像只是一个笑话的事，
and they agreed, so...他们同意了，所以…
Not cheap, their cakes.不便宜，他们的蛋糕。
With delivery, it was what, 80 quid?交货，这是什么，80英镑吗？
Um...嗯...
Well, I didn't pay for it all myself.嗯，我没有支付我自己的钱。
- We all put a pound in each.-我们都在每个人都放了一磅。
- We?我们？
Yeah. I'm on a mums and carers是啊.我在妈妈和保姆
message board.留言板。
I held a sort of whip-round.我举行了一个鞭子轮。
- You crowd-sourced the money?-你的人群来源的钱？
- Yeah, if you like.-是的，如果你喜欢的话。
From 80 other people?从80个其他人？
Look, I'm not...看，我不是…
I'm not being funny, okay?我不好笑，好吗？
I know she is dead.我知道她死了。
But did you read what she had written?但是你读过她写的东西吗？
How much do you think she got paid你认为她得到了多少钱
for spouting that horrible shit?对喷，可怕的事情吗？
I don't know.我不知道。
- I was just using my freedom of speech.-我只是在用我的言论自由。
- To send a threatening message.-发送一个威胁性的消息。
It was funny, okay?这很有趣，好吗？
And I can see if I'd done it myself,我可以看看我是否自己做过，
then that would be a bit weird,然后，这将是一个有点奇怪，
but I'm not mental.但我不是精神。
You wished she was dead.你希望她死了。
Well, uh...嗯，嗯…
No, no, I didn't.不，不，我没有。
- "Death to Jo Powers."-“Jo Powers死”。
- That's just...-这只是…
It's a... a hashtag game, you know,它是一个..一个标签游戏，你知道的，
like "Death to..."像“死亡……”
You insert the name您插入的名称
of someone who's being an arsehole.一个人是被一个混蛋。
It's not... real. It's a joke thing.它不是…真正的。这是一个笑话。
And who started it? The hashtag?是谁开始的？标签？
I don't know. I don't know.我不知道。我不知道。
I saw it somewhere.我在某个地方看到它。
Excuse us a moment.请原谅我们一会儿。
Toxicology say the cake's clean.毒理学说蛋糕的清洁。
They also said:他们还说：
"Thanks, it was delicious."“谢谢，真好吃。”
We'll give her a caution.我们会给她一个警告。
Offensive Communications Act.进攻通信法。
- Does that cover cakes?-那是蛋糕吗？
- As far as she's concerned, it does.-就她而言，它确实。
What about the others who chipped in?什么样的人了？
Are you going to tell them off, too?你也要告诉他们吗？
- I didn't do anything.-我什么都没做。
- Start a thread about it.-开始一个线程。
Hospital's discharging the husband医院的丈夫
tomorrow.明天.
We'll bring him in for questioning.我们会带他来问问题。
Blue? We're arresting the husband.蓝色的吗？我们逮捕了丈夫。
Don't wallow in that.不要沉湎于那。
The Internet will be pissed off互联网会被气死的
with someone else today.与今天的其他人。
Tusk.图斯克。
Everyone's pissed off with Tusk每个人都讨厌的象牙
'cause of that thing with the kid.因为那个孩子的事。
He's catching a shit storm他在抓一个该死的风暴
on social media.论社会媒体。
- Liza will be organising the cake now.莉莎将举办了蛋糕。
- Yeah.-是的。
- See you tomorrow.明天见。
- See you.-见你。
__
- Whoo!-哇！
- ♪ Turn a penny to a grand ♪
♪ When I'm ready,
rocking steady for my fans ♪
Where my ladies at?我的女士们在哪里？
- Yo! Good show.- Yo！好节目。
- Yeah, that's a good show, brother.-是的，这是一个很好的表演，兄弟。
- I'm feeling my shit.-我感觉我的屎。
- You want some of that?-你想要一些吗？
- What you smoking?-你吸烟是什么？
- Good shit, boy.-好屎，男孩。
A'ight.好了。
Damn!该死!
Eyes on, eyes on, eyes on.眼睛，眼睛，眼睛。
Don't stress. It's legal here.不要强调。这里是合法的。
Pfft! Keep forgetting.呵！忘记了。
Welcome to Europe, I guess.欢迎来到欧洲，我想。
- Kinda takes the joy out of it.- Kinda从它的喜悦。
- Tell me about it.-告诉我关于它。
Careful! You break it, you pay for it.小心！你打破它，你为它付出。
Always doing some bullshit.总是做一些废话。
Tusk? Tusk?Tusk ?Tusk ?
Yo, yo! We need some help over here!哟，哟！我们这里需要一些帮助！
- I got you.-我得到了你。
- Get it out! Get it out! Get it out!-把它弄出来！把它拿出来！把它拿出来！
Call an ambulance!叫辆救护车。
Commencing.开始。
- Did he say what it is?-他说是什么了吗？
- Nope.-不。
- Good morning.-早上好。
- Morning.-早上好。
She's in here.她在这里。
So I go in,所以我走了进去，
and there's not just the wound而且不仅仅是伤口
from the glass.从玻璃。
There's a hole. Dug in.有一个洞。挖。
A bore hole, like a tiny tunnel.一个孔，像一个微小的隧道。
So I follow it, you know,所以我跟着它，你知道，
how deep does it go?它有多深？
It goes all the way from her ear canal它一路从她的耳道走去
to deep in her brain.在她的大脑深处。
Where I find this.我在哪里找到这个。
Nestled right in there. Looks quite cosy.坐落在那里。看起来很舒适。
- It's one of those bee things.-这是一个蜜蜂的东西。
- An ADI.- An ADI。
An Autonomous Drone Insect自主的无人机
from the Granular Project.从颗粒工程。
- How did it get in there?-它是怎么到那里的？
- I'd say it burrowed in.我想说，它在。
- Fuck me.-他妈的我。
- That's not the worst part.-这不是最坏的部分。
It crawled right through它爬了通过
her dorsal posterior insula,她背后岛，
which is basically这基本上是
the brain's pain centre.大脑疼痛中心。
You're talking agony off the scale.你说的是规模的痛苦。
- You'd do anything to make it stop.-你会做任何事情让它停止。
- Even cut your own throat.甚至割破你自己的喉咙。
- Good afternoon.下午好。
- DCI Parke.- DCI Parke。
- TDC Blue Colson.- TDC蓝科尔森。
- Okay. Thank you.-好的。谢谢您.
They're so fucking fancy-looking,他们是如此的他妈的看，
these companies.这些公司。
- Billions on branding.数十亿品牌。
- Well, they can afford it.-嗯，他们可以负担得起。
The whole ADI project's pretty much整个ADI项目差不多
bankrolled by the government.而政府。
It's why so many people这就是为什么这么多人
are paranoid about it.是偏执狂。
Let me guess,让我猜一猜。
this is some people on the Internet?这是一些人在网上吗？
They reckon the government他们估计政府
uses the bees to spy on us.用蜜蜂来监视我们。
There's a schizophrenic world view.有一种精神分裂的世界观。
Jesus, I didn't expect to find myselfJesus，我没想到会找到我自己
living in the future,生活在未来，
but here I fucking well am.但在这里我他妈的很好。
- Karin Parke?- Karin Parke？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
Vanessa Dahl.Vanessa Dahl。
Please. Follow me.拜托.跟着我.
You're after information你是在信息
on our Project Swarm ADIs?我们的项目群艾滋病？
That's right.这是正确的.
Any particular reason?有什么特别的原因吗？
Yes.对.
Rasmus.Rasmus。
Rasmus Sjoberg.Rasmus斯伯格。
- He heads Swarm.-他头群。
- Nice to meet you.-很高兴见到你。
- Hi.-嗨。
- Nice greenhouse.-漂亮的温室。
- Yeah.-是的。
So, your bees, your ADIs,所以，你的蜜蜂，你的艾滋病，
talk me through them.让我通过他们。
Colony Collapse Disorder.蜂群衰竭失调。
We still don't know what's behind it.我们仍然不知道它背后是什么。
Bees themselves were virtually extinct蜜蜂自己实际上已经灭绝了
so what our ADIs do所以我们的ADIs做的
is effectively stand in for them.是有效地支持他们。
They're solar powered.他们是太阳能供电。
They don't need nectar.他们不需要花蜜。
but they pollinate flowers the same way.但他们花授粉方式相同。
They crawl inside,他们在里面爬行，
pollen sticks to their legs花粉贴在他们的腿上
and gets brushed off并被刷掉
the next flower they visit.他们访问的下一朵鲜花。
- Can they make honey?-他们会做蜂蜜吗？
- Uh... No.-嗯…不.
I was joking.我在开玩笑。
How do they know他们怎么知道
where the flowers even are? I mean...哪里的花呢？我的意思是…
Well, they have a sensor.嗯，他们有一个传感器。
Like a... camera?就像..相机吗？
No. Just a basic visual sensor.不，只是一个基本的视觉传感器。
You see,你看，
they need rudimentary pattern recognition他们需要基本的模式识别
in order to locate compatible flora为了定位兼容的植物区系
and navigate.和导航。
- They navigate?- 他们>导航？
- Yes.-是的。
You don't... I don't know... steer them?你不这样做。我不知道。引导他们？
They're autonomous.他们是自治的。
That's right, isn't it?是的，不是吗？
They make their own decisions.他们做出自己的决定。
They look after themselves.他们照顾自己。
Yes. You see, the ADIs对.你看，ADIs
cover the whole of the UK.覆盖整个英国。
We couldn't command each one我们不能命令每一个
individually ourselves.单独的自己。
It's just not logistically possible.这不是逻辑上可能的。
No. We simply不，我们只是
set the behaviour and leave them to it.设置的行为，并把他们。
They even construct these hives他们甚至建造这些蜂箱
themselves.自己。
They reproduce...它们的繁殖…
- They reproduce?-他们繁殖？
- Yes. Each hive is a replication point.-是的。每一个蜂巢都是一个复制点。
- It's like a 3D printer, basically.-它就像一个3D打印机，基本上。
- Exactly.-完全。
They create duplicates of themselves,他们创造自己的重复，
create more hives创造更多的蜂巢
and spread out exponentially.并扩散指数。
- Cover the country.-覆盖全国。
- Maybe you should work here.也许你应该在这里工作。
Yeah, well, I read up on it.是的，嗯，我读了它。
It's impressive.这是令人印象深刻的。
It is. It's just a shame it's necessary.它是.这只是一个耻辱，这是必要的。
The alternative would have been另一选择是
environmental catastrophe.环境灾难。
Bees were dying out.蜜蜂消失了。
So, what is it that brings you here?那么，是什么把你带到这里？
We think one of your ADIs我们认为你的ADI
may be involved in an unexplained death.可能参与一个不明原因的死亡。
Sorry? A death?对不起？死亡？
Uh-huh.嗯。
Thank you.谢谢您.
Yeah. It's one of ours.是啊.它是我们的一个。
But, look, these are not designed to...但是，看，这些都不是设计的…
Kill people? I'd hope not.杀了人？我希望没有。
Could it have malfunctioned somehow?它有可能失灵了吗？
No. I mean, when they do malfunction...不，我的意思是，当他们出现故障时…
It happens, but then they just break,它发生了，但他们只是打破，
they just hit the ground.他们刚刚撞到地面。
What if someone hacked one and then如果有人攻击了一个又一个
they found a way of controlling it?他们找到了一种控制它的方法吗？
That's impossible.这是不可能的。
You see,你看，
it's got military-grade encryption,有军事级加密，
and you would need a diagnostic你需要一个诊断
controller, which is also encrypted.控制器，这也是加密的。
So I would say the likelihood is...所以我会说的可能性是…
I don't know what he's saying,我不知道他在说什么，
but it's not the same as "impossible."但它不一样的“不可能”。
This is every hive we have online.这是我们在网络上的每一个蜂巢。
See...看到…
These are the hives in the building here.这些都是在这里建造的蜂房。
- How many bees per hive?-每只蜜蜂有多少只蜜蜂？
- Around 4,000.-约4000。
- It's like air traffic control.-这就像空中交通管制。
- Yeah.-是的。
Is that the search input?是搜索输入吗？
- Yeah, but, uh... you'd need...-是的，但是，呃…你需要…
- Sorry.-对不起。
Jo Powers' postcode.Jo Powers邮编。
Is that who this is about?这是谁的？
- You said you get some malfunctions?-你说你有故障？
- A fair few, yes.-一个公平的少数，是的。
They smack into a car or something.他们打到一辆车或什么的。
We even had people trap them.我们甚至有人困住他们。
You know, put them in the microwave你知道，把它们放在微波炉里
for YouTube videos.YouTube视频。
And this logs这日志
any that drop off the system?任何一滴水系统吗？
Logs everything, yes.记录一切，是的。
Did you lose any around here你在这附近丢了吗
on Monday evening?星期一晚上？
Well, I can check.嗯，我可以检查。
Just one. Went out at 1903 hours.只有一个。在1903小时内外出。
Here, I can replay.在这里，我可以重播。
There.那里。
- That's odd.-这很奇怪。
- What's odd?-什么奇怪？
When they pass between hives,当他们通过之间的蜂巢，
they switch from one jurisdiction他们切换从一个司法管辖区
to another.另一个。
- It's, you know, like a...-这是，你知道，像一个..
- It's like a phone between cell masts?这就像细胞桅杆之间的电话吗？
Exactly. It tried to do that,确切地.它试图这样做，
but there was nothing to switch to.但没有什么可以切换到。
Unless someone spoofed a hive and then除非有人伪造了蜂房，然后
they've used that to commandeer your ADI.他们用，要征用你的阿迪。
No, you would need不，你需要
a diagnostic controller to do that.一个诊断控制器来做。
What's the range on one of those?其中的一个范围是什么？
Ten, 20 metres, perhaps.20，十米，也许。
So whoever was controlling it would have因此，无论是谁控制了它都会有
to be no more than 20 metres away.不超过20米远。
- Outside the house.-在房子外面。
- Yeah. Sitting in a car, even.-是的。坐在车里，甚至。
- Can you trace back who did this?-你能追溯到这是谁干的吗？
- Yes. I-I'm already trying to do that.-是的。我已经在努力这样做。
Uh...休斯敦大学...
You know what? Uh...你知道什么？休斯敦大学...
It would be easier without an audience.没有观众会更容易。
Okay.可以.
You two swap numbers,你两个交换号码，
keep a line of communication.保持沟通的路线。
Can you shut the whole thing down你能把整个事情都关了吗
if need be... hypothetically speaking?如果需要…说不定呢？
Even a short stoppage即使是一个短暂的停顿
would damage the ecosystem,会破坏生态系统，
and we'd need approval我们需要批准
from the Department of the Environment.从环境部。
We'll need a list of any Granular staff我们需要一个任何颗粒的工作人员的名单
that had access to that system,那有访问该系统，
past or present.过去或现在。
Some were government employees.一些是政府雇员。
Use a different font for those使用不同的字体
if it helps.如果它有帮助。
Bye.再见.
Nick, that's a setNick，那是一套
of Granular personnel records.粒状人员记录。
Root out anyone interesting.根除任何有趣的人。
Maybe not just one.也许不只是一个。
Could be a group involved.可能是一个团队参与。
Technically we should refer this up从技术上说，我们应该把这个
to the NCA,在国家版权局，
but there's no fucking way但没有他妈的方式
they're taking this off me.他们把我的这个。
The NCA already knows about it.国家版权局已经知道它。
What?什么？
DCI Karin Parke?DCI Karin Parke？
- Yes.-是的。
- Shaun Li, National Crime Agency.Shaun Li，国家犯罪局。
How come you're here?你怎么来的？
There's been more than one.有不止一个。
This is Tusk, last night.这是塔斯克，昨晚。
- Shit.-该死。
- They thought it was a fit.-他们认为这是一个合适的。
Took him to the hospital.带他去医院。
He had to be anaesthetised他被麻醉了
to stop him mutilating himself.为了阻止他伤害自己。
X-ray seemed to indicate some kindX射线似乎表明某种形式
of plaque or tumour in his brain在他大脑中的斑块或肿瘤
so they popped him in the MRI.所以他们在核磁共振成像中出现了他。
Yeah. Basically one big magnet.是啊.基本上有一个大磁铁。
Tore it right out of his head,它从他的头上撕下，
through the eye socket.通过眼睛插座。
Battered the ADI too.破旧的ADI太。
Yours is more intact你的更完整
so I'm gonna need it for analysis.所以我需要它来分析。
It's evidence.它的证据。
Two's a pattern. It knocks二是一种模式。它把
any malfunction theory in the head.头上的任何故障理论。
- And they're similar victims.-他们是相似的受害者。
- Similar?相似吗？
Both in the middle of online shit storms.无论是在网络上的屎风暴。
Well, if you wanna kill someone,好吧，如果你想杀了人，
there's a million easier ways to do it.有一百万种更简单的方法来做。
Pull this off and you've done it把这个拉下来，你已经做了
from across the street.从街对面。
No fingerprints, no DNA.没有指纹，没有DNA。
It's like wishing them dead.就像是希望他们死了一样。
Fuck.性交.
Guys? Come here.的人吗？来这里。
Okay, so, um... Jo Powers and Tusk,好吧，那么，嗯…Jo Powers和图斯克，
both were being kicked around两人都被踢了
the Internet for hours,互联网几个小时，
but in both their cases,但在他们的情况下，
people were also tweeting their photos人也在他们的照片
accompanied with this hashtag: #DeathTo.伴随着这个标签：#去死。
- Like our friend the teacher.-像我们的朋友老师。
- Right.-对。
She didn't know where she'd first heard她不知道她第一次听到的是哪里
of it, but trace it back,它，但追溯它，
and it looks like the first real use它看起来像第一个真正的使用
of the hashtag was last weekend.该标签是在上周末。
- By who?-由谁？
- Uh...-嗯…
Looks like, um...看起来像，嗯…
Looks like identical tweets看起来像是相同的鸣叫
from a set of duplicate bot accounts.从一组重复的僵尸账户。
Um...嗯...
Automated. It's like spam.自动化。这就像垃圾邮件。
This is someone trying to seed the tag,这是有人试图种子的标签，
you know? Get it out there.你知道吗？把它在那里。
It's like bait. This is someone这就像是诱饵。这是一个人
wanting people to pick up on it.想要人们拿起它。
Check out the senders' avatar photos.查看发件人的头像照片。
Bees. Shit.蜜蜂.倒霉.
Okay.可以.
There's more.还有更多。
So each tweet had a sort of所以每一条微博都有一种
instruction video attached to it.连接到它的指令视频。
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
- There.-有。
"Game of Consequences"?“后果游戏”？
It's like an unpopularity contest.这就像一个不受欢迎的竞赛。
Pick someone you don't like and if enough选择一个你不喜欢的人，如果不够的话
other people choose the same name,其他人选择相同的名称，
then that's who gets targeted.然后，这是谁得到的目标。
Here, watch.这里，看。
Game of Consequences.游戏的后果。
- One: Pick a target.- 一：选择一个目标。
- Oh, my God.-哦，我的上帝。
Two: Post their name and photo二：张贴他们的名字和照片
with #DeathTo.与#死亡。
No.不.
Three: Most popular target三：最受欢迎的目标
will be eliminated after 5 p.m. each day.将被淘汰后，每天晚上5点。
Four: Game resets at midnight.四：游戏将在午夜。
- Oh, no.哦，不。
- Fuck.-他妈的。
Someone's holding a public ballot,有人持有公众选票，
bumping off the top person.撞上顶层的人。
- Jesus, it's just mad.- Jesus，这是疯了。
- Yeah, and it's growing.-是的，它的成长。
Day one. 63 people used the hashtag一天一个。63人使用的标签
on Jo Powers, okay?Jo Powers，好吗？
On day two, 223 used it on Tusk.第二天，223用它的象牙。
- Who's using it now?-现在是谁在使用它？
- There's... There's loads more people.-有..有更多的人。
There's quite a few votes有相当多的选票
for the Chancellor.为财政大臣。
- Yeah.-是的。
- Um...-嗯…
But at number one...但在第一号…
is 880 people using it是880人使用它
on someone called Clara Meades.在一个叫Clara Meades的。
- Who's she?她是谁？
- Clara Meades.- Clara Meades。
Okay, um...好的，嗯…
it looks like she was at a demo,它看起来像她在一个演示，
and she took a selfie她拍了一张自拍照
in front of a war memorial.在战争纪念碑前。
- Pretending to piss on it.•假装小便对它。
- Nice work, Clara.-很好的工作，克拉拉。
Yeah, it's getting near the end是的，它接近结束
of the vote,投票的，
and her mentions are blowing up.和她提到的是吹起来。
- Tusk isn't public knowledge yet?塔斯克不是公共知识吗？
- Um, no.-嗯，没有。
So people can't know the hashtag works.所以人们不知道标签的作品。
They're using it to scare her.他们用它来吓唬她。
- Yeah, but they're gonna get her killed.-是的，但他们会让她杀了。
- We need to get to her before five.-我们需要在五之前到达她。
Yeah. Pulling her citizens details.是啊.拉她的公民细节。
You're not supposed你不应该
to have access to that.要有这样的。
Yeah, I know. Just getting her location.是的，我知道。只是让她的位置。
There.那里。
__
Hello?你好吗？
Yeah, she is.是的，她是。
All right, all right, hold on.好吧，好吧，坚持住。
Clara!克拉拉！
Police. For you.警方.为你.
How did they get my number?他们是怎么得到我的号码的？
- Hello?-你好吗？
- Clara Meades?- Clara Meades？
This is DCI Karin Parke, Met Police.这是DCI Karin Parke，遇到警察。
Sorry to track you down like this,对不起，跟踪你这样，
but we think you may be in danger.但我们认为你可能处于危险之中。
Sorry, is this a joke? Because对不起，这是一个笑话吗？因为
all this stuff I'm getting is not funny.所有这些东西我得到的是不好笑。
I'm not joking.我不是在开玩笑。
Stay where you are until we get there.呆在你的地方，直到我们到达那里。
And keep your windows closed.并保持你的窗户关闭。
I'm setting up a perimeter.我在设置一个周长。
Call Rasmus, we need him across this.叫Rasmus，我们需要他在这。
- Rasmus?- Rasmus？
- Hi, Blue.- 嗨，蓝。
I'm sending you a postcode and my GPS.我送你一个邮编和我的GPS。
I need you to monitor the area.我需要你来监控这个地区。
Track my location and see if you get跟踪我的位置，看看你是否得到
anything unusual, any rogue ADIs, yeah?任何不寻常的东西，任何流氓ADIs，是吗？
Yeah, great, good.是的，伟大的，好的。
Look, if they come back,看，如果他们回来，
I think I can catch them.我想我能抓住他们。
I have basically set a trap.“我基本上设置了一个陷阱。”
So if they...所以如果他们…
if they try it again, we've got them.如果他们再试一次，我们已经得到了他们。
- Are you Batman?-你是蝙蝠侠吗？
- They only just rolled them out.-他们只是把他们滚出去。
This'll turn every red light这将打开每一个红色的光
between here and there to green.在这里和那里之间的绿色。
Fuck me. If this is the NCA life,他妈的我。如果这是NCA的生活，
I should apply for a transfer.我应该申请一个转会。
Let's go.走吧.
__
We can take her here.我们可以带她来这里。
It's a safe house这是一个安全的房子
for terrorist informers usually.恐怖分子的告密者通常。
No target sighted.没有目标瞄准。
This is a police operation!这是一个警察的行动！
Everybody vacate their premises now.大家腾出自己的处所了。
Please leave...请离开……
- What's that?-那是什么？
- Someone's trying to break in.-有人试图打破。
- Rasmus?- Rasmus？
- I just picked up an attempted breach.-我只是拿起一个企图违反。
Granular, they've got a breach.颗粒，他们有一个缺口。
- One ADI just went offline.- 一阿迪只是脱机。
- Where?-在哪里？
- 800 metres from your location.从你的位置- 800米。
- That's outside our cordon.那是在我们的警戒线。
If someone's trying to pilot it this way,如果有人试图以这种方式试验，
they're gonna turn 'round他们要转一转
the moment they see all these uniforms.当他们看到所有这些制服的时候。
Clara Meades? I'm Karin Parke.Clara Meades？我是Karin Parke。
Did you pack a bag?你包了一个包吗？
- Yeah, it's by the door.-是的，它在门上。
- Right, let's go.-对，让我们走吧。
- Rasmus got a track on them?- Rasmus他们有跑道吗？
- Not yet.-还没有。
__
It's just precautionary,只是预防，
and it's only for one night.它只为一个夜晚。
Just gotta call in.只是要打电话。
Hi.你好.
No, not yet.没有，还不习惯。
Hopefully never. Granular are onto it.希望永远。颗粒是到它。
Understood.理解.
They housed a witness here for a while,他们在这里住了一段时间，
Shaun said.肖恩说。
- Must've had kids.-一定有孩子。
- Have you got kids?-你有孩子了吗？
No.不.
No plans.没有计划。
Up the stairs.上楼梯。
- Rasmus.- Rasmus。
- Still nothing. I can't trace it.- 仍然什么都没有。我不能跟踪它。
At least there's an en-suite.至少有一个套间。
- Is there nothing?-什么都没有吗？
- No. -不。
Whoever it is,无论它是谁的，
they've masked their path well.他们已经掩盖了他们的道路。
But that's not...但这不是…
- Fuck.-他妈的。
- What? -什么？
- We just lost a whole hive.-我们刚刚失去了一个完整的蜂巢。
- What does that mean?-这是什么意思？
Packed full of ADIs.挤满了艾滋病。
Lost them all too.失去了他们都太。
- No... Rasmus?-不..拉斯木斯？
- There's thousands of them.-有成千上万的人。
- Where?-在哪里？
- It's close to your location.-它接近你的位置。
Rasmus, say that again.Rasmus，再说一遍。
Blue? Blue. It's close...蓝色的吗？蓝色。它是关闭的…
It's very close to you.它离你很近。
- Text it. Text it to me.-文本。文本它给我。
- Rasmus. Text it to... Shit.- Rasmus。文本它…倒霉.
Do I get to redecorate?我要重新装修？
Hello. Hello.你好.你好.
No...不...
They've got the whole thing.他们得到了整件事。
We're not in control anymore.我们不再控制了。
- They've got the whole thing.-他们得到了整个事情。
- What are you doing?-你在干什么？
- Fix it! Can't you fix it?-修复它！你不能修理它吗？
- Shut up!-闭嘴！
__
Shit.倒霉.
We need to go. Now. Now! Come on!我们需要去。现在.现在!来吧！
Go. Go, go, go.去。去，去，去。
What's... what's happening?什么..发生什么事了？
Karin...卡琳…
In there! Go!在那里！去！
- Help me block the gap!帮助我阻止我的差距！
- Tell me what's going on!-告诉我发生了什么事！
You're scaring the shit out of me!你吓死我了！
Oh! Fuck!哦!性交!
The fan! The fan!风扇！风扇！
Get it away from me!把它从我身边拿走！
Take your time.慢慢来.
I'd seen so many bodies before.我以前见过这么多的尸体。
At crime scenes, in autopsies.在犯罪现场，在解剖。
But I'd never seen anyone die.但我从来没有见过任何人死。
And she was right there.她就在那里。
And can you describe the reaction你能描述一下反应吗
of your colleague, Miss Colson?你的同事，Colson小姐？
Blue took it hard.蓝色的它很难。
Uh-huh.嗯。
I'll shut it down.我会把它关闭。
We thought this was one guy,我们以为这是一个家伙，
some Mr. Mystery in the vicinity,一些Mystery先生在附近，
hijacking one ADI劫持一个ADI
and personally controlling it.并亲自控制它。
But there were thousands of them.但有成千上万的人。
- So it can't be that, right?-所以它不能是，对吗？
- No.-不。
- One person can't fly hundreds at once.-一个人不能一次飞上几百个。
Whoever this is,这是谁的，
they're controlling the whole system.他们控制着整个系统。
- Do you know where from?-你知道从哪里来的吗？
- Could be anywhere.-可能在任何地方。
You need to fucking sort this out!你需要他妈的解决这个问题！
How do the ADIs know who to target?如何做和知道是谁的目标？
Could've found Clara the same way可能已经找到了克拉拉同样的方式
you did, the identity database?你做过的，身份数据库？
No. That just gives you the basic area.不，只是给你基本的领域。
We were in the room too,我们也在房间里，
and they only went for her.他们只为她。
Facial recognition.面部识别。
It's got to be facial recognition.它必须是面部识别。
Which means the feed from their visual这意味着从他们的视觉的饲料
sensors, that's been accessed too.传感器，也被访问过。
- That's not possible.-这是不可能的。
- It's the only explanation.-这是唯一的解释。
Now look, the visual feed is secure现在看，视觉饲料是安全的
between each ADI and the hive.每个ADI和蜂巢之间。
- There you go.-你去了。
- Although...虽然…
one of the government's conditions政府的条件之一
for backing the project...为支持该项目…
Okay. Enough.可以.足够的。
We had to consent to permitting我们必须同意允许
government security services政府的安全服务
access to the visual feed at times有时访问视觉进给
of quote, "increased national security."的报价，“增加国家安全。”
Which is, as I understand it,这是，因为我明白，
pretty much all the time.几乎所有的时间。
- I wasn't happy about it.-我不高兴。
- Your lot went along with it.-你的命运和它一起。
That implies a greater range这意味着一个更大的范围
of options than your lot presented.比你提出的期权。
- So they are spying on us.-所以他们是监视我们。
- This is all classified.-这是所有分类。
So what did you do, did you put in那么你做了什么，你穿上了吗
a back door and route it through GCHQ?后门和路由通过GCHQ？
I mean, you do CCTV, you do traffic cams.我的意思是，你做中央电视台，你做交通凸轮。
So what don't you have所以你没有
your fucking noses in?你他妈的鼻子？
Look, millions of those things看，数以百万计的那些东西
flying around, propping up the ecosystem?绕飞，支撑生态系统？
Well, that's great, save the planet,嗯，这是伟大的，拯救地球，
hallelujah!哈利路亚！
Government's not going政府不去
to pump billions into it向它注入数十亿美元
just 'cause some lab coat says so,只是'导致一些实验室外套说，所以，
and it grabs 200 green votes.它抓住了200个绿色的选票。
They saw an opportunity to get more,他们看到了一个获得更多的机会，
they took it.他们拿走了。
Total nationwide surveillance.全国性监测。
We tracked suspects for weeks我们跟踪了几个星期的嫌疑犯
in ways they couldn't dream of.在他们不能梦想的方式。
- We prevented bombings, mass shootings.-我们阻止爆炸，大规模枪击。
- By spying on the public.-通过监视公众。
And keeping them safe,并保持他们的安全，
which is what they want.这是他们想要的。
Clara Meades isn't safe, though,Clara Meades不安全，虽然，
is she, Shaun?是她吗，肖恩？
Knowing what you knew,知道你知道什么，
that might've helped us,这可能帮助了我们，
but no,但没有，
you kept your little fucking secret.你保持你的小秘密。
Okay! The government's a cunt.可以!政府是一个荡妇。
We knew that already.我们已经知道了。
Word's going to get out about Clara.关于克拉拉的话。
The public's going to wake up and find公众会醒来，发现
this mental assassination game going on,这种精神暗杀游戏继续下去，
and soon we're going to have another body.很快我们将有另一个身体。
- So what do we do?-那么我们做什么？
- I don't know.-我不知道。
We're totally locked out. Totally blind.我们完全被锁在外面。完全瞎了。
If I can work out how they got in,如果我能算出他们是怎么得到的，
I might be able to reverse engineer我可能会逆向工程师
some means of getting control back.一些控制回来的手段。
Do the ADIs have a command log,做ADIs已经命令日志，
on-board cache?板载缓存？
- Yeah, but that's encrypted.-是的，但这是加密的。
- I'll need the key to that.-我需要的关键。
Been through the employee files,已通过员工档案，
found some POIs.发现了一些景点。
Bring them in.把他们带。
Are you sitting in on these?你坐在这些上吗？
Granular interviews?颗粒的采访？
I've got to be somewhere.我必须在某处。
It's 7:15.是7:15。
Three deaths have now been linked现在已经有三人死亡了
to a hashtag circulating on social media.一个标签在社交媒体上流传。
Controversial journalist Jo Powers...有争议的记者Jo Powers……
Good morning.<我早上好。
Have you posted the hashtag?你贴的标签？
Is it real or an urban myth?是它是真的还是一个城市的神话？
Well, thousands have been taking part,嗯，成千上万的人参加了，
but how culpable are they?但他们有罪呢？
People are dying,人们都快死了，<
and we want to hear your thoughts.和 >我们> 想听听你的想法。
Line seven, Liana...七线、Liana…
This is real, this is happening...这是真实的，这是发生……
I am happy to see her die.我很高兴看到她死了。
It's not the hashtag killing them.不是标签杀死他们。
That's just a game.这只是一个游戏。
Like, if you're an arsehole,一样，如果你是一个混蛋，
you deserve to be shamed.你应该感到惭愧。
Steve, line five.史提夫，行五。
Yeah, but my point is,是的，但我的观点是，
someone's gotta be top of the list, yeah?有人必须是名单的顶部，是吗？
So why not make it someone,为什么不让它成为一个人，
you know, who deserves it, like a racist.你知道，谁配得上它，就像一个种族主义者。
With the hashtag, I've seen与标签，我看到
celebrities, politicians, everyone.名人，政治家，每个人。
This doesn't mean you have to sit there这并不意味着你必须坐在那里
encouraging people to take part.鼓励人们去参加。
The point is this is already happening.这一点是已经发生了。
And people know that they can jump onboard和人们都知道他们可以在船上跳下去>
because nobody will ever know因为没有人会知道
if they did or didn't.如果他们做了或没有。
Well, let's just pause for a moment好吧，让我们暂时停一下吧
and go back to that top five.回到那个前五名。
As we have been saying,正如我们一直在说的，
the Chancellor is at number one,财政大臣在第一号，
and I want us to think about that.“我想让我们去想一想。”
What does that tell us告诉我们什么
about the choice of the nation?关于国家的选择？
Well, I can't say I'm surprised，我不能说我很惊讶
that he's number one on the list.他在名单上的第一号。
He's been pretty unpopular他很不受欢迎
for quite a long time now.有相当长的一段时间了。
But does that warrant但这是值得的
his place on this list?他在这个名单上的位置？
I'm saying people我在说人
don't have to think too hard about it.不要想太难了，
Now that's he's number one,
that should generate more discussions这应该产生更多的讨论
and probably more votes.可能更多的选票。
__
Thanks for your time.感谢你的时间。
- No good?-不好？
- No good.-不好。
- Well, that's all fascinating...-嗯，这都是迷人的…
- Shaun.-肖恩。
- But when do we shut it down?-但我们什么时候关闭它？
- Tom.-汤姆。
Forgive me for being sceptical原谅我怀疑
about your agency's basic competence.关于你的代理的基本能力。
- Tom.-汤姆。
- I'm on the fucking chopping block here.-我在他妈的砍块。
Number one on the list.名单上的第一号。
The people's fucking choice!人们的他妈的选择！
Farrington's number four,Farrington的四号，
and he's a paedophile.他是个恋童癖。
- Suspected paedophile.疑似恋童癖。
- He did it. You know he did.-他做了。你知道他做了。
Let's just shut it down. All social media.让我们把它关闭。全社会媒体。
The whole bloody Internet, pull the plug.整个血腥的互联网，拉插头。
Just for today,只为今天，
at least until Thumbelina here至少在Thumbelina这里
pulls his finger out拉他的手指
and he actually catches someone.他实际上抓住了一个人。
I wouldn't advise shutting things down.我不会建议关闭东西。
- But it's possible? We can do that?-但这是可能的？我们可以这样做吗？
- The whole of social media?-整个社会媒体？
- Yeah. Pull a North Korea on it.-是的。拉上一个朝鲜。
- Well, yes, technically.-嗯，是的，在技术上。
- Right, so push the off switch.-对，所以按下关闭开关。
- That's not a good idea.-这不是一个好主意。
- No?-没有？
- Not in my opinion.-不是在我看来。
Right, okay. It's just that speaking好的，好的。这只是说
as a marked man, I beg to fucking differ.作为一个显着的男人，我乞求他妈的不同。
If we shut it down,如果我们把它关闭，
you'll still be number one.你仍然是第一号。
Guaranteed to be, in fact.保证是，事实上。
He's right. If we let it run on,他是对的。如果我们让它运行，
at least there's a few hours.至少有几个小时。
Anything could happen before five o'clock.任何事情都可能在五点之前发生。
The vote might change.投票可能会改变。
Yeah, and it might not.是的，它可能不会。
What about that report? The archive job?那份报告呢？档案工作？
From 1985, that memo about Farrington?1985、备忘录的有关Farrington的情况吗？
- That was over an unrelated matter.-这是一件不相关的事。
- Leak it.-泄漏。
Tom, that would be a smear.汤姆，那将是一片。
A head-to-toe shit smear,一个从头到脚的屎涂片，
I fucking hope so.我他妈的希望如此。
He's in his 80s. He's had his life.他80多岁了，他有了自己的生活。
Fuck him under the bus.在公共汽车上他妈的。
If I could suggest an alternative?如果我能提出另一种选择？
We move you to a safe location.我们将你转移到一个安全的地方。
- Have you secured before five.-你有没有固定在五之前。
- Worked out well for you last night.昨晚你为你工作得很好。
I'll show you.我指给你看。
This next one's Tess Wallender.下一个是Tess Wallender。
She was a junior.她是一个初级。
So not much所以不多
in the way of technical skills.在技术技能的方式。
- Quit Granular for personal reasons.-因个人原因而放弃。
- Nervous exhaustion, yeah.-紧张疲惫，是的。
Worked in Human Resources在人力资源部工作
for Granular until she quit.直到她戒了。
She took a photo of a guy on the Tube,她在管上拍了一个男人的照片，
said he'd harassed her,说他会骚扰她，
lewd comments or something.好色的评论或什么的。
Turned out he had a learning disability原来他有一个学习障碍
so she caught a ton of shit on...所以她抓住了一吨的屎…
On social media.论社会媒体。
- Hello. I'm DCI Karin Parke.-你好。我是DCI Karin Parke。
- Hi.-嗨。
__
It was like having a whole weather system这就像有一个全天候系统
turn against me.背叛我。
Just hate message after hate message,恨消息后才恨消息，
around the clock, all piling on.在时钟周围，所有的打桩。
It's hard to describe what that does很难描述这是什么
to your head.到你的头。
Suddenly
there's a million invisible people,有一百万个看不见的人，
all talking about how they despise you.都在谈论他们是如何鄙视你。
It's like a mental illness.这就像一个精神疾病。
Fuck.性交.
What?什么？
Shit.倒霉.
I mean, hands up, I made a mistake,我的意思是，举起手来，我犯了一个错误，
but the way people enjoyed kicking me,但人们喜欢踢我的方式，
that's what got to me.那是我的东西。
The casual fun they had and, um...他们有和，嗯休闲的乐趣…
I just felt I couldn't go on.我只是觉得我不能继续。
Who found you?谁找到你的？
Um... Garrett, my flatmate.嗯...加勒特，我的室友。
He found me in the bath他在浴室里找到我
five minutes after I'd slashed them.我砍了他们五分钟后。
I mean, it's crazy.我的意思是，它是疯狂的。
I'm half-conscious.我是半意识。
He's dragging me out of the bath,他把我从浴室中拖出来，
and I'm telling him to get out,我告诉他要出去，
saying, "I'm naked."说，“我是裸体的。”
He tied towels 'round my wrists,他把毛巾围在我的手腕上，
kept me conscious,保持我意识，
kept stroking my hair不停地抚摸着我的头发
till the ambulance arrived, talking to me.直到救护车到了，和我说话。
Sort of weird.奇怪的排序。
I think he always had a thing for me.我想他总是为我有一件事。
And we worked at the same place so,我们在同一个地方工作，
you know... awkward.你知道的...尴尬。
- He worked at Granular?-他工作在颗粒？
- Yeah. On the ADI thing.-是的。在阿迪的事。
- He was a real wunderkind. Ultra-smart.他是一个真正的神童。超智能。
- What did you say his name was?-你说他的名字是什么？
Garrett. Garrett Scholes.加勒特。Garrett Scholes。
Garrett Scholes.Garrett Scholes。
We need the whereabouts of a Garrett...我们需要一个加勒特的下落…
Scholes. We were about to tell you.斯科尔斯。我们正要告诉你。
It was buried in the on-board memory它被埋葬在板上的记忆里
of the Jo Powers' ADI.在乔大国ADI。
- What was?-什么是？
- A manifesto. A 98-page manifesto.-宣言。一个98页的宣言。
__
And check this out.并检查这个。
There's fucking selfies in it.有他妈的自拍吧。
So we're good to go?是的，所以我们很好去？
Okay, that's the charge in place.好的，这是收费的地方。
Okay. Pull back.可以.拉回来。
We're all set here.我们都在这里集合。
Detonate.引爆。
So, the plan is,因此，该计划是，
we move you to an underground bunker,我们把你移到一个地下的地下，
knock out every hive打掉每一个蜂巢
within a ten-mile radius.在一一零英里半径范围内。
And, what, just leave me there?什么，只留下我在那里？
How long for?多久？
It's a temporary measure.这是一个临时措施。
How long till you take out all the hives?多久，直到你把所有麻疹？
There's 20,000, 30,000 of them.有20000个，30000个。
That would take two years.这需要两年时间。
Two years, a victim a day.两年，一天一个受害者。
More to the point,更多的点，
the environmental impact would...环境影响会…
Fuck that.他妈的。
Shit!！
- What?-什么？
- Fuck!-他妈的！
Stay back, stay back!呆在后面，呆在后面！
Get back!“我回来了”！
Go, go, go! Get away!去，去，去！逃掉!
For fuck's sake, move!看在他妈的份上，移动！
What's your Plan B?你的B计划是什么？
He was on the original employee roster,他在原来的员工名册上，
but we discounted him.但我们给他打了折扣。
He left the country six months ago.他六个月前离开了这个国家。
We thought we were looking我们以为我们在寻找
for someone nearby.附近有人。
Run a full trace on him.在他身上运行一个完整的痕迹。
Everything we can find.我们所能找到的一切。
Lunatic with production values,有生产价值的疯子，
that's the worst kind.这是最坏的一种。
"Thanks to the technological revolution,“多亏了技术革命，
we have the power to rage and accuse,我们有愤怒和指责的力量，
spout bile without consequence.无结果胆汁。
Only by being forced to recognize只有被强迫承认
the power technology grants us,电力技术使我们，
to acknowledge承认
individual responsibility..."个人责任……”
Is it all like this?这一切都是这样吗？
He likens the population to insects,他把人口的昆虫，
says we revel in cruelty,说我们陶醉在残酷，
that it's a weakness这是一个弱点
that should be bred out of us.我们应该从我们的。
Recurrent theme is he wants people to face经常性的主题是他想让人们面对
the consequences of what they say and do.他们说的和做的后果。
- Wants to force that on them.-想迫使他们。
- The whole thing's a moral lesson?-整件事都是一堂道德课？
He wanted us to find this他想让我们找到这个
and spread it about.并传播它。
Well, fuck him.好吧，他妈的他。
__
Fuck.性交.
Shit.倒霉.
Karin. Karin. He's messed up.卡琳。卡琳。他搞砸了。
He's put this document他把这个文件
together himself, right?自己在一起，对吗？
His author name's in the metadata.他的作者名字在元数据中。
But he stripped out everything else,但他剥夺了一切，
so we don't know when he's written it,所以我们不知道他什么时候写的，
for example.例如.
Mm-hmm.嗯嗯。
Most of the photos are clipart大部分照片是剪贴画
off the Internet, except this one.关闭互联网，除了这一个。
- The selfie.-自拍。
- That's where he's screwed up.-这是他搞砸的地方。
He's taken it with his phone,他拿了它的电话，
and the phone left a geotag on the image.和电话留下一个标记图像。
- So you know where he took this?-你知道他把这个带到哪里去了吗？
- I know precisely where.-我知道确切的地方。
He's here and Granular HQ is there.他在这里，颗粒总部在那里。
__
- Armed police! Stay down!武装警察！蹲下!
- Armed police!武装警察！
Armed police! Stay where you are!武装警察！呆在你所在的地方！
Armed police! Show yourselves!武装警察！表明自己！
Move!移动！
Left.左。
- Clear!-清晰！
Clear!明确！
Lifestyles of the rich and famous.富人和名人的生活方式。
There. The forge.那里。锻造。
Nice one.很好的一个。
Half the drives I sifted in forensics一半的硬盘被我在取证
had scorch marks on 'em.有烧焦的痕迹在他们。
- What do you think?-你怎么看？
- Yeah. Looks like his toolkit.-是的。看起来像他的工具包。
- You can use it?-你可以用它吗？
- Pretty much the key to the door.-几乎到了门的钥匙。
So you can get control back?那么你可以得到控制回来？
Send the deactivation?发送失活？
Well, I've got his source code.嗯，我有他的源代码。
- I should be able to bounce him out.-我应该能让他出去。
- Be quick.-快。
Key to the door?门的钥匙？
Our guy doesn't seem the type我们的人似乎不太类型
to leave keys lying around.离开钥匙躺在周围。
Well, I'm in.嗯，我在。
Okay. Deactivate her.可以.使她。
- Yeah, I need to repair permissions.-是的，我需要修复权限。
- Fucking hell.-他妈的地狱。
That's weird.这很奇怪。
What's weird?什么奇怪？
- Time's ticking.时间的滴答声。
- That file. Wasn't there before.-该文件。以前不在那里。
- This file?-这个文件？
- Yeah.-是的。
What is it?这是怎么一回事？
- Blue?蓝色的吗？
- I think they're IMEI numbers.我认为他们的IMEI号码。
What does that mean?那是什么意思？
Every phone, every device每一个电话，每一个设备
has a unique number, an IMEI number.有一个独一无二的号码，一个IMEI号码。
It tethers it to a unique user.它将是一个独特的用户。
- Yeah.-是的。
- But I can check, just... reverse lookup.-但我可以检查，只是…反向查找。
Take it easy.别紧张.
Who are these people?这些人是谁？
I don't know.我不知道。
There's 387,000 of them.他们有387000个。
Are these IDs这些ID
your spooks have been collecting?你的幽灵已经收集？
- No! Are you ready yet?-没有！你准备好了吗？
- Yeah, almost there.-是的，几乎在那里。
Wait. Wait.等待.等待.
What was the name of that teacher?那个老师叫什么名字？
Hate cake.讨厌蛋糕。
- Liza. Liza Bahar.-莉莎。Liza Bahar。
- Liza Bahar.- Liza Bahar。
Fuck's sake.他妈的的缘故。
This is a list of everyone这是一个每个人的名单
who's used the hashtag.谁用标签。
What?什么？
Everyone who took part每一个参加的人
in the Game of Consequences.在游戏的后果。
They've hoovered up their ID from GCHQ他们收缴他们的身份从GCHQ
by the looks of it.通过它的外观。
That backdoor worked both ways, it seems.这后门工作的两种方式，它似乎。
- See if I'm on there.-看看我是否在那里。
- What?-什么？
I posted the tag earlier我提前贴了标签
with Scholes' face.用斯科尔斯的脸。
- Just trying to get a reaction from him.-只是想从他那里得到一个反应。
- Yeah, yeah, almost there.-是的，是的，几乎在那里。
Yeah, you're there.是的，你在那里。
Almost there.几乎没有。
Why has he collected everyone为什么他要收集所有的人
who took part? I mean...谁参加了？我的意思是…
Okay. I'm ready.可以.我准备好了。
- Shit.-该死。
- Run it now.-现在运行它。
No. Think. He left us a trail.不想。他给我们留下了一条线索。
- Oh, come on.哦，来吧。
- That photo with the whereabouts,-那照片的下落，
it's too big a mistake for him.这对他来说太大了。
He knew we'd do this.他知道我们会这样做。
- Now we're shutting it down, all right?-现在我们关闭它，好吗？
- And maybe that'll trigger some endgame,这也许会引发一些残局，
something to do with that list.与那个列表有关的事情。
What if those are his real targets?如果这些是他的真正目标呢？
The people on the list.名单上的人。
Everyone who took part.每一个参加的人。
Consequences.后果.
The hate figures were the bait.讨厌的数字是诱饵。
The players are the target.球员是目标。
- Run the deact command.运行deact命令。
- Now just wait a minute, okay?-现在就等一分钟，好吗？
- Run it.-运行它。
- No!-没有！
__
Yeah.是啊.
Yeah, it worked.是的，它工作。
Sorry, but that needed doing.对不起，但那需要做。
- No, no, no, no, no.-不，不，不，不，不。
- What?-什么？
No. No.号号
- Fuck!-他妈的！
- No.-不。
Shit.倒霉.
Oh, no.哦，不，
♪ Follow me ♪
♪ I'll show you the way ♪
♪ Out of this home ♪
♪ Out of this land ♪
♪ Fall into me ♪
♪ And drown inside me ♪
♪ I know you will see ♪
♪ The beauty of me ♪
There's...有...
♪ I love you so ♪
♪ All that I can be ♪
♪ I know you will see ♪
♪ The beauty of me ♪
♪ Tired are your splendid soldiers ♪
♪ Tired are they, here they go ♪
We're all tragically familiar with我们都是熟悉的
the rest of the events of that week.其余那周发生的事件。
And we need no reminding我们不需要提醒
of the sheer scale纯粹规模的
of the loss of life that followed.其次是生活的损失。
No. No, we don't.不，不，我们不知道
And what became of Ms. Colson?和Colson小姐怎么样了？
I think she blamed herself.我想她责怪自己。
No. I know she did.不，我知道她做过。
She felt she'd followed his breadcrumb她觉得她会跟着他的面包屑
trail and sprung the whole thing.跟踪和涌现了整个事情。
She left the force.她离开了部队。
I didn't hear from her.我没有收到她的来信。
Rang her, tried emailing, but no response.给她打电话，试着发邮件，但没有回应。
Then, um...然后，嗯…
About four months later,大约四个月后，
they found her things.他们发现了她的东西。
On a beach.在海滩上。
With a note.用笔记。
She killed herself?她自杀了？
That's the base theory, yes.这是基础理论，是的。
Ms Parke, I would like to commend you帕克女士，我想推荐你
for sharing your testimony and your time.分享你的见证和你的时间。
Thank you.谢谢您.
__
Señor.
- Gracias.-格拉西亚斯。
__
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com
♪ Tired are your splendid soldiers ♪
♪ Tired are they, here they go ♪