Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com
__
Okay, my people!好的，我的人民！
Rise and shine. Get up, Stripe.上升和照耀。起来，条，
Hey. You awake yet?嘿.你醒了吗？
- Sure as shit ain't dreaming no more.-当然，作为屎不再做梦。
- Company!公司！
Something went down last night昨晚有东西落下来了
in Her Falls,在她的瀑布，
a village about three miles east.东约三英里的一个村庄。
We've got reports of a food store我们有一家食品店的报告
broken into, shit stolen.破了，屎被偷了。
Locals think it's roaches.当地人认为这是蟑螂。
Roaches!蟑螂！
We head out in five minutes. Let's go!我们五分钟后就到了。走吧!
Hey, so, it looks like you're getting嘿，所以，看起来你越来越
your first real-live roach hunt, huh?你的第一个真正的蟑螂打猎，嗯？
Hey, new!嘿，新！
New!新的！
It's Stripe.它的条纹。
Here's a little tip just in case这里有一个小提示以防万一
you get your first toe-to-toe你得到你的第一个脚趾到脚趾
- with one of them roaches today.与其中一个蟑螂今天。
- Uh-huh?-嗯？
When you see one right here,当你在这里看到一个，
try not to shit your pants.尽量不要穿你的裤子。
It's only gonna piss them off.这只会让他们滚蛋。
- I'll try.-我会尝试。
- Try to ignore Len.尝试去忽略Len。
His aim's so bad,他的目标是如此糟糕，
he's the only guy on Earth他是地球上唯一的一个
who could shit his own pants and miss.谁能他自己的裤子和小姐。
- Fuck you, farm girl.-操你，农场女孩。
- Farm girl?-农场女孩？
Yeah. Hunting's in my blood.是啊.我的血液在我的血液里。
Some of us are naturals.我们中的一些人是天生的。
Moving out!搬出去！
Whoo! Yeah!喔！是啊!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay.哇，哇，哇。可以.
You can speak now.你现在可以说话了。
- It must have been roaches.- 一定是蟑螂。
- Roaches, you see them? You see?-蟑螂，你看到了吗？你看到了吗？
I didn't see them.
I heard them.我听到他们。
All the mess. It must have been them.所有的混乱。一定是他们了。
Want a cookie?想要一块饼干吗？
- Here you go.-在这里你去。
- They've been in the food.他们一直在食物中。
We'll have to destroy“我”我们将不得不摧毁
everything they left.他们所留下的一切。
No one will eat it.没有人会吃它。
We can replace that, okay?我们可以代替，好吗？
They destroyed the cooler.他们摧毁了冷却器。
Broke it and took the parts.打破了它，并采取了部分。
The cooler?冷吗？
They stole parts from the cooler?他们偷了冷却器的零件？
Which way did they go?他们走哪条路？
There were footprints有脚印
in the dirt leading that way.在污垢引导的方式。
Parn Heidekker.Parn Heidekker。
Heidekker? Is that a name?Heidekker？那是一个名字吗？
Stop them coming. Please, you must stop.阻止他们的到来。请，你必须停止。
Okay.可以.
I have child who is scared.我有一个害怕的孩子。
I will. I promise.我会的.我的承诺。
Stripe!条纹！
Okay. Our friend here thinks可以.我们的朋友在这里想
that the roaches那蟑螂
went in the direction走向方向
of Parn Heidekker's place.Parn Heidekker的地方。
Local oddball, seems to be some kind当地的古怪，似乎是某种
of religious freak.宗教狂。
Anderson, Hague, I want you乔林，海牙，我想你
to stay here and help them torch the food,留在这里，并帮助他们火炬的食物，
keep them calm and reassured.让他们保持冷静和安心。
The rest of you,其余的你，
we're gonna drop in on Heidekker.我们要去拜访heidekker。
Ask some questions,问一些问题，
sniff around the place.嗅周围的地方。
If there's roaches,如果有蟑螂，
we show we're ready for them. Let's go.我们表明我们已经准备好了。走吧.
So Mr. Heidekker is not exactly所以Heidekker先生是不是
what you call a socialite or a mingler.你所称的社会名流或搅拌器。
Seems like mental health issues.似乎是心理健康问题。
He's got some interesting views他有一些有趣的观点
on roaches, by all accounts.对蟑螂，所有帐户。
I'm putting his info我把他的信息
in your Mass system now.现在在你的质量系统。
Been complaints lodged against him被控告他
going months back.去几个月回来。
Locals claim that he let roaches当地人说，他让蟑螂
cross his land, left food out for them.过了他的地，给他们留了食物。
Could be just shit talk可能只是废话
from the local villagers though so...从当地村民虽然如此…
Yo, how many roaches哟，有多少蟑螂
we got left out here?我们被留在这里了？
A couple of thousand?几千个？
A couple of hundred, if that?几百个，如果是这样的话？
I mean, back home we had millions, man.我的意思是，我们有上百万的人，男人。
It only took two years它只花了两年时间
to get shit back on track.回到轨道上的轨道。
Out here you got rustic fucks在这里你有质朴的乱搞
throwing them scraps.把它们扔了。
No wonder it's taken so long难怪它采取了这么久
to mop shit up.拖屎了。
But how can anyone be dumb enough但怎么能有人足够愚蠢
to help a fucking roach?帮助一个该死的蟑螂？
Hell, yeah.地狱，是的。
Portals front and rear.门户网站的前部和后部。
Windows blacked out.Windows涂黑。
Chimney smoke. Someone's home.烟囱冒烟。某人的家。
Lennard, you use the boomer.Lennard，你用潮。
Okay, Mass check. Everyone got the layout?好的，质量检查。每个人都有布局？
- Check.-检查。
Check.检查。
Aikin, Valcon, Coach,Aikin，valcon，教练，
you check the outbuildings here.你检查库房这里。
Take them one at a time and slow.以他们一个在一个时间和缓慢。
Stripe, Raiman,条纹，Raiman，
you come with me and Lennard.你跟我来，Lennard。
We go in here.我们在这里。
Len and I will talk to Heidekker,Len和我会和Heidekker谈谈，
you check the rest of the house.你检查房子的其余部分。
Okay.可以.
Optimal outcome, no shots fired.最佳结果，没有投篮。
Except on a roach.除了蟑螂。
Morning, sir.早上，先生。
There's no need for this.没有必要这样。
I speak your language.我说你的语言。
Okay.可以.
- What is it you want?-你想要什么？
- Just to talk.-只想说话。
That's what we're doing.这就是我们正在做的。
Be a little more neighbourly是一个小更友好
if we did it inside.如果我们在里面做。
Check the upstairs rooms.检查楼上的房间。
Relax. I'm not your enemy.放松。我不是你的敌人。
Where are they?在什么地方？
Where are who?谁在哪里？
You know, we got a whole bunch你知道，我们得到了一大堆
of frightened, angry people害怕，愤怒的人
in that village.在那个村庄里。
Roaches have been breaking蟑螂已经被打破
into the food stores, stealing supplies.进食品店，偷用品。
You know anything about that?你知道吗？
No.不.
See, it's not just what they stole.看，这不只是他们偷了什么。
All that food left is gonna be destroyed.所有的食物都会被摧毁。
- No one's gonna eat it.-没人会吃了。
- Stripe.条纹。
Makes life harder for everyone.让每个人的生活更难。
Cross on the wall there.那里的墙上的十字架。
You got principles.你有原则。
Think all life is sacred. And I get it.认为所有的生命都是神圣的。我得到它。
I agree. All life is sacred so...我同意。所有的生命都是神圣的…
you even got to protect the roaches.你甚至要守护的蟑螂。
Right?对吗？
It's not their fault they're like that.这不是他们的错，他们是这样的。
They didn't ask for this.他们没有要求这个。
I get it. We get it.我得到它。我们得到它。
Mm-hmm.嗯嗯。
There's shit有屎
in their blood that made them that way.在他们的血液中，使他们的方式。
The sickness they're carrying.他们携带的疾病。
That doesn't care about那不在乎
the sanctity of life生命的尊严
or the pain或疼痛
about who else is gonna suffer.关于谁会受到痛苦。
We don't stop the roaches,我们不停的蟑螂，
in five, ten, 20 years from now,在五，十，20年从现在开始，
you're still gonna get kids born that way,你仍然会让孩子出生的方式，
and then they're gonna breed.然后他们会繁殖。
Bingo.答对了.
And so it goes on. That cycle of pain.所以它继续。那个痛苦的循环。
That sickness,这病，
and it could have been avoided.它本来是可以避免的。
Fucking roach nest.该死的蟑螂窝。
You check in there. I'll take the stairs.你在那里检查。我会走楼梯。
Every roach you save today,每一个蟑螂，你今天存，
you condemn God knows how many people你谴责上帝知道有多少人
to despair and misery tomorrow.绝望和痛苦的明天。
You can't still see them as human.你仍然看不到他们是人类。
Understandable sentiment, granted,可以理解的情绪，
but it's misguided.但这是被误导的。
We gotta take them out if humankind如果人类，我们必须把他们带出来
is gonna carry on in this world.将继续在这个世界上。
That's just the hard truth.这只是硬道理。
Gotta make sacrifices.必须做出牺牲。
What the fuck?什么他妈的？
Help me out here!在这里帮我！
Fuck!性交!
♪ Try to shame me and still I'll care ♪
♪ You can run around, even put me down ♪
♪ I'll still be there for you ♪
Rai!RAI！
We gotta listen to Mr. Sunday School我们得听星期日先生的学校
all the way back to base?所有的方式回到基地？
You can cover your ears.你可以覆盖你的耳朵。
Yeah, or, uh....是的，或者，呃……
I'll just hit permanent mute.我将只打永久静音。
Lower your weapon.放下你的武器。
Roach lover counts as a kill too, right?罗奇的爱人作为一个杀了，对吗？
He's a civ, right?他是一个文明，对吗？
You shoot a civ, that's gonna stay你拍一个文明，那会留下来
with you the rest of your life.和你在一起，你的生活。
Yo, Stripe, why don't you, uh...哟，条纹，为什么不，嗯…
pull the stick out of your ass?把棍子从你的屁股上拉出来？
Because I'm fucking with him, not you.因为我他妈的是他，而不是你。
I guess I had you both going, right?我想我让你俩都走了，对吗？
All right!好吧！
Let's torch the place.让我们的火炬的地方。
Hey, you okay, man?嘿，你还好吗，男人？
Yeah.是啊.
- I heard you popped one in there.-我听说你突然出现在那里。
- Two.两。
Wait, two?等等，两个？
- I got another one, with my knife.-我还有一个，用我的刀。
- With your knife? Holy shit!用你的刀吗？天啊!
- Pretty good, right?-很好，对吗？
- Yeah, you fucking Terminator.-是的，你他妈的终结者。
Damn! First time out, he gets two.该死!第一次出去，他得到两个。
You lucky motherfucker, man.你这个幸运的混蛋，人。
Sweet dreams for this asshole.这混蛋甜蜜的梦。
Gonna get a treat tonight.今晚会得到一个治疗。
Whoo-hoo! Whoo!呼呼呼！喔！
I love you.我爱你！
Whoa! Miss Sharp Shooter.哇！Sharp小姐射手。
Patronising fuck!高高在上的他妈的！
__
Ruthless! You're the Grim Reaper.无情的!你是死神。
Yeah, well, no roach gets away next time.是啊，嗯，没有蟑螂逃脱了下次。
Are you still sweating that?你还在流汗吗？
Well, I grew up tracking deer.嗯，我从小跟踪鹿。
You never give up.你永远不会放弃。
I don't like it when they get away.我不喜欢他们离开的时候。
__
Nice.好的。
Yeah,是啊,
if that fucker made it to the forest,如果那混蛋了森林，
probably made it to the border,可能是到了边境，
gone for good.去了好。
Yeah. It's all right for you.是啊.这对你来说都是正确的。
You popped two of 'em.你把两个呢。
It's been a while for me.这是一段时间对我来说。
You know, the gal is getting twitchy.你知道，女孩也变得焦躁不安。
Come on, Rai.来吧，莱伊。
You sleep good?你睡的好吗？
Yeah, I slept OK.是的，我睡得好。
What, that's all you're gonna give me?什么，这是你要给我的吗？
Okay? You know, if I got two in one go,好吗？你知道，如果我有两个在一个去，
I would want to come for like an hour!我想来像一个小时！
All right, shut up.好吧，闭嘴。
All right.好吧。
Ah! That's the way.啊啊啊啊啊！就是这个方法。
Hey, you okay, man?嘿，你还好吗，男人？
Yeah, think I'm tired is all.是的，我觉得我累了。
Uh-huh?嗯？
All right, so you did have a good night.好的，所以你有一个好的夜晚。
39, 40, 41....39，40，41……
42...42…
43, 44, 45, 46,43，44，45，46，
47, 48, 49,47，48，49，
50, 51, 52,50，51，52，
53, 54, 55,53，54，55，
56, 57, 58, 59...56，57，58，59…
Strong and pure.强而纯。
- Hey, Stripe, you okay?-嘿，条纹，你还好吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
I mean, I... don't know.我的意思是，I.。不知道.
I feel a little off.我感觉有点过。
I mean, I ain't sick or nothing.我的意思是，我没有生病或没有。
It's just, uh...只是，呃…
Report to the sick bay.报告给生病的海湾。
Running diagnostic.运行诊断。
What do you see?你看到了什么？
A cube.一个立方体。
- Rotating?旋转？
- Yeah.-是的。
- And now?-现在？
- A tree.-一棵树。
- Like an apple tree.-像一棵苹果树。
- Touch the apples for me.-为我触摸苹果。
Full marks.满分。
- So you say you had like a headache?-所以你说你有像头痛？
- Yeah, but just quick.-是的，但只是快速。
Nothing big, just...没什么大的，只是…
Well, everything looks okay.好吧，一切看起来好。
No sign of any malfunction没有任何故障的迹象
or dropout with your Mass implant.或辍学与您的群众植入。
And physically,和身体，
you're in exemplary shape.你是模范的。
You've just seen combat,你刚刚看到战斗，
you can expect some sort of side effect.你可以期待某种副作用。
There was this, uh... this thing...有这个，呃…这件事…
with a light on it at the farmhouse.在农舍里有一个灯。
- Roach had it.Roach把它。
- A roach had it?-一只蟑螂呢？
- Kind of like a flashlight.-有点像手电筒。
- Flashlight?-手电筒？
Kinda.有点.
I don't know.我不知道。
Seriously, you're fine. Your Mass is fine.说真的，你很好。你的质量很好。
Blood's fine. It's all fine.血液的罚款。一切都很好。
Okay. Yeah.可以.是啊.
Maybe you should speak to Arquette.也许你应该和阿奎特说话。
Who's Arquette?谁是阿奎特？
So, you must be Koinanchey?所以，你一定是Koinanchey？
Koinange. Folks call me Stripe.Koinange。人们叫我条纹。
Why would they call you that?他们为什么会这样称呼你呢？
Couldn't pronounce Koinange either,发音不koinange要么，
I guess.我猜。
- That's funny.-这很有趣。
- Thank you.-谢谢。
At ease, son. Sit down.放心，儿子。坐下来.
So you recently logged your first kills?那么你最近记录了你的第一次杀人？
- Two roaches?两蟑螂？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
First time out. It's impressive.第一次出去。这是令人印象深刻的。
Yeah, I guess.是的，我想。
So what happened?那么发生了什么事？
- What, with the kills?-什么，杀了？
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
Oh. I'm in this, uh... farmhouse.哦.我在这个，呃…农舍。
There's this, like,有这样的，像，
hidden room or something.隐藏的房间或东西。
We go in and there they are.我们去那里，他们是。
First one, I just... It was automatic.第一个，我只是…这是自动的。
Just pop-pop, you know?只是流行流行，你知道吗？
Right. Just like in training.正确的.就像在训练中。
Yeah, just like that, yeah. Yeah.是的，就这样，是的。是啊.
- And the second?-和第二？
- I mean, he was on the ground with me.-我的意思是，他和我在一起。
He?他？
It was a he.这是一个他。
Oh.哦.
So, this was close quarters then?那么，这是近四分之一的？
Yeah, he's on top of me.是的，他在我的上方。
Struggling, I mean...挣扎，我的意思是…
I couldn't reach my rifle我没能够到我的步枪
so I had to stick him.所以我不得不坚持他。
Stick it. With my knife.坚持它。用我的刀。
And how did that... feel?那是怎么做的…的感觉？
- What, like...?-什么，像…？
- Emotionally.-情感。
I didn't. I mean, it was quick.我没有，我的意思是，它很快。
It was self-protection.这是自我保护。
I guess all I felt was, you know, relief.我想我所感受到的是，你知道，救济。
- Just relief?-只是救济？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
It's not unusual to experience这不是不寻常的经验
other feelings too.其他感觉太。
A moment of euphoria even.一瞬间的快感甚至。
Yeah, I guess.是的，我想。
I don't know,我不知道。
I thought maybe I'd feel...我想也许我会觉得…
I don't know.我不知道。
- Something else?-其他东西？
- Yeah, like...-是的，像…
Regret. Something like that,后悔。这样的东西，
but that just wasn't there.但那只是不在那里。
Hmm.隐马尔可夫模型.
So you'd do it again?那么你会再做一次吗？
Yeah, sure.是的，当然。
So... why are you here?所以…你为什么在这里？
I don't know. I mean...我不知道。我的意思是…
I had a few weird moments.我有一些奇怪的时刻。
My Mass looked like it was glitching out.我看起来像是失灵了。
But your implants,但你的植入物，
I mean, they passed every diagnostic.我的意思是，他们通过了每一项诊断。
- There is nothing wrong with that?-这没有什么错吗？
- Yeah, they said it's fine.-是的，他们说这很好。
I don't know, I think I just...我不知道，我想我只是…
Felt like something was up with it.感觉好像有东西在一起。
- But there's not.-但没有。
- No.-不。
You did a big thing.你做了一件大事。
You should be proud of yourself.你应该为自己感到骄傲。
Okay?好吗？
It'll pass.它会通过。
Let's get you a good sleep tonight, huh?今晚我们睡个好觉吧，嗯？
A real good sleep.一个真正的好睡眠。
Fuck me.他妈的我。
Way to go, fuck fingers.去的路，他妈的手指。
It seems Heidekker didn't stay silent看来heidekker不保持沉默
too long once we got to work on him.一旦我们对他工作太久。
He's given up a location, someplace他放弃了一个地方，一个地方
the roaches have been scavenging.蟑螂已清除。
Well, all right.好吧，好吧。
It's a housing project这是一个住房项目
that's been empty since the war.这是空的，因为战争。
It's not far from here.离这儿不远。
So control wants us to do recon所以让我们做侦察
before we go back to base.在我们回到基地之前。
Can we hurry it up here?我们可以在这里快点吗？
We ought to burn the whole forest down,我们应该把整个森林都烧毁了，
huh?嗯？
Give those roaches nowhere to run.给那些蟑螂无处可逃。
Okay, you see that?好吧，你看到了吗？
Solar panel looks cleaner than the rest.太阳能电池板看起来比其他的清洁。
And there are some cables.并且有一些电缆。
- There's got to be roaches leaching power.-有蟑螂的浸出能力。
- Why here?-为什么在这里？
Christ knows.上帝知道。
All right.好吧。
Better dial it in.最好拨到。
Control. This is Medina.控制。这是麦地那。
Positive ID. Signs of activity here积极的身份证。在这里活动的迹象
at the housing project location.在住宅项目的位置。
Sighted one solar panel, looks有远见的一个太阳能电池板，看起来
recently wiped clean and some cabling.最近擦干净和一些布线。
Roger so far.罗杰为止。
- You all right there?-你都在那里吗？
- Smell the grass.-闻草。
We can't usually smell nothing.我们通常不闻什么。
- You ever noticed that?-你注意到了吗？
- No, I never noticed that.-不，我从来没有注意到。
Requesting course of action.请求行动过程。
Didn't read. Please repeat.没有读。请重复。
Okay.可以.
Control says we should fall back控制说我们应该后退
and await comm...等待为主。
Shit!倒霉!
Medina.麦地那。
Oh!哦!
Stripe, get back! She's dead. Come on!条纹，回来！她死了。来吧！
Okay. Ready? Cover me.可以.准备好了吗？掩护我。
Rai! Rai, come on.RAI！莱伊，来吧。
Okay.可以.
Oh, fucking roach got a rifle.哦，该死的蟑螂有步枪。
Jesus Christ.Jesus Christ。
Fuck. Piece of shit.性交.一块屎。
Okay, Stripe.好吧，条纹。
Stripe, come on. Get it together, dude.条纹，来吧。把它放在一起，伙计。
He fired six shots.他开了六枪。
His rifle looks old, bolt action.他的步枪看起来很旧，螺栓的动作。
- Should take him ten seconds to reload.-应带他十秒重新加载。
- We go in?-我们进去吗？
We go in and take him out.我们进去带他出去。
Are you with me?你听懂了吗？
- I'm with you.-我和你在一起。
- Let's go!-让我们走吧！
Follow me!跟着我!
Ready? Okay, three, two, one. Cover me.准备好了吗？好的，三，两个，一个。掩护我。
Come on, man! What the fuck?来吧，男人！什么他妈的？
What the fuck is this shit?这是什么他妈的是什么？
Let's go.走吧.
Stripe!条纹！
Whoa, whoa! It's okay. Hey. Hey.哇，哇！这是好的。嘿.嘿.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.冷静.冷静.冷静.
It's okay. It's okay.这是好的。这是好的。
I'm not gonna hurt you.我不会伤害你。
I'm not gonna hurt you. Okay?我不会伤害你。好吗？
Go on, get out of here. Go on.继续，离开这里。去。
It's not safe. There's roaches here.它不安全。这里有蟑螂。
Go on. Get.去。得到。
Come on!来吧！
- Rai, what did you do?-清莱，你做了什么？
- Shut up! Come on!-闭嘴！来吧！
What did you do, Rai?做什么，莱伊？
Got ya.找到你。
Rai!RAI！
No!不!
- Run!运行！
- What the fuck are you doing?-你他妈的在干什么？
- You're killing them!-你要杀了他们！
- They're roaches!他们是蟑螂！
You're fucking killing them, Rai!你他妈的杀了他们，莱伊！
Fuck you!你他妈的！
What the fuck's wrong with you, man?你他妈的怎么了，男人？
You got some blown shit.你有一些吹粪。
- Pull it together!-把它拉在一起！
- No.-不。
Are you all right?你还好吗？
You gotta get out of here. Come on.你得离开这里。来吧。
Come on!来吧！
Fuck!性交!
You better run.你最好跑。
Shh. Shh.嘘。嘘。
Here.在这里.
I'm all right.我都是对的。
You see me as I am.你看到我，因为我。
Of course I see you.我当然看见你了。
You don't see roach?你没有看到蟑螂？
You ain't a roach.你不是一个蟑螂。
Roaches is all...蟑螂是所有…
Fucked up?搞砸了？
Roaches don't speak.蟑螂不说。
You just can't hear us.你听不到我们的声音。
- What the fuck are you talking about?-你他妈的在说什么？
- Your implants. Your army implants.-你的植入物。你的军队植入物。
The Mass system?质量系统？
They put it in your head to help you fight,他们把它放在你的头，以帮助你战斗，
and when it works,当它工作时，
you see us as something other.你看到我们作为其他的东西。
One of us, Luka,我们中的一员，Luka，
was making a... a machine.正在做一个..一个机。
Light flashes.灯闪烁。
Said it can interfere with the implant.说它可以干扰植入物。
You're roaches?你是蟑螂？
But I've seen roaches.但我见过蟑螂。
I've seen them, they're fucking...我见过他们，他们他妈的…
They're like, uh...他们是喜欢，嗯…
- Animals?动物吗？
- No, they're monsters. I've seen them.-不，他们是怪物。我见过他们。
The implant made you see this.植入物使你看到这个。
Fuck. The villagers... Huh?性交.村民们…嗯？
The locals, they... they ain't army.当地人，他们…他们不是军队。
They got no Mass in their heads.他们的头没有质量。
They're scared of the roaches.他们害怕蟑螂。
- They hate the fucking things.-他们讨厌他妈的东西。
- Everybody hates us.-每个人都恨我们。
Well, what the fuck do they see? Huh?嗯，他们他妈的是什么？嗯？
The fucking civs, when they look他妈的文明，当他们看
at a roach, what do they see?在一种方法中，他们看到了什么？
What you see now.你现在看到的是什么。
They hate all the same他们讨厌所有相同的
because it's what they've been told.因为这是他们被告知的。
Ten years ago, it began.十年前，它开始了。
Post-war.战后。
First, the screening programme,首先，筛选计划，
the DNA checks,DNA检查，
then the register,然后寄存器，
the emergency measures.应急措施。
And soon everyone calls us creatures.很快每个人都称我们为生物。
Filthy creatures.肮脏的动物。
Every voice. The TV. The computer.每一个声音。电视。计算机。
Say we have... we have sickness in us.说我们有…我们在我们的疾病。
We have weakness. It's in our blood.我们有弱点。它在我们的血液里。
They say that our blood cannot go on.他们说，我们的血液不能继续。
That we cannot go on.我们不能继续。
My name was Catarina.我的名字叫卡塔琳娜。
He was Alec.他是亚历克。
Now we're just roach.现在我们只蟑螂。
But now...但现在…
Now you see me.现在你看到我。
Rai?莱伊？
Rai, no!清莱，没有！
Tell me I shouldn't kill you.告诉我我不应该杀了你。
- None of it's true, Rai.-真的没有，莱伊。
- What the fuck got you?-你他妈的得到了什么？
None of it's true.没有一个是真的。
Fuck you.你他妈的。
Get up. Back against the wall.起床.背靠墙。
Get up!起床!
You want me to come in there?你要我进来吗？
It's all right. I can just talk to him.这一切都是对的。我可以和他谈谈。
Thank you, Briley.谢谢你，布里利。
Stripe.条纹。
We owe you an apology.我们欠你一个道歉。
We didn't spot the fault in your Mass.我们没有发现你的质量的错。
I got you a coffee.我给你喝了一杯咖啡。
The device you found in the farmhouse,你在农舍里找到的装置，
you mentioned it to the doctor.你向医生提过。
Is this the thing?这是什么东西吗？
We found it on an old block我们在一个旧街区发现的
that you and Raiman were searching.你和Raiman搜索。
Looks like they reverse engineered it看起来他们逆向设计的
from some of our drone parts and so on.从我们的一些无人机零件等。
The light here transmits a code.这里的光发送一个代码。
It's like a virus.它就像一个病毒。
It burrows into your Mass,它融入你的质量，
trying to shut it down from within.试图把它从内部关闭。
I tell you, those roaches我告诉你，那些蟑螂
are getting more ingenious变得越来越巧妙
than we give them credit for.比我们给他们的信贷。
The whole thing is a lie.整个事情是一个谎言。
I understand why you'd say that, yeah.我明白为什么你会说，是的。
Roaches.蟑螂。
They look just like us.他们看起来像我们。
Of course they do.他们当然做。
That's why they're so dangerous.这就是为什么他们如此危险。
Humans.人类.
You know, we give ourselves a bad rap,你知道，我们给自己一个坏说唱，
but we're genuinely empathetic但是我们真正的同情
as a species.作为一个物种。
I mean, we don't actually really want我的意思是，我们不真的真的想要
to kill each other.杀死对方。
Which is a good thing.这是一件好事。
Until your future depends直到你的未来取决于
on wiping out the enemy.论消灭敌人。
Come on, sit down.来吧，坐下。
I don't know how much history我不知道有多少历史
you studied in school.你在学校学习。
Many years ago,许多年前，
I'm talking early 20th century,我说的是第二十世纪初，
most soldiers大部分的士兵
didn't even fire their weapons.甚至没有火他们的武器。
Or if they did, they would just aim或者如果他们那样做了，他们只会瞄准
over the heads of the enemies.越过敌人的头。
They did it on purpose.他们是故意做的。
British Army. World War I.英国军队。第一次世界大战。
The brigadier,准将，
he'd walk the line with a stick他用一根棍子走线
and he'd whack his men他打他的人
in order to get them to shoot.为了让他们射击。
Even in World War II, in a firefight,甚至在第二次世界大战，在交火中，
only 15%, 20% of the men只有15%，20%的男人
would pull the trigger.会扣扳机。
The fate of the world at stake世界的命运在赌注
and only 15% of them fired.只有15%的人被解雇。
Now what does that tell you?现在告诉你什么？
It tells me that that war它告诉我，那场战争
would have been over a whole lot quicker会有一个更快的整个地段
had the military got its shit together.让军队把它的屎放在一起。
So we adapted.所以我们适应。
Better training. Better conditioning.更好的培训。更好的调理。
Then comes the Vietnam War,然后是越南战争，
and the shooting percentage goes up to 85.投篮命中率高达85。
Lot of bullets flying.很多子弹飞。
The kills were still low.杀死的仍然很低。
Plus the guys who did get a kill,再加上那些没有被杀的人，
well, most of them came back嗯，他们中的大多数回来了
all messed up in the head.都在头上乱了。
And that's pretty much how things stayed这是相当多的事情留下
until Mass came along.直到质量的到来。
You see, Mass...你看，质量…
Well, that's the ultimate military weapon.嗯，这是最终的军事武器。
It helps you with your intel.它可以帮助你与你的英特尔。
Your targeting. Your comms.你的目标。你的通讯。
Your conditioning.你的空调。
It's a lot easier to pull the trigger这是一个更容易拉动扳机
when you're aiming at the bogeyman, hmm?当你瞄准怪物，嗯？
It's not just your eyes, though.这不仅仅是你的眼睛，虽然。
Takes care of your other senses, too.照顾你的其他感觉，太。
You don't hear the shrieks.你不会听到尖叫声。
You don't smell the blood and the shit.你闻不到血和屎。
They're human beings.他们是人类。
Do you have any idea the amount of shit你有什么想法吗
that's in their DNA?那是在他们的DNA里？
Higher rates of cancer.更高的癌症率。
Muscular dystrophy.肌营养不良症。
MS. SLS. Substandard IQ.SLS女士。不合格的智商。
Criminal tendencies. Sexual deviances.犯罪倾向。性偏差。
It's all there.都在那里。
The screening shows it.筛选显示它。
Is that what you want这是你想要的吗
for the next generation?为下一代？
Don't feel bad about doing your job.做你的工作，不要感到不好。
The villagers won't do it.村民们不会这样做的。
The folks back home won't do it.那些回家的人不会这样做的。
They don't have Mass.他们没有质量。
Mass lets you do it.质量让你这样做。
You.你。
You're protecting the bloodline.你保护的血统。
And that, my friend, is an honour.并且，我的朋友，是一个荣誉。
There's no honour here.这里没有荣誉。
It's just killing.这只是杀人。
- Lying and killing.-说谎和杀戮。
- No one lied to you.-没有人对你撒谎。
You knew all of this. All along.你知道这一切。所有沿。
What are you talking about?你在说什么？
You agreed你同意
to have your Mass implant put in.有你的植入物放在。
Set up. Every soldier does.设置.每个士兵都做。
We can't just embed it and feed you我们不能只嵌入它和喂养你
a dream. Your mind would reject it.一个梦想。你的头脑会拒绝它。
You have to accept it. Willingly.你必须接受它。很乐意.
It's exactly what you did.这正是你所做的。
So you see the terms所以你看到的条款
and conditions there?还有条件吗？
Yeah, that's like a whole essay, man.是的，这就像一个完整的文章，人。
What is that?那是什么？
That's your consent video.这是你的同意视频。
From when you signed up six months ago.从你六个月前签署的。
Basically, it says you agree基本上，它说你同意
to Mass implant activation.要大量植入激活。
- I didn't do this.-我没有这样做。
- Yes, you did.-是的，你做了。
- Works kind of like hypnosis.工作有点像催眠。
- Yeah, all right.- 是的，好的。
Part of what you're agreeing to是你同意的一部分
is not realising没有意识到
you've been put in this state.你已经被放在这个状态了。
If you follow me.如果你跟我走。
You won't recall this conversation.你不会记得这次谈话。
That's kind of funny, man.这是一种有趣的，人。
Turn it off.关闭它。
- So for you to register consent...-所以为你注册同意……
- Turn it off, man.-把它关掉，男人。
I'm gonna need your thumbprint there.我需要你的指纹在那里。
- Right here?-“我就在这里？”
- Yes, please.- <我是的，请。
That's dope.这是毒品。
I didn't do that!我没有这样做！
- I don't remember that!-我不记得了！
- Just like the man said.-就像那个人说的。
- I know you're upset.-我知道你很难过。
- Fuck you!-他妈的你！
- What's happening?-发生了什么事？
- We control what you see, Stripe.我们控制你所看到的，条纹。
- I can't see nothing.-我什么也看不见。
- Because we control it.-因为我们控制它。
Give me my fucking eyes back.给我我他妈的眼睛回来。
- Let me lay out your options.-让我来制定你的选择。
- Give me my fucking eyes back, man!给我我的眼睛，男人！
Let me lay out your options!让我来制定你的选择！
Option one,选择一个，
you agree to have your Mass reset.你同意有你的质量复位。
All the recollections所有的回忆
of the past few days,在过去的几天里，
including this conversation, erased.包括这段对话，删除。
No way.没有办法。
Option two's incarceration.方案二的监禁。
- I'd advise you to consider.-我建议你考虑一下。
- Fuck you!-他妈的你！
Mass is a friend.大众是一个朋友。
Without it, you will remember没有它，你会记得
everything that you did.你所做的一切。
I ain't having this Mass shit.我没有这个大屎。
No more. No way.没有更多的。没有办法。
Okay.可以.
Well...好...
Maybe you should see也许你应该看到
what life would be like without it.如果没有它，生活将是什么样的。
What's happening?发生什么事了？
Where am I?我在哪里？
Heidekker's ranch. Three days ago.heidekker的牧场。三天前。
I have it all logged, Stripe.我有它所有的记录，条纹。
We can feed you everything that you did.我们可以养活你的一切，你做了。
Hey, no, no, no. No.嘿，不，不，不。
Please! Please don't shoot. Please!拜托!请别开枪。拜托!
Please! Please don't shoot.拜托!请别开枪。
- Please! Please!-请！拜托!
- No! No!-没有！不!
No. Make it stop.不，让它停止。
No! Please.不!拜托.
Make it stop!使它停止！
Please!拜托!
No! No!不!不!
No!不!
Fuck off! Stop it!滚开!它停下来！
You'll see and smell and feel it all.你会看到和闻到，感觉到这一切。
Is this what you want?这是你想要的吗？
On a loop? In a cell all alone?在一个循环？在一个细胞里独自一人？
We can make that go away.我们可以让离开。
This conversation goes away too.这一谈话也消失了。
All of it.所有它。
But you gotta say the word.但你必须说这个词。
Just say the word, Stripe.只要说一句话，条纹。
And it all goes away.这一切都消失了。
Just say the word.只要说一句话。
__
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull通过explosiveskull同步和修正
www.addic7ed.comwww.addic7ed.com