- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
__
I'm gonna have to ask you我要问你
to switch that off for now.为了切换到现在。
Okay, thanks.好的，谢谢。
You know what it's kinda like?你知道它有什么样的吗？
It's kinda like a rollercoaster.这有点像过山车。
You know what I mean?你明白我的意思吗？
It's like a roller coaster.它就像一个过山车。
Try it, try it with me.尝试它，尝试它与我。
How tall... How tall is the Eye?多高…眼睛有多高？
How tall... How tall is Big Ben?多高…大本钟有多高？
Since then, I've been working从那时起，我一直在工作
as a technology correspondent作为一名技术记者
for about two years now. It's been great.大约两年了。这是伟大的。
Cool, that's awesome. So you do, like,酷，这太棒了。所以你这样做，喜欢，
TV reports and, like, you're like...电视报道和，喜欢，你喜欢…
- No, just the website.-不，只是网站。
- Oh, just the website?-哦，只是网站？
I mean, there's some video stuff,我的意思是，有一些视频，
but tech industry pieces mainly.但科技产业碎片主要。
Cool, tech. Tech's awesome. Tech's...酷，科技技术很棒。技术..
So where have you been so far?那么，你到哪里去了？
Travelling around the周游
map like Indiana Jones?像印第安娜琼斯这样的地图？
- Yeah.-是的。
- Where the adventure line-冒险线在哪里
goes zigzagging all over the place.走曲折的所有地方。
Yeah, actually, I'm almost done. Uh...是的，事实上，我几乎完成了。休斯敦大学...
But I started off, flew into但我开始了，飞进了
Sydney, went to Thailand.悉尼，去泰国。
- Oh, jealous.哦，嫉妒。
- India. Yeah.-印度。是啊.
Did Rome, went to Rome.罗马，去罗马了吗。
- Did the whole Europe vacation.-整个欧洲假期。
- Even I haven't done that.-即使我没有这样做。
- Oh, really?-哦，真的吗？
- Mm.毫米。
It was awesome. I went这是可怕的。我去了
to Pamplona in Spain.在潘普洛纳的西班牙。
- Is that where they do the bull runs?-是他们在哪里做的公牛跑？
- Ran with the bulls.与公牛奔跑。
- You ran with the bulls?-你和公牛一起跑吗？
- I ran with the bulls.-我和公牛一起跑。
- That's how I got this.-这就是我得到的。
- Look at that!-看那个！
You really are Indiana Jones.你真的是印第安娜琼斯。
Have you got your whip你有你的鞭子吗
in your bag and your hat?在你的书包和你的帽子里？
I saved the world from the Nazis.我从纳粹手中拯救了这个世界。
That was pretty cool.那很酷。
I, you know, just... trying to do,我，你知道，只是…试图做，
you know, shit I've never done before.你知道，我以前从未做过的事。
Is that what you're doing on this trip?这是你在这次旅行中所做的吗？
You're, like, finding yourself?你是，喜欢，找到自己？
- Yeah, um... in a way.-是的，嗯…以一种方式。
- I mean, I...-我的意思是，I.。
Really to get away from the真的要离开
family home is what I'm doing.家庭的家是我所做的。
Oh.哦.
Yeah, that was...是的，那是…
Whatever, that's boring.不管什么，这很无聊。
Yeah, well, I'm afraid是的，嗯，我很害怕
Britain's pretty tame英国的漂亮驯服
as far as daredevil opportunities go.至于冒失的机会去。
Yeah? It's alright, it's the last是吗？这是好的，这是最后一次
leg of the trip anyway so...无论如何旅行的腿…
I'm... unfortunately home next week.我是...不幸的是下星期回家。
- Not much time...-没有太多的时间…
- Next week?-下星期？
- Yeah.-是的。
- That's not very long.-这不是很长。
- No, it's not.-不，它不是。
- Mnh-mnh.- Mnh mnh。
So... I could use some所以…我可以用一些
suggestions on fun shit to do.关于好玩屎的建议。
- Hmm. Fun shit to do?-嗯，有趣的事情要做吗？
- Fun shit to do.-有趣的屎。
Ow! Ow!OW！OW！
Jesus!Jesus！
Hello.你好.
- Good morning.-早上好。
Oh. Another battle scar.哦.另一个战斗疤痕。
Kind of.有点.
Let me guess, you were, like,让我猜猜，你是，像，
totally shark完全的鲨鱼
fishing in Cape Town, dude.在开普敦钓鱼，老兄。
Is that your那是你的
best American accent?最好的美国口音？
- Yes.-是的。
- That's pretty good. No, um...-这很好。不，嗯…
It was courtesy of Josh Peters,这是因为Josh Peters，
high school dick.高中的迪克。
He and I got into a fight in shop class.他和我在商店里打了一个打架。
And he hit me with this,他用这个打我，
like, metal rod thing.像，金属棒的东西。
What an arsehole.多么混蛋。
- That's terrible.-这太可怕了。
- I'm sorry.-我很抱歉。
Is that you or me?是你还是我？
Oh, it's gotta be you.哦，这是必须是你。
"Mom." You're so American.“妈妈，”你是如此的美国人。
Yes, I am.是的，我是。
Are you not gonna get that?你不明白吗？
Okay, that was a little impersonal.好的，那是一个没有人情味的。
What, you wanna talk to her now?什么，你想和她谈谈吗？
- You wanna talk to my mum? I'll call back.-你想和我妈妈说话吗？我会打过去的。
- Fair point.-公平点。
I don't think so.我不这么认为.
You hungry?你饿了吗？
Wow, look at all these games.哇，看这所有的游戏。
You're, like, a gamer. Cool.你喜欢，一个玩家。酷。
Of course I am. For my job.我当然是。为我的工作。
What, a girl never beat you什么，一个女孩永远不会打败你
at Street Fighter?街头霸王？
Is this... Like, this is, like,这是…喜欢，这是，喜欢，
your dating manual?你的约会手册？
What? The Singularity?什么？奇异吗？
It's when computers learn to outsmart这是当计算机学会智取
man like women did years ago.男人喜欢女人做了几年前。
Oh! Wow!哦!真的!
See, what I was doing, it was like a joke.看，我在做什么，这就像一个笑话。
- You know?-你知道吗？
- Really?真的吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
- Well, that's what you call a joke?-嗯，那是你说的笑话吗？
Mm-hmm. Yeah, you guys have those.嗯，是的，你们有那些。
- You guys have those here, right?-你们这里有人，对吗？
- Yeah, yeah. We do at the moment.-是的，是的。我们此刻在做。
Ow!OW！
That was a good joke. That was a good joke.这是一个很好的笑话。这是一个很好的笑话。
Enjoy your Marmite.享受你的砂锅。
Whoa! Oh, my...哇！哦，我的…
Do you guys seriously eat this shit?你们真的吃这个屎吗？
Okay, alright.好吧，好吧。
Alright, saved by mum.好吧，妈妈救了。
The best way to actually just实际上只是最好的方法
stop her from calling is...阻止她打电话是…
I don't know, answer it.我不知道，回答它。
Yeah, it's kind of like a can of worms是的，它有点像一个可以蠕虫
I just don't wanna open right now, so...我只是不想打开现在，所以…
She's worried. You're her son.她很担心。你是她的儿子。
You've been travelling,你一直在旅行，
and I just think if you我只是想如果你
speak to her, then...和她说话，然后…
Yeah, well, I still live at是的，嗯，我仍然生活在
home with her back in Syracuse.在锡拉丘兹她回家。
- That's cool. That's fine.-这很酷。好得很。
- Yeah.-是的。
I was taking care of my dad.我在照顾我的爸爸。
Oh, shit. Is he...?哦，该死的。他……吗？
- ...okay?-……好吗？
- No, he died.-不，他死了。
- Oh, my God. I'm sorry.-哦，我的上帝。我很抱歉.
- Last year. No, it's okay.-去年。不，这没关系。
It was coming for a while.它来了一段时间。
It was early onset Alzheimer's.这是早发性阿尔茨海默氏症。
Oh, that must have been really...哦，那一定是真的…
uh... tough.休斯敦大学...艰难的。
Yeah, he was my best friend.是的，他是我最好的朋友。
Sometimes he'd just look at me有时他只是看着我
and wouldn't even know who I was.甚至都不知道我是谁。
Well, my mum, like, I don't even...嗯，我的妈妈，喜欢，我甚至不…
I don't know how to talk to her.我不知道如何和她说话。
You know, I don't have that connection.你知道，我没有那个连接。
I don't even know where to start.我甚至不知道从哪里开始。
So that's why I left.所以这就是我离开的原因。
That's why I went on this trip.这就是我此行的原因。
Just to get away and make, you know,只是为了离开和作出，你知道，
all the memories that I can...所有的记忆，我可以…
while I can.虽然我可以。
And I know I gotta talk to her我知道我必须和她谈谈
and I gotta just...我必须…
But not on this. You know,但不是在这个。你知道的,
I just... I'll deal with it.我只是…我会处理它。
I'll deal with it when I get当我得到的时候，我会处理它
back, you know. I'll just...回来，你知道。我只会…
You're a good guy, Cooper.你是个好人，Cooper。
Call your mum.打电话给你的妈妈。
Zero, zero, one, nine,零，零，一，九，
three, nine, two, nine.九，三，二，九。
No, I did not buy a pair of不，我没有买一双
sandals in Koh Samui last night昨晚在苏梅岛的凉鞋
because I'm in...因为我在…
And how long does that take?那要花多长时间？
Because I need to buy a因为我需要买一个
ticket back to America.回到美国的机票。
Oh, my God.我的天！
Mm-hmm.嗯嗯。
Can I just say, this is the most blatant我可以说，这是最喧嚣的
cover story for a second hook-up ever?封面故事的第二个挂钩了吗？
Yes! Yes! Oh, my God.对!对!我的天！
Thank you, thank you, thank you.谢谢你，谢谢你，谢谢你。
Alright. Don't forget your bag.好吧。别忘了你的包。
The bag, yep, my bag.是的，我的袋袋。
Alright. You are a top bird.好吧。你是一只鸟。
I don't know what that means, but I heard我不知道这是什么意思，但我听到了
somebody say it once, and you're it.有人说了一次，你是它。
I got a plan.我有一个计划。
Yeah. It's odd jobs.是啊.这是奇怪的工作。
- For who?-谁？
- For, like, it's an app.-对于，喜欢，这是一个应用程序。
You can kind of... like, I've used it你可以种…喜欢，我用过
all over when funds were low, so...当资金较低的时候，所以…
- Oh, there's some interesting ones.-哦，有一些有趣的。
- Pretty cool.-很酷。
- "Thrillseekers wanted."“thrillseekers想要的。”
- Ooh.-哦。
- This looks right up your street.-这看起来对你的街道。
- Okay.-好的。
Okay, four pound signs.好的，四磅的迹象。
That's a biggie. That's good.这是一个大问题。那太好了。
It's a little out of town.这是一个小城镇。
And some kind of play test deal和一些类型的游戏测试
for a company called Saitoo...在一家叫saitoo…
Saitogoo...Saitogoo…
- SaitoGemu?- SaitoGemu？
- SaitoGemu. Yeah.- SaitoGemu。是啊.
They're huge.他们是巨大的。
- They're really big.-他们真的大。
- Really?真的吗？
- Horror games?-恐怖游戏？
- Uh...-嗯…
Have you heard of...你听说过吗…
Oh, what's one of theirs?哦，他们的一个？
- Harlech Shadow.-哈里克的影子。
- Harlech Shadow? Yes, I have.-哈里克的影子吗？是的我签了。
I used to play that in my我曾经在我的
buddy David Ludwig's basement好友David Ludwig的地下室
when we were, like, seventh grade.当我们是，像，第七级。
Well, that's Shou Saito.哦，那是Shou Saito。
It's his company.这是他的公司。
- He's like this genius, super secretive.-他像这个天才，超级秘密。
- Okay.-好的。
And apparently, they're显然，他们是
working on this new project.在这个新项目上工作。
Big money involved. Groundbreaking.涉及的大资金。开创性的。
But nobody knows anything about it.但没有人知道它的任何东西。
Well, maybe if I play my cards right嗯，也许如果我打牌我的权利
I can get you an exclusive with Shou.我可以给你一个独家的。
Hmm? Fo Shou? Yeah?嗯？Fo Shou？是吗？
You should take a photo.你应该拍一张照片。
Seriously, if you get a photo of说真的，如果你得到一张照片
anything that they're working on,任何他们正在做的事情，
that's a fuckload more这是一个fuckload更多
money than four pound signs.钱比四磅的迹象。
Cool.酷。
Well, where is this place?好的，这个地方在哪里？
Mr. Copper.Copper先生。
Oh, hi. Um... Just Cooper.哦，嗨。嗯...只是库柏。
Mr. Cooper, I apologize.Cooper先生，我向你道歉。
Just Cooper is fine.只是库珀是好的。
Then, in that case, I'm just Katie.那么，在这种情况下，我只是凯蒂。
- Hi.-嗨。
- Follow me.-跟着我。
- Oh, yeah.-哦，是的。
- I'll just get my pack here.-我会在这里得到我的包。
- Rav will take care of that.Rav会照顾。
Oh, Rav will take care哦，Rav会照顾
of that. Okay, great.那。好的，伟大的。
That's good. I don't那太好了。我不
wanna carry it anyway.无论如何都要携带它。
Rav kind of reminds me ofRAV类让我想起
like an end-of-level boss.像一个老板的结束。
You know, haiukon. Just...你知道，haiukon。只是…
- How was your journey?-你的旅程怎么样？
- Great. Thanks.-大。谢谢.
- The car pick you up okay?-车来接你好吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
Wow.真的.
This way.这种方式.
Are they... seeing? It's cool. Very cool.他们是…看到了吗？很酷。非常酷的。
Wow.真的.
Come on.来吧。
Feel like I'm gonna go meet Dumbledore.感觉我要去见邓布利多。
Hope I get Gryffindor.希望我能得到Gryffindor。
I'm gonna need your phone and anything我需要你的电话和任何东西
else you might use to send and receive.你可能会使用发送和接收。
- A little paranoid, don't you think?-有点偏执，你不认为吗？
- Can't be too careful.-不能太小心。
Okay, there you go.好吧，你去了。
Wow, you really are哇，你真的
paranoid. Whoa!偏执狂.哇！
It's white.它是白色的。
Um...嗯...
Okay, so I'm guessing this says, like,好吧，所以我猜这说，像，
I agree to have my kidneys harvested?我同意我的肾脏收获吗？
Actually, it's a pretty事实上，这是一个美丽的
standard NDA-disclaimer thing.标准协议免责事。
Okay.可以.
It's important that you realize there重要的是你在那里意识到
is a small medical procedure involved.是一个小的医疗程序。
Sorry, for a game?对不起，为了一场比赛？
Nothing permanent and we没有什么是永恒的
don't harvest your kidneys,不要收获你的肾脏，
- I promise.-我保证。
- Okay.-好的。
It's no more invasive than它的侵入性比
having your ears pierced.有你的耳朵穿孔。
"Confidential information,“机密信息，
brain downloads脑下载
the game, duration, termination..."游戏、持续时间、终止……”
Um... The signature page...嗯...签名页…
- Where do I sign?-我在哪里签名？
- Oh.-哦。
- Signature. Yeah.签名。是啊.
- There's a page missing.-有一个缺页。
- Okay.-好的。
- Just a moment.-只是一个时刻。
Alright. I'll just wait... here.好吧。我会等待…在这里.
What the fuck?什么他妈的？
- All good?-都好吗？
- All good.-所有好。
What we're working on is an我们正在做的是一个
interactive augmented reality system.交互式增强现实系统。
- Like VR?-像虚拟现实？
- More like layers on top of reality.-更像是现实的层。
Oh.哦.
Okay. Um...可以.嗯...
Ow.OW。
Um...嗯...
- What's that?-那是什么？
- We call this a mushroom.我们称之为蘑菇。
- Like Mario Brothers?-像马里奥兄弟？
- If you like.如果你喜欢。
- You're qualified to do this, right?-你有资格这样做，对吗？
- I haven't killed anyone yet.-我还没有杀任何人。
May I?我可以吗？
Yeah.是啊.
All done.所有做的。
- That was it?-是吗？
- See, I told you I'm good.-看，我告诉过你我很好。
- No, don't worry, it's not permanent.-不，别担心，这不是永久性的。
- Um...-嗯…
Okay. What is this, like, some kind可以.这是什么，像，某种
of memory test or something like that?记忆测试或类似的东西？
- You'll find out.-你会发现。
- Oh, okay.-哦，好吗。
You might feel a slight你可能会感到轻微的
twinge as it initializes.他为它初始化。
Oh, okay.哦，好吗。
Commencing at 5:38.开始在38。
- You ready?-你准备好了吗？
- Yes, sir!-是的，先生！
Nearly there.近有。
I thought I turned that off.我以为我拒绝了。
- All done. You feel okay?-所有做的。你觉得好吗？
- Uh-huh.-嗯哼。
Feel great.感觉很好。
- Watch the targets.-看目标。
- Okay.-好的。
Um...嗯...
Is...是...
What do you see?你看到了什么？
Like a... um...就像..嗯...
Like a video game gopher.像一个视频游戏网站。
- Is it more detailed now?-现在更详细的吗？
- Yeah.-是的。
Yep, yeah.是的，是的。
- And now?-现在？
- Holy fuck!-神圣的他妈的！
Holy shit! He... Fuck. He's right...天啊!他…性交.他是对的…
He's right... He's right... Can I...他是对的…他是对的…我可以吗...
Whoo!喔！
He's not real. He's a他不是真的。他是一个
sort of mental projection.心理投射。
- You can see him. I can't.-你可以看到他。我做不到。
- You can't?-你不能？
Wow! Oh, okay.真的!哦，好吗。
Give him a whack.给他一个重击。
Give him a whack? Oh. Okay, alright.给他一份了吗？哦.好吧，好吧。
Okay! Alright, so just like whack-a-mole.可以!好吧，就像打地鼠。
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
- I've played it a million times. Okay.-我已经玩了一百万次。可以.
Alright.好吧。
Here we go. Come on up.让我们开始吧。来吧。
Oh! Where you coming up?哦!你要上哪儿？
No. No.号号
No.不.
Oh!哦!
Alright. Stay down.好吧。蹲下.
Oh! Okay.哦!可以.
Good game. Very good game.好的游戏。很好的游戏。
You are so adorable.你是如此可爱。
Okay, bye. Bye.好的，再见。再见.
- Is that it?-是吗？
- Afraid so.害怕如此。
Oh.哦.
Now, were the gophers现在，是地鼠
two-dimensional or three?二维或三？
Three. No, no, no.三。不，不，不。
3D, super 3D. Like... Yeah.3D，超级3D…是啊.
- Now this is just a limited test demo.-现在这只是一个有限的测试演示。
- That was a demo?-这是一个演示？
I think you should beta test the我认为你应该测试测试
full experience we're working on.充分的经验，我们正在努力。
There'd be more money in it,里面会有更多的钱，
of course. If you're game?当然.如果你是游戏？
Yeah, yeah, yeah.是的，是的，是的。
Uh-huh, I'm game. I'm game.嗯，我是游戏。我是游戏。
- This is Shou Saito.这是Shou Saito。
- Oh!-哦！
- You must be our latest volunteer.-你一定是我们最新的志愿者。
- Hi.-嗨。
This is really great. Hi.这真的很棒。你好.
Hi.你好.
I just... I wanted to say that我只是…我想说的是
the mole game, super fun.鼹鼠游戏，超级好玩。
Super fun... fun.超级好玩的…乐趣。
- Fun?有趣的？
- Fun.有趣的。
- Fun is good.-乐趣是好的。
- Yeah. Oh.-是的。哦.
- Playing games is good.玩游戏是好的。
- Mm.毫米。
Your heart goes faster.你的心走得更快。
- You smile.-你的微笑。
- Yeah.-是的。
Yeah. Or, um... scream.是啊.或者，嗯…尖叫。
Oh!哦!
I have always liked to我一直很喜欢
make the player jump.使玩家跳。
Frightened. You get scared, you jump.害怕。你害怕，你跳。
- Afterwards, you feel good.-之后，你感觉很好。
- Yeah.-是的。
You glow.你的光芒。
Why?为什么？
Oh, um...哦，嗯…
Because of the adrenaline rush.因为肾上腺素激增。
- Yes.-是的。
- Yeah.-是的。
But mostly because you are still alive.但主要是因为你还活着。
You have faced your greatest你面对着你最伟大的
fears in a safe environment.安全环境中的恐惧。
It is a release of fear.这是一种恐惧的释放。
It liberates you.它解放了你。
Yeah. I mean, totally.是啊.我的意思是，完全。
What we are working on now我们现在正在做的
is the most personal survival是最个人的生存
horror game in history.历史上的恐怖游戏。
Cool.酷。
One that works out how to scare一个工作如何吓唬
you by using your own mind.你通过使用你自己的想法。
Whoa. That... That sounds crazy.哇。那…听起来很疯狂。
Can't wait!不能等了！
I'm uploading a neural net package.我上传一个神经网络包。
Neural net packing, neural net. Hmm.神经网络包装，神经网络。隐马尔可夫模型.
Name could use a little work, I think.名字可以用一点工作，我想。
It's all 90s.这都是90年代。
I'm just kidding, it's a good name.我只是在开玩笑，这是个好名字。
It's state of the art它的艺术状态
intelligence software.智能软件。
It learns and adapts on the fly.它在飞行中学习和适应。
It'll monitor your brain activity它会监视你的大脑活动
and try and work out并尝试和解决
how best to frighten you如何最好地吓唬你
and then adjust to your然后调整到你的
experience accordingly.相应的经历。
-Whoa!哇哦！
- Are you ready?-你准备好了吗？
- Oh, yeah.-哦，是的。
- Beam me up. Here we go, lock and load.-束我。在这里，我们去，锁和负载。
- Eyes closed.闭上眼睛。
- Time is currently 6:17 p.m.时间现在是下午6:17
- Okay.-好的。
It's uploading. Five, four,它的上传。五，四，
three, two, one.三，两个，一个。
How are you feeling?你感觉怎么样？
Um...嗯...
I feel good. I feel normal.我感觉很好。我感觉很正常。
Okay. Stand up, slowly.可以.站起来，慢慢地。
Are you ready to play?你准备好玩了吗？
Isn't this the这不是
Harlech Shadow house?哈里克影子的房子吗？
It's part of the estate.这是遗产的一部分。
The gamekeeper's lodge, actually.猎场看守人的小屋里，其实。
But, yeah, this was the model.但是，是的，这是模型。
The layout was replicated for复制的布局
the game and the texture scanned.游戏和纹理扫描。
Wow!真的!
Very, very cool.非常，非常酷。
So what's the game, what do I do?那么，什么是游戏，我该怎么办？
You don't have to do anything.你不需要做任何事情。
You just stay in here alone,你就呆在这里，
see how long you last until看看你持续多久，直到
you're too scared to continue.你太害怕了，不敢继续。
So all I have to do is,所以我所要做的就是，
like, stay here?喜欢，呆在这里吗？
And I get paid for that?我会得到报酬吗？
I'll be back in the control room, watching.我会在控制室里，看。
There are cameras all over,到处都是相机，
so no stealing the silverware.所以没有偷银器。
And now there's this.现在有这个。
- And what's this?-这是什么？
- It's an earpiece.这是一个耳机。
Oh!哦!
Yeah, just pop it in, and you and I是的，只是弹出它，你和我
will be in contact the whole time.将在接触的整个时间。
Oh, cool.哦，酷。
And I can, like, talk to you,我可以，像，和你说话，
and you'll hear it? Great, that's great.你会听到吗？太好了，那太好了。
Now, nothing you'll see现在，你什么也看不见
can physically harm you.可以伤害你的身体。
It's all just audio-visual,这一切只是视听，
like the gopher game.像Gopher游戏。
Oh, okay.哦，好吗。
But if it does get too intense,但如果它变得太激烈，
we can pull you out at any time我们随时都可以把你拉出来
- and stop the experiment.-停止实验。
- Okay.-好的。
Is there a safe word you can think of?你能想到的一个安全的词吗？
Something easy to remember in distress?有什么容易记住的痛苦？
How about the word "stop"?“停止”这个词怎么样？
- Good choice. "Stop" it is.-好的选择。”停止“它是。
- Yeah.-是的。
Okay, we'll leave you好吧，我们会离开你
to enjoy your evening.享受你的夜晚。
- Alright.-好的。
- You'll hear from me in a moment.-你会听到我的一刻。
Just make yourself at home.只是让自己在家里。
Okay, all right.好的，好的。
Well, take her easy.好吧，带她轻松。
Harlech... Shadow.哈勒赫…阴影。
Is this real? Yeah, it's real.这是真的吗？是的，这是真的。
That's real. It's really dead.这是真实的。它真的死了。
- Cooper.- Cooper。
- Oh, hey.-哦，嘿。
- Are you hearing me?-你在听我说吗？
- Loud and clear.-响亮和清晰。
Oh!哦!
Reaching for the Dutch达到荷兰
courage already, I see.我已经有勇气了，我明白。
- I'm afraid that wine's non-alcoholic.-我恐怕酒是不含酒精的。
- Lame.瘸的。
- Well, we need you with a clear head.-嗯，我们需要你一个清醒的头脑。
- Okay. Fair point. Fair point.-好的。公平点。公平点。
This is high-quality craftsmanship.这是高品质的工艺。
This is nice.这个真不错。
Yeah. It's good woodwork.是啊.这是很好的木制品。
- That's this place.-这是这个地方。
- Full marks for observation.全标记观察。
Mm-hmm! Yep!嗯！是的!
Alright, there we go.好吧，我们去。
Ah!啊啊啊啊啊！
- Oh, shit.哦，该死的。
- What's up?-怎么了？
I just forgot I don't have my phone.我只是忘了我没有我的电话。
I keep going for it,我一直坚持下去，
I forget it's not in my pocket.我忘了它不在我的口袋里。
And there's, uh... no TV here, so...还有，呃…这里没有电视，所以…
Welcome to the 19th century.欢迎来到第十九世纪。
No TV, no Internet, no wi-fi.没有电视，没有互联网，没有Wi-Fi。
Yeah. No wonder people were seeing shit.是啊.难怪有人看到屎。
Probably were just bored可能只是无聊
out of their gourds.从他们的葫芦。
Well, that's the leading嗯，这是领先的
theory about ghost sightings.关于鬼魂目击事件理论。
The mind plays tricks头脑玩把戏
when less stimulated.当少刺激。
Fewer distractions,少分心，
people saw more ghosts.人们看到更多的鬼。
Isn't that a nice piece of info?这不是一个很好的信息吗？
Well, they got literature, though.嗯，他们有文学，虽然。
That's pretty sweet, right?这很甜，对吗？
Oh, my God, I can't remember the哦，我的天，我不记得了
actual last time that I read a book.我读一本书的最后一次。
To think people used认为人们使用
to do this on purpose.故意这样做。
I know. Crazy. Why?我知道.疯子.为什么？
- You know, I don't think I've...-你知道，我不认为我有…
- Shh, alright?嘘，好吗？
I need to get into some old-school我需要进入一些旧学校
shit here. Concentrate.妈的在这里。集中。
Pardon me.请原谅我。
Can I point out your heart我能指出你的心
rate just increased?利率增加？
Yeah. Well, it should have cos是啊.嗯，它应该有
there's a huge crazy spider.有一个巨大的疯狂的蜘蛛。
You see a spider?你看见一只蜘蛛吗？
- You don't... you don't see that?-你不。你看不到吗？
- No.-不。
Don't... Don't walk. Don't...不要...不要走。不要...
Holy shit!天啊!
Tough guy like you, scared of spiders.像你这样的强硬的家伙，害怕蜘蛛。
Yeah, I'm just not fond of them.是的，我只是不喜欢他们。
It's worked out you're它是你的工作
an arachnophobe quickly.一个arachnophobe快。
It's probing for weak spots.它在探索薄弱点。
God damn it.该死的上帝。
Fucker!混蛋!
Yeah!是啊!
Um...嗯...
Okay.可以.
Yeah, well, yeah.是的，嗯，是的。
Whole lot more realistic整个地段更逼真
than the gopher game.比地鼠游戏。
It's good. It's good graphics.很好。它是很好的图形。
It's good, uh... Yeah.很好，嗯…是啊.
Weak sauce.弱酱。
- What is it?-它是什么？
- Just...-只是…
Nothing. Nothing.没有什么.没有什么.
Here with the figures.这里的数字。
There's a... No. There's a light on...有一个..不，有一个光…
now, in the...现在，在…
Can you... zoom in and... Zoom in on it?你能...放大和缩小…放大它？
And you can see what I'm talking about.你可以看到我在说什么。
Whoa!哇！
- Cooper...- Cooper…
- And now there's... Shh!-现在有了..嘘！
There's a guy in the window.窗户里有一个家伙。
That wasn't...那不是。
Yeah.是啊.
And now he's gone.现在他已经走了。
Now nobody's in the window.现在没有人在窗口中。
Which is the...这是…
Mm-hmm.嗯嗯。
Yeah, there's a...是的，有一个..
Just leaky pipes.只是漏管。
I knew it. It was leaky pipes, like...我早知道了。这是漏水的管子，像…
Holy fuck!圣操！
Fuck!性交!
Oh! Oh!哦!哦!
Okay.可以.
That got me. You got me.那得到了我。你难住我了.
What are you seeing?你看到了什么？
Like a creepy fucking guy.像一个令人毛骨悚然的家伙。
Wow, just...哇，只是…
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!我的天！啊，天哪！
He kinda looks like Josh Peters.他有点像Josh Peters。
- It's Josh Peters! You're Josh Peters!这是Josh Peters！你是Josh Peters！
- Sorry?对不起？
You're Josh Peters from high school!你从高中Josh Peters！
From a guy I know at high school.从我认识的一个在高中的人。
The system could be mining some of该系统可以挖掘一些
your personal memories for texture.你对质地的个人记忆。
Was Josh Peters someone是Josh Peters的人
you were scared of?你害怕了？
He was a bully. I wasn't scared.他是个恶棍。我不害怕。
I wasn't scared of him,我不害怕他，
but he was a bully and...但他是一个恶棍和…
Man! Take a couple of Krav男人！以一对夫妇的Krav
Maga classes and I'd be ready.该类和我已经准备好了。
I'd be ready!我会准备好！
Kali ma! Dah!卡里玛！大！
I'm gonna get some wine. Re-up.我要买些酒。再起来。
I'd offer you some, but I don't我会给你一些，但我不给你
think you can drink it so...认为你可以喝它…
Whoo-hoo-hoo!呼呼呼呼！
Catch ya later, Peters.赶上亚后，彼得斯。
This non-alcoholic wine is pretty good.这种不含酒精的酒是很不错的。
I'm not like a expert or anything,我不喜欢一个专家或任何东西，
but it's kinda great.但它有点伟大。
I was in France.我那时正在法国。
I stayed at this, like, vineyard,我呆在这，像，葡萄园，
and they had this wine, like,他们有这酒，如，
grape-stomping festival.葡萄跺脚节。
Now that, that wine was good. I know that.现在，那酒是好的。我知道。
You're being discursive.你的话语。
- What is discursive? Discursive?什么是话语？话语？
- Talkative.-健谈。
- Mm-hmm.-哦。
- Rambling.-漫步。
Is that a problem?这是一个问题吗？
People sometimes talk人们有时说
more when they're afraid.当他们害怕的时候。
Helps compensate for the fear.有助于弥补恐惧。
- Masks it, too.-面具它，太。
- Oh, yeah?-哦，是吗？
Similar to when you've got当你有了类似的
the TV on late at night.深夜的电视。
The voices make you feel less alone.这些声音让你感到不那么孤独。
Even though you are alone.即使你独自一人。
You aren't scaring me, Katie.你没有吓到我，凯蒂。
Pity.可惜。
Is there like a refrigerator here?这里有冰箱吗？
There's some snacks in the cupboard.柜里有一些零食。
Alrighty. Eenie meenie, miney...好了。黑白猜，没钱…
Mo! Alright.瞬间!好吧。
Okay, ginger snaps.好吧，姜脆饼。
Let's see.让我想想。
Yeah, yeah, yeah. This'll do.是的，是的，是的。这将做。
Now... um...现在...嗯...
He's gonna be right behind this door他会在这扇门后面
when I close it, isn't he?当我关上它，不是吗？
Yeah, that's how this works.是的，这是如何工作。
Knew it. Jump scares get pretty old...知道它。跳的恐惧得到相当大的…
Fuck!性交!
Oh, God.哦，上帝。
- What the hell is that?-那到底是什么？
- What do you see?-你看到了什么？
Holy shit!天啊!
A fucking... Uh...他妈的…休斯敦大学...
Hard to explain.很难解释。
It's like a huge-ass spider with a它就像一只巨大的蜘蛛
face and dicks coming out of his mouth.脸和鸭子从他的嘴里出来的。
It's...它..
Peters. Peters is inside.彼得斯。彼得斯在里面。
Like a Peters-spider mash-up.像彼得斯的蜘蛛侠。
Ah, Katie! Are you doing啊，凯蒂！你在做
this, or is this fucking me?这，或者这他妈的我？
- I think that's all you.-我想这是你的一切。
- I'm so fucked up!我真的搞砸了！
God! Fuck!上帝！性交!
Holy shit, you're fucking gross.神圣的屎，你他妈的毛。
Yeah...是啊...
Sorry, can you say again?对不起，你能再说一遍吗？
Katie, hello?凯蒂，你好吗？
Damn it, Katie!该死的，凯蒂！
Whenever you come back online,每当你回来在线，
just say the word.只要说一句话。
No, I'm not scared, just... bored.不，我不害怕，只是…无聊的.
That you guys?你们这些家伙？
Coming to fix the earpiece?来修耳机吗？
That's probably a good idea.这可能是个好主意。
Yeah. Yeah.是啊.是啊.
Fuck it, man!他妈的，人！
Come on!来吧！
You're in danger.你处于危险中。
Sonja?索尼娅？
Now we're talking.现在我们在谈论。
Alright, this is incredible.好吧，这是难以置信的。
This... very impressive.这…非常令人印象深刻的。
I am thoroughly impressed.我彻底的印象。
I am... Wow! Wow!我是...真的!真的!
You look so real.你看起来如此真实。
You're, like, just like her.你是，喜欢，就像她。
I mean, wow.我的意思是，哇。
Except... you're just除了…你只是
unfortunately not... um...不幸的是，不…嗯...
- Cooper, what are you doing?Cooper，你在干什么？
- Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on.-等待，等待。坚持住，坚持住。
- Cooper, you're in danger.Cooper，你有危险。
- Shh! Quiet. Quiet! I need to think.-嘘！安静的.安静的!我需要思考。
You're fucking real.你他妈的真的。
You are real. You're real.你是真实的。你是真实的。
- Cooper, you're in...Cooper，你在…
- You're Sonja. You're actually here.-你是索尼娅。你实际上是在这里。
- Are you actually here right now?-你现在真的在这里吗？
- I'm real. I'm actually here.-我是真实的。我实际上在这里。
- God.-上帝。
- And we have to go.-我们必须走。
- You have to listen to me.-你必须听我说。
- How are you here?-你怎么在这里？
You know that photo that you sent me?你知道你寄给我的那张照片吗？
I dug around and apparently我四处挖，显然
Shou Saito took out a patentShou Saito拿出一个专利
for a computer brain interface last year.去年的一个计算机脑接口。
How are you real? I don't...你是真的吗？我不...
Okay, fuck. I don't...好吧，他妈的。我不...
They brought you here!他们把你带到这里！
You are, you're real,你是，你是真实的，
and they brought you here,他们把你带到这里，
and they're trying to fuck with me.他们试图跟我做爱。
Nice try, good try.很好的尝试，很好的尝试。
I get it. It's part of the test.我得到它。这是测试的一部分。
His patent got rejected outright. They他的专利被彻底否决了。他们
said it was insane, it was dangerous.说这是疯了，这是危险的。
Wow. Really? How much真的.真的？多少钱
are they paying you?他们在给你钱吗？
Honestly. Cos you're老实说。因为你
killing it right now.现在杀死它。
- Have they given you something?-他们给你什么了吗？
- Sorry, I thought you were fake.-对不起，我以为你是假的。
But now I know you're real,但现在我知道你是真实的，
I'm being a really terrible host.我是一个非常可怕的主人。
I got some non-alcoholic wine.我有一些不含酒精的酒。
Might put us in the mood.可能会让我们的心情。
- Cooper, what I want to do is...Cooper，我想做的是…
- We'll talk about it in the kitchen.我们会在厨房里谈论它。
- Cooper!- Cooper！
- Sonja, relax, okay?-宋，放松点，好吗？
Give it up. I know, the放弃它。我知道，
jig's up, okay? Let it go.跳了起来，好吗？过去的事就让它过去吧。
Look, Cooper, there's more.看，Cooper，还有更多。
Five people have disappeared五人消失了
in the past year.在过去的一年里。
All tourists, all registered所有的游客，所有的注册
with that stupid odd jobs app.有了这个愚蠢的奇怪的工作。
Oh, yeah? Wow. God, that's crazy.哦，是吗？真的.上帝，这太疯狂了。
Whatever they're doing to you,不管他们对你做什么，
whatever they've done to you,不管他们对你做了什么，
it's dangerous, and we really这是危险的，我们真的
have to go now, Cooper.现在就去，Cooper。
Okay, okay. Alright.好吧，好的。好吧。
- Well, if your story's true...-好吧，如果你的故事是真的…
- Cooper.- Cooper。
- Then how'd you find me?-那你怎么找到我？
- What?-什么？
How'd you know where I am?你怎么知道我在哪里？
It's a games company,这是一家游戏公司，
I looked up the address.我抬头看了看地址。
Yeah, really?是的，真的吗？
No, no, no, no. How'd you不，不，不，你怎么了
find me here? This place.在这里找到我？这个地方。
- I tracked you.我跟踪你。
- You tracked me?-你跟踪我？
Yeah, with your GPS on your是的，与你的全球定位系统在你的
phone. Find My Friends.电话。找到我的朋友。
Find My Friends? That would've找到我的朋友吗？那会
worked, but they took my phone.工作，但他们拿了我的电话。
And it's in a building, like, a mile away.它在一个建筑物，像，一英里以外。
So, yeah, nice try.所以，是的，很好的尝试。
That's right.这是正确的.
So much for women outsmarting men.这么多的女人赢得男人。
Singularity that!奇异点！
Look, all I'm saying is that看，我要说的是
I think that you could've我想你可能会
come up with a better story,想出一个更好的故事，
it could have been funny or...它可能是有趣的或…
Okay, alright, don't be pissed.好了，好了，别生气。
Do you ever wonder how your你曾经想知道你的
bank account got hacked?银行账户被黑客攻击了？
What are you doing?你在做什么？
- I cloned your card as you were asleep.-我克隆了你的信用卡，当你睡着了。
- Whoa. Okay.哇哦。可以.
Put the knife down.把刀放下。
What are you going to do with that?那你打算怎么办？
I drew your attention to this job.我把你的注意力吸引到了这份工作。
Sonja, put the fucking knife索尼娅，把那该死的刀
down, okay? It's not funny.下来，好吗？这不好笑。
Should've called your mum, Cooper.应该打电话给你的妈妈，Cooper。
- But you called me, and I led you here...-但你打电话给我，我带你到这里…
- Sonja.-索尼娅。
- You know what?-你知道吗？
- ...like a breadcrumb trail.-…像面包屑。
Put the knife down. Drop the act.把刀放下。放弃行为。
Okay, seriously, drop the knife, Sonja.好吧，说真的，放下刀，索尼娅。
It's not fucking funny. Put the knife...这不是他妈的有趣。把刀…
This isn't what I signed up for.这不是我注册的。
I'm fucking done, okay?我他妈的干了，好吗？
Fuck!性交!
What the fuck?什么他妈的？
Oh, fuck! Oh!哦，他妈的！哦!
Holy fuck!圣操！
Stop!停止！
Fuck!性交!
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!哦，他妈的！哦，他妈的！
- Cooper.- Cooper。
- Katie!-凯蒂！
- Cooper, what's happening?Cooper，发生什么事了？
What the fuck happened?他妈的发生了什么？
What's happening? We've been talking.发生什么事了？我们一直在谈论。
You've not been responding.你没有回应。
- You said I wouldn't feel anything!-你说我什么都感觉不到！
- What are you seeing? What's there?-你看到什么了？那里有什么？
- Fuck! She's gone now.-他妈的！她现在走了。
- Who's gone?-谁走了？
Oh, my God, I-I felt it.哦，我的上帝，我觉得。
There's a knife in my arm!我的胳膊上有一把刀！
- In my shoulder.在我的肩膀上。
- Cooper, who was there?Cooper，谁在那里？
- Fuck... Sonja.-他妈的…索尼娅。
- Who?-谁？
Sonja. She's this girl that I know,索尼娅。她是我所知道的女孩，
that fucking... She stabbed me.他妈的…她刺伤了我。
- She had a fucking knife.-她有一把他妈的刀。
- Nothing can harm you, Cooper.没有什么能伤害你，Cooper。
- No, no, no, no. She was solid.-不，不，不，不，她是固体。
- No, she can't have been.-不，她不可能。
She... I was stabbed! I would know!她…我被刺伤了！我会知道！
Nothing you see can你看不到什么
harm or even touch you.伤害甚至触摸你。
It's purely audio-visual.这是纯粹的视听。
- There's no physical sensation.-没有身体的感觉。
- Fuck! Yes, there was!-他妈的！是的，有！
- Cooper, you need to calm down.Cooper，你需要冷静下来。
- I know because I felt it, okay?-我知道，因为我感觉到了，好吗？
I felt her arm, it was warm,我摸到她的手臂，很温暖，
and I felt her fucking我感觉到了她他妈的
stab me in the shoulder.在肩膀上刺我。
- That's not possible.-这是不可能的。
- Oh, my God.-哦，我的上帝。
- It's not possible, Cooper.这是不可能的，Cooper。
- Yeah, it is! Yeah, it is!-是的，它是！是的，它是！
Physical sensations身体的感觉
shouldn't be possible.不应该是可能的。
- Unless, I mean...-除非，我的意思是…
- Oh, God. Unless what?哦，上帝。除非什么？
I don't know. The neuron net,我不知道。神经元网络，
it could have maybe worked out它可能有可能解决
some means of replicating一些复制的方法
physical experiences,物理的经验，
- but that would be unprecedented.-但这将是前所未有的。
- Jesus Christ.- Jesus Christ。
Okay, you know what? Stop the game.好吧，你知道吗？停止游戏。
I want out. Just pull me out now.我想出去。现在就把我拉出来。
Stop, stop, stop. Safe停止，停止，停止。保险柜
word. Fucking stop!字。他妈的别！
- Okay, okay, just let us work it out.-好吧，好吧，让我们一起努力吧。
- Oh, God.哦，上帝。
No, I want this fucking thing out now.不，我现在要这个该死的东西。
Cooper, do not attemptCooper，不要尝试
to remove that yourself.要删除你自己。
Removing it yourself除它自己
is extremely dangerous.是非常危险的。
Stop that, that could kill you!停止，这可能会杀死你！
Just stay calm!只是保持冷静！
Is that Shou?那是手吗？
Is that Shou? What's he saying?那是手吗？他在说什么？
What's he saying?他在说什么？
Okay, Cooper. We're gonna好吧，Cooper。我们会
commence with deactivation.开始失活。
Oh, that's great news.哦，这是伟大的消息。
We need you to follow instructions我们需要你按照指示
and make it to the access point.并使之进入到接入点。
The access point? Great.访问点？伟大的.
Where the fuck's the access point?他妈的在哪里的接入点？
- Oh, fuck! More stairs? Come on!哦，他妈的！更多的楼梯？来吧！
- Just one more level.-只有一个更多的水平。
- Trust me.-相信我。
- Okay.-好的。
Left at the top.左顶部。
- Okay, which door?-好的，哪一扇门？
- Room at the end.-最后的房间。
What is it?这是怎么一回事？
There's gonna be something会有东西
behind there. I can feel it.后面。我能感觉到它。
- Something like...-类似的东西…
- Like what?-喜欢什么？
Some personal fucked-up shit.个人的一些混乱的狗屎。
Like... I don't know, I could像…我不知道，我可以
feel it digging around in my head.感觉它在我的脑海里挖掘。
Cooper, get to the door.Cooper走到门口。
It's gonna be like my mum,它会像我的妈妈，
I don't know, dead.我不知道，死了。
- Your mum?-你妈妈？
- Fucking swinging from a fucking beam.-他妈的从一个横梁上荡秋千。
- Your mother is not in there.-你的母亲不在那里。
- You're not in control of this!-你不在控制这个！
It's in my head. It它在我的脑海里。它
fucking knows. It knows.他妈的知道。它知道。
- It knows!-它知道！
- It knows what?-它知道什么？
It knows I got this thing with my mum.它知道我得到了这个东西与我的妈妈。
Cooper, I promise you,Cooper，我答应你，
she's not in there.她不在那里。
- Now open the door.-现在打开门。
- Oh, my God.-哦，我的上帝。
It's the only way I can这是我唯一的办法
get you out. Listen to me.带你出去。听我说。
Okay, Okay. Fuck. Okay.好吧，好的。性交.可以.
Whatever's in there cannot harm you.无论在那里，都不会伤害你。
But I can't get you out unless但我不能让你出来，除非
you open that door, Cooper.你打开门，Cooper。
Okay.可以.
Would you kindly open the door?请你把门打开好吗？
Here we go. Here we go.让我们开始吧。让我们开始吧。
Okay.可以.
Okay, okay, I'm in the room.好吧，好吧，我在房间里。
Where's the access point?接入点在哪里？
Access point?接入点？
- There is no access point.-没有访问点。
- What?-什么？
I'm fucking with you, Cooper.我他妈的你，Cooper。
I told you to come up here to我告诉过你到这里来
see if we've broken you enough看看我们是否已经打破了你足够
to obey instructions without question.毫无疑问地服从命令。
- And we have.-我们有。
- Oh, no, no, no.哦，不，不，不。
Katie, come on. Katie, come on, let me out!凯蒂，来吧。凯蒂，来吧，让我出去！
Katie, let me out, come on! What the fuck!凯蒂，让我出去，来吧！到底怎么了!
Oh, what are you gonna do?哦，你要怎么办？
Oh, what are you doing to me?哦，你在对我做什么？
- Why are you doing this?-你为什么要这样做？
- You thought you'd see your mother.-你以为你会看到你的母亲。
- Oh, fuck!哦，他妈的！
- What does she look like?-她长的什么样子？
Your mother, can you describe her face?你妈妈，你能描述一下她的脸吗？
Her hair colour?她的头发颜色？
She...她…
Is she tall, short, fat, thin?她高，矮，胖，瘦吗？
- Where did you grow up?你在哪里长大的？
- She...-她…
What's your favourite band?你最喜欢的乐队是什么？
Your favourite flavour ice cream?你最喜欢的口味冰淇淋？
The name of the girl who stabbed you?那个刺伤你的女孩的名字？
You don't know any of你不知道任何的
these things, do you?这些东西，是吗？
Don't you think that's odd?你不觉得这很奇怪吗？
It's fucking taking my memories!这是他妈的带走我的回忆！
Overwriting them, technically.覆盖它们，技术。
Fuck.性交.
Look in the mirror behind you.在你身后的镜子。
Do you recognize yourself?你认识你自己吗？
Do you even know who you're looking at?你甚至知道你在看谁吗？
Soon you won't be anything.很快你就不会是什么。
You'll be just like your dad.你会像你爸爸。
Shut up, shut up, shut up.闭嘴，闭嘴，闭嘴。
- That's what really scares you, isn't it?-这真的让你害怕，不是吗？
- Stop it.-停止它。
- Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!-闭嘴！闭嘴!闭嘴!
- You're going the same place he did.-你要去他做的同一个地方。
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!闭嘴!闭嘴!闭嘴!
- You're going nowhere.-你去哪儿了。
- Shut up! Shut up.-闭嘴！闭嘴.
You should have你应该有
called mum. She's all that's left.叫妈妈。她是剩下的一切。
- You abandoned her.-你抛弃了她。
- No, no, no, no!-不，不，不，不！
Get out of my head!从我的头上！
You'll never see her again.你再也见不到她了。
You'll never speak to her again.你再也不会跟她说话了。
- Never see her face.-永远看不到她的脸。
- Get out of my fucking head!-从我他妈的头上！
Get out of my fucking head!从我他妈的头上！
You're a bad son. You'll never你是个坏孩子。你永远不会
see your mother again.再次见到你的母亲。
You're going nowhere.你去哪儿了。
Straight into oblivion.直接进入遗忘。
You deserve it.你该享受一下。
You should have called her.你应该给她打电话的。
Get out of my fucking head!从我他妈的头上！
Get it out of my head!把它从我的头上！
Get it out of my fucking head!把它从我的头上拿出来！
Cooper, I'm gonna shut it off, okay?Cooper，我会把它关掉，好吗？
I just need to connect.我只需要连接。
Get it out of my head!把它从我的头上！
Oh, my God. Where am I?我的天！我在哪里？
Who are you?你是谁？
I can't stop it.我不能阻止它。
I don't know who I am.我不知道我是谁。
So I... So I need to go home.所以我...所以我需要回家。
The interface has data tendrils like roots.界面像根数据卷须。
They've dug in deeper他们挖的更深
than they're meant to.比他们的意思。
Threaded through your brain,穿过你的大脑，
taken over whole areas, I can't stop it.接管了整个地区，我不能阻止它。
I can't remove it, and I can't stop it.我不能删除它，我不能阻止它。
But I...但我...
But I don't know who I am.但我不知道我是谁。
I don't know... I don't know who I am.我不知道。我不知道我是谁。
I don't know who I am.我不知道我是谁。
I don't know.我不知道。
On behalf of Saito Game Team,在他比赛代表队，
I most humbly apologize.我最谦卑的道歉。
Who are you?你是谁？
What have you done to me?你对我做了什么？
- What have you done to me?-你对我做了什么？
- Put him with the others, please.-把他和其他人，请。
No, no, no, no! No, no, no!不，不，不，不！不，不，不！
Stop, stop, stop, stop! Stop, stop, stop!停，停，停，停！停止，停止，停止！
Stop, stop, stop, stop! No, don't, don't!停，停，停，停！不，不要，不要！
Don't! Don't!不要!不要!
Stop! Stop!停止！停止！
No!不!
Oh, fuck.哦，他妈的。
That was one second.那是一秒钟。
Either he's super susceptible to this or要么他是超级容易受到这个或
the software is way too powerful still.软件太强大了。
It's jumped from zero to它从零跳到
18K in five milliseconds...18k五毫秒…
I'm sorry. The experience was我很抱歉.经验
more powerful than intended, Mr. Cooper.比预期的更强大，Cooper先生。
I hope you can forgive us.我希望你能原谅我们。
...all luggage under……所有的行李
the seat in front of you.在你前面的座位。
All electronic devices should所有电子设备应
now be turned off and stowed现在被关掉，把
as they may interfere with the aircraft's因为他们可能会干扰飞机的
navigational and communication....导航和通信…
Mum?妈妈？
I have to call him.我必须给他打电话。
Why did Cooper go?Cooper为什么要走？
- I...- I.。
- Mom, I'm right here. I'm...-妈妈，我就在这里。我是...
- I'm right here, Mum.-我就在这里，妈妈。
- I have to call Cooper.我要打电话给库柏。
I have to call and我必须打电话和
make sure that he's safe.确保他是安全的。
I have to call him. I have to call him.我必须给他打电话。我必须给他打电话。
I have to call him.我必须给他打电话。
Mum?妈妈？
Mum!妈妈!
Mum! Mum! Mum! Mum!妈妈!妈妈!妈妈!妈妈!
__
"Mum."“妈妈。”
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --